<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<config xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/shopware/platform/master/src/Core/System/SystemConfig/Schema/config.xsd">

    <card>
        <title> </title>
        <title lang="de-DE"> </title>
        <title lang="nl-NL"> </title>
        <title lang="it-IT"> </title>
        <title lang="pt-PT"> </title>
        <title lang="es-ES"> </title>
        <title lang="sv-SE"> </title>
        <title lang="nb-NO"> </title>
        <title lang="pl-PL"> </title>
        <title lang="cs-CZ"> </title>
        <title lang="sl-SL"> </title>
        <title lang="hu-HU"> </title>
        <title lang="fi-FI"> </title>
        <title lang="da-DK"> </title>
        <title lang="sk-SK"> </title>
        <component name="mollie-pluginconfig-section-info">
            <name>molliePluginConfigSectionInfo</name>
        </component>
    </card>
    <card>
        <title>API</title>
        <title lang="de-DE">API</title>
        <title lang="nl-NL">API</title>
        <title lang="it-IT">API</title>
        <title lang="pt-PT">API</title>
        <title lang="es-ES">API</title>
        <title lang="sv-SE">API</title><title lang="nb-NO">API</title><title lang="pl-PL">API</title><title lang="cs-CZ">API</title><title lang="sl-SL">API</title><title lang="hu-HU">API</title><title lang="fi-FI">API</title><title lang="da-DK">API</title><title lang="sk-SK">API</title>

        <input-field type="password">
            <name>liveApiKey</name>
            <copyable>true</copyable>
            <label>Live Key</label>
            <label lang="de-DE">Live Key</label>
            <label lang="nl-NL">Live-sleutel</label>
            <label lang="it-IT">Chiave Live</label>
            <label lang="pt-PT">Chave ativa</label>
            <label lang="es-ES">Clave activa</label>
            <label lang="sv-SE">Live API-nyckel</label><label lang="nb-NO">Aktiv nøkkel</label><label lang="pl-PL">Live Klucz API</label><label lang="cs-CZ">Live klíč</label><label lang="sl-SL">Live Key</label><label lang="hu-HU">Élő kulcs</label><label lang="fi-FI">Live Avain</label><label lang="da-DK">Live nøgle</label><label lang="sk-SK">Live kľúč</label>
        </input-field>
        <input-field type="password">
            <name>testApiKey</name>
            <copyable>true</copyable>
            <label>Test Key</label>
            <label lang="de-DE">Test Key</label>
            <label lang="nl-NL">Test-sleutel</label>
            <label lang="it-IT">Chiave Test</label>
            <label lang="pt-PT">Chave de teste</label>
            <label lang="es-ES">Clave de prueba</label>
            <label lang="sv-SE">Test API-nyckel</label><label lang="nb-NO">Testnøkkel</label><label lang="pl-PL">Testowy Klucz API</label><label lang="cs-CZ">Testovací Klíč</label><label lang="sl-SL">Testni ključ</label><label lang="hu-HU">Teszt kulcs</label><label lang="fi-FI">Test Avain</label><label lang="da-DK">Testnøgle</label><label lang="sk-SK">Testovací kľúč</label>
        </input-field>
        <input-field type="bool">
            <name>testMode</name>
            <label>Test Mode</label>
            <label lang="de-DE">Test Modus</label>
            <label lang="nl-NL">Test Modus</label>
            <label lang="it-IT">Modalità test</label>
            <label lang="pt-PT">Modo de Teste</label>
            <label lang="es-ES">Modo de prueba</label>
            <label lang="sv-SE">Testläge</label><label lang="nb-NO">Testmodus</label><label lang="pl-PL">Tryb testowy</label><label lang="cs-CZ">Testovací režim</label><label lang="sl-SL">Testni način</label><label lang="hu-HU">Teszt üzemmód</label><label lang="fi-FI">Testitila</label><label lang="da-DK">Testtilstand</label><label lang="sk-SK">Testovací režim</label>
            <defaultValue>true</defaultValue>
            <helpText>Enables the test mode with the Mollie Sandbox payment page. The Storefront will also show (Test Mode) next to the payment method names.</helpText>
            <helpText lang="de-DE">Aktiviert den Testmodus mit der Mollie Sandbox Zahlungsseite. In der Storefront wird (Test Modus) neben den Zahlungsarten angezeigt.</helpText>
            <helpText lang="nl-NL">Staat de test modus toe met de Mollie Sandbox betalingspagina. De Storefront zal ook "(Test Mode)" tonen naast de naam van de betaalmethode.</helpText>
            <helpText lang="it-IT">Abilita la modalità test con la pagina di pagamento di Mollie Sandbox. Lo Storefront mostrerà anche (Modalità test) accanto ai nomi dei metodi di pagamento.</helpText>
            <helpText lang="pt-PT">Ativa o modo de teste com a página de pagamento do Mollie Sandbox. A loja também será mostrada (Modo de teste) ao lado dos nomes dos métodos de pagamento.</helpText>
            <helpText lang="es-ES">Habilita el modo de prueba con la página de pagos de Mollie Sandbox. También verás la tienda (Modo de prueba) junto a los nombres de los métodos de pago.</helpText>
            <helpText lang="sv-SE">Aktivera testläget med Mollies Sandbox betalningssida. Skyltfönstret kommer också visa (Testläge) bredvid betalningsmetodernas namn.</helpText><helpText lang="nb-NO">Aktiverer testmodus med Mollie Sandbox betalingsside. Butikkfronten vil også vise (Testmodus) ved siden av navnene på betalingsmetodene.</helpText><helpText lang="pl-PL">Ta opcja włącza tryb testowy z użyciem strony płatności Mollie Sandbox. W widoku sklepu obok nazw metod płatności będzie wyświetlana informacja "(Tryb testowy)".</helpText><helpText lang="cs-CZ">Aktivuje testovací režim s platební stránkou Mollie Sandbox. V obchodě se vedle názvů platebních metod také zobrazí označení (Testovací režim).</helpText><helpText lang="sl-SL">Omogoči testni način z Mollie Sandbox stranjo za plačilo. Trgovina bo prav tako prikazala (Testni način) poleg načinov plačila.</helpText><helpText lang="hu-HU">Engedélyezi a teszt üzemmódot a Mollie Sandbox fizetési oldalon. Az áruház is megjeleníti a (Teszt üzemmód) feliratot a fizetési módok neve mellett.</helpText><helpText lang="fi-FI">Ottaa käyttöön testitilan Mollie Sandbox -maksusivulla. Kaupanjulkisivu näkyy myös (testitilassa) maksutapojen nimien vieressä.</helpText><helpText lang="da-DK">Aktiverer testtilstanden med Mollie Sandbox betalingsside. Butikken vil også vise (Testtilstand) ved siden af betalingsmetodenavne.</helpText><helpText lang="sk-SK">Aktivuje testovací režim s platobnou stránkou Mollie Sandbox. V obchode sa pri názvoch platobných metód zobrazí označenie (Testovací režim).</helpText>
        </input-field>
        <component name="mollie-pluginconfig-section-api">
            <name>molliePluginConfigSectionApi</name>
        </component>
    </card>
    <card>
        <title>Logger</title>
        <title lang="de-DE">Logger</title>
        <title lang="nl-NL">Logger</title>
        <title lang="it-IT">Logger</title>
        <title lang="pt-PT">Logger</title>
        <title lang="es-ES">Logger</title>
        <title lang="sv-SE">Logger</title>
        <title lang="nb-NO">Logger</title>
        <title lang="pl-PL">Logger</title>
        <title lang="cs-CZ">Logger</title>
        <title lang="sl-SL">Logger</title>
        <title lang="hu-HU">Logger</title>
        <title lang="fi-FI">Logger</title>
        <title lang="da-DK">Logger</title>
        <title lang="sk-SK">Logger</title>
        <input-field type="bool">
            <name>debugMode</name>
            <label>Debug Mode</label>
            <label lang="de-DE">Debug Modus</label>
            <label lang="nl-NL">Debug Modus</label>
            <label lang="it-IT">Modalità Debug</label>
            <label lang="pt-PT">Modo de Depuração</label>
            <label lang="es-ES">Modo de depuración</label>
            <label lang="sv-SE">Felsökningsläge</label><label lang="nb-NO">Feilsøkingsmodus</label><label lang="pl-PL">Tryb debugowania</label><label lang="cs-CZ">Režim ladění</label><label lang="sl-SL">Način odpravljanja napak</label><label lang="hu-HU">Hibakeresési üzemmód</label><label lang="fi-FI">Virheenkorjaustila</label><label lang="da-DK">Fejlsøgningsmodus</label><label lang="sk-SK">Režim ladenia</label>
            <defaultValue>false</defaultValue>
            <helpText>Mollie has a custom log file in the Shopware log directory. This feature enables the extended logs with more information that could help to solve problems.</helpText>
            <helpText lang="de-DE">Mollie hat eine eigene LOG Datei im Shopware Log Verzeichnis. Dieser Modus kümmert sich um erweiterte Informationen in diesen Log Dateien, die zusätzlich bei der Analyse von Fehlern beitragen können.</helpText>
            <helpText lang="nl-NL">Mollie heeft een op maat logbestand in de Shopware logboek-map. Deze functie maakt uitgebreide logs mogelijk met meer informatie die helpen bij het oplossen van problemen.</helpText>
            <helpText lang="it-IT">Mollie dispone di un file di log personalizzato nella directory dei log di Shopware. Questa funzione abilita i log estesi con ulteriori informazioni che potrebbero aiutare a risolvere i problemi.</helpText>
            <helpText lang="pt-PT">A Mollie tem um ficheiro de log personalizado no diretório de log do Shopware. Esta funcionalidade permite a criação de logs alargados com mais informações que podem ajudar a resolver problemas.</helpText>
            <helpText lang="es-ES">Mollie tiene un archivo de registro personalizado en el directorio de registros de Shopware. Esta función habilita los registros ampliados con más información para ayudar a resolver problemas.</helpText>
            <helpText lang="sv-SE">Mollie har en anpassad loggfil i Shopware-loggmappen. Denna funktion aktiverar de utökade loggarna med mer information som kan hjälpa till att lösa problem.</helpText><helpText lang="nb-NO">Mollie har en egendefinert loggfil i Shopware loggmappen. Denne funksjonen aktiverer utvidede logger med mer informasjon som kan hjelpe med å løse problemer.</helpText><helpText lang="pl-PL">Mollie posiada niestandardowy plik logów w katalogu logów Shopware. Ta funkcja umożliwia istnienie rozszerzonych logów z większą ilością informacji, które mogą pomóc w rozwiązywaniu problemów.</helpText><helpText lang="cs-CZ">Mollie má vlastní soubor protokolu v adresáři protokolů Shopware. Tato funkce aktivuje rozšířené protokoly s více informacemi, které mohou pomoci při řešení problémů.</helpText><helpText lang="sl-SL">Mollie ima datoteko dnevnika po meri v imeniku dnevnikov Shopware. Ta funkcija omogoča obsežnejše dnevnike z več informacijami, ki bi lahko pomagale pri reševanju težav.</helpText><helpText lang="hu-HU">Mollie-nak van egy egyéni naplófájlja a Shopware naplók könyvtárában. Ez a funkció lehetővé teszi a kibővített naplókat, amelyek további információkat tartalmaznak a problémák megoldásához.</helpText><helpText lang="fi-FI">Molliella on mukautettu lokitiedosto Shopwaren lokihakemistossa. Tämä ominaisuus mahdollistaa laajennetut lokit, joissa on lisätietoja, jotka voivat auttaa ratkaisemaan ongelmia.</helpText><helpText lang="da-DK">Mollie har en tilpasset logfil i Shopware loggmappen. Denne funktion aktiverer udvidede logs med mere information, der kan hjælpe med at løse problemer.</helpText><helpText lang="sk-SK">Mollie má vlastný súbor protokolu v adresári logov Shopware. Táto funkcia umožňuje rozšírené protokolovanie s podrobnejšími informáciami, ktoré môžu pomôcť pri riešení problémov.</helpText>
        </input-field>
        <input-field type="int">
            <name>logFileDays</name>
            <label>Keep log files (days)</label>
            <label lang="de-DE">Log-Dateien aufbewahren (Tage)</label>
            <label lang="nl-NL">Logbestanden bijhouden (dagen)</label>
            <label lang="it-IT">Conserva i file di log (giorni)</label>
            <label lang="pt-PT">Manter arquivos de log (dias)</label>
            <label lang="es-ES">Mantener archivos de registro (días)</label>
            <label lang="sv-SE">Behåll loggfiler (dagar)</label><label lang="nb-NO">Behold loggerfiler (dager)</label><label lang="pl-PL">Zachowuj pliki dziennika (dni)</label><label lang="cs-CZ">Udržovat soubory protokolu (dny)</label><label lang="sl-SL">Obdržite datoteke dnevnika (dni)</label><label lang="hu-HU">Naplófájlok megtartása (napok)</label><label lang="fi-FI">Pidä lokitiedostoja (päivinä)</label><label lang="da-DK">Behold logfiler (dage)</label><label lang="sk-SK">Uchovávať súbory protokolu (dni)</label>
            <defaultValue>14</defaultValue>
            <helpText>Set the number of days how long log files are kept until they will be automatically deleted.</helpText>
            <helpText lang="de-DE">Legen Sie die Anzahl der Tage fest, wie lange Protokolldateien aufbewahrt werden, bis sie automatisch gelöscht werden.</helpText>
            <helpText lang="nl-NL">Stel het aantal dagen in hoe lang logbestanden worden bewaard totdat ze automatisch worden verwijderd.</helpText>
            <helpText lang="it-IT">Imposta il numero di giorni per quanto tempo i file di log devono essere conservati prima di essere automaticamente eliminati.</helpText>
            <helpText lang="pt-PT">Defina por quantos dias os arquivos de log são mantidos até serem automaticamente eliminados.</helpText>
            <helpText lang="es-ES">Establece el número de días que se conservarán los archivos de registro hasta eliminarse automáticamente.</helpText>
            <helpText lang="sv-SE">Ange antalet dagar hur länge loggfiler behålls innan de automatiskt tas bort.</helpText><helpText lang="nb-NO">Angi hvor mange dager loggfiler holdes før de blir automatisk slettet.</helpText><helpText lang="pl-PL">Ustaw liczbę dni, przez które pliki dziennika będą przechowywane, zanim zostaną automatycznie usunięte.</helpText><helpText lang="cs-CZ">Nastavte počet dnů, po které budou protokolové soubory uchovávány, než budou automaticky smazány.</helpText><helpText lang="sl-SL">Nastavite število dni, koliko časa naj se ohranjajo datoteke dnevnika, dokler ne bodo samodejno izbrisane.</helpText><helpText lang="hu-HU">Állítsa be a napok számát, hogy meddig tartják meg a (log) naplófájlokat, amíg automatikusan törlésre kerülnek.</helpText><helpText lang="fi-FI">Määritä päivien lukumäärä, kuinka kauan lokitiedostoja säilytetään, ennen kuin ne poistetaan automaattisesti.</helpText><helpText lang="da-DK">Indstil antallet af dage, hvor logfiler opbevares, indtil de automatisk slettes.</helpText><helpText lang="sk-SK">Nastavte počet dní, počas ktorých sa budú súbory protokolu uchovávať, kým nebudú automaticky odstránené.</helpText>
        </input-field>
    </card>
    <card>
        <title>Payments</title>
        <title lang="de-DE">Zahlungen</title>
        <title lang="nl-NL">Betalingen</title>
        <title lang="it-IT">Pagamenti</title>
        <title lang="pt-PT">Pagamentos</title>
        <title lang="es-ES">Pagos</title>
        <title lang="sv-SE">Betalningar</title><title lang="nb-NO">Betalinger</title><title lang="pl-PL">Płatności</title><title lang="cs-CZ">Platby</title><title lang="sl-SL">Plačila</title><title lang="hu-HU">Fizetések</title><title lang="fi-FI">Maksut</title><title lang="da-DK">Betalinger</title><title lang="sk-SK">Platby</title>
        <input-field type="bool">
            <name>shopwareFailedPayment</name>
            <label>Use Shopware standard behaviour for failed payments</label>
            <label lang="de-DE">Shopware Standardverhalten für fehlerhafte Zahlungen verwenden</label>
            <label lang="nl-NL">Gebruik de standaard Shopware instelling voor mislukte betalingen</label>
            <label lang="it-IT">Utilizza il comportamento standard di Shopware per i pagamenti non riusciti</label>
            <label lang="pt-PT">Utilizar o comportamento padrão do Shopware para pagamentos falhados</label>
            <label lang="es-ES">Proceso predeterminado de Shopware para pagos fallidos</label>
            <label lang="sv-SE">Använd Shopwares standardbeteende för misslyckade betalningar</label><label lang="nb-NO">Bruk Shopware standard oppførsel for mislykkede betalinger</label><label lang="pl-PL">Użyj domyślnego działania Shopware dla nieudanych płatności</label><label lang="cs-CZ">Použijte standardní chování Shopware pro neúspěšné platby</label><label lang="sl-SL">Uporabite standardni proces Shopware za neuspešna plačila</label><label lang="hu-HU">Használja a Shopware standard viselkedését a sikertelen tranzakcióknál</label><label lang="fi-FI">Käytä Shopwaren oletustoimintaa epäonnistuneissa maksuissa</label><label lang="da-DK">Brug Shopware standard adfærd for mislykkedes betalinger</label><label lang="sk-SK">Použiť štandardné správanie Shopware pre neúspešné platby</label>
            <defaultValue>true</defaultValue>
            <helpText>Use the default Shopware behaviour on failed payments. If disabled, Mollie will automatically provide a way to retry the payment by redirecting the user to the Mollie payments page.</helpText>
            <helpText lang="de-DE">Aktiviert das Standardverhalten von Shopware für fehlerhafte Zahlungen. Wenn nicht aktiv, kümmert sich das Mollie Plugin um einen erneuten Versuch der Zahlung und leitet den Käufer auf die externe Mollie Zahlungsauswahl.</helpText>
            <helpText lang="nl-NL">Gebruik de standaard Shopware instelling voor mislukte betalingen. Indien uitgeschakeld, zal Mollie automatisch een manier aanbieden om de betaling opnieuw te proberen door de user om te leiden naar de Mollie betalingspagina.</helpText>
            <helpText lang="it-IT">Usa il comportamento predefinito di Shopware per i pagamenti non riusciti. Se disabilitato, Mollie fornirà automaticamente un modo per riprovare il pagamento reindirizzando l'utente alla pagina dei pagamenti di Mollie.</helpText>
            <helpText lang="pt-PT">Utilizar o comportamento padrão do Shopware em pagamentos falhados. Se este estiver desativado, a Mollie fornecerá automaticamente uma maneira de tentar novamente o pagamento redirecionando o utilizador para a página de pagamentos da Mollie.</helpText>
            <helpText lang="es-ES">Procedimiento predeterminado de Shopware para pagos fallidos. Si está desactivado, Mollie reintentará el pago de forma automática redirigiendo al usuario a la página de pagos de Mollie.</helpText>
            <helpText lang="sv-SE">Använd Shopwares standardbeteende för misslyckade betalningar. Om inaktiverad, kommer Mollie automatiskt att tillhandahålla ett sätt att försöka igen genom att omdirigera användaren till Mollies betalningssida.</helpText><helpText lang="nb-NO">Bruk Shopware standard oppførsel på mislykkede betalinger. Hvis deaktivert, vil Mollie automatisk gi brukeren mulighet for å prøve å betale på nytt ved å omdirigere dem til Mollie betalingsside.</helpText><helpText lang="pl-PL">Użyj domyślnego działania Shopware w przypadku nieudanych płatności. Jeśli ta opcja jest wyłączona, Mollie automatycznie udostępni możliwość ponowienia płatności, przekierowując użytkownika na stronę płatności Mollie.</helpText><helpText lang="cs-CZ">Pro neúspěšné transakce použijte výchozí nastavení Shopware. Pokud tuto možnost deaktivujete, Mollie automaticky nabídne způsob pokusu o vrácení peněz a přesměruje uživatele na platební stránku Mollie.</helpText><helpText lang="sl-SL">Uporabite privzet proces Shopware za neuspešna plačila. Če je onemogočeno, bo Mollie samodejno zagotavljal način za ponovni poskus plačila, tako da preusmeri uporabnika na plačilno stran Mollie.</helpText><helpText lang="hu-HU">Használja a Shopware alapértelmezett beállítást a sikertelen tranzakcióknál. Ha letiltja ezt az opciót, Mollie automatikusan biztosít egy módot a visszafizetés megkísérlésére, és felhasználót átirányítva a Mollie fizetési oldalára.</helpText><helpText lang="fi-FI">Käytä oletusarvoista Shopware-toimintaa epäonnistuneissa maksuissa. Jos se on poistettu käytöstä, Mollie tarjoaa automaattisesti tavan yrittää maksua uudelleen ohjaamalla käyttäjän Mollien maksut -sivustolle.</helpText><helpText lang="da-DK">Brug den standard Shopware adfærd ved mislykkede betalinger. Hvis deaktiveret, vil Mollie automatisk give en måde at forsøge at gennemføre betalingen ved at omdirigere brugeren til Mollie betalingsside.</helpText><helpText lang="sk-SK">Použiť predvolené správanie Shopware pri neúspešných platbách. Ak je táto možnosť vypnutá, Mollie automaticky poskytne možnosť zopakovať platbu presmerovaním používateľa na platobnú stránku Mollie.</helpText>
        </input-field>
        <input-field type="bool">
            <name>createCustomersAtMollie</name>
            <label>Create customers at Mollie</label>
            <label lang="de-DE">Kunden bei Mollie anlegen</label>
            <label lang="nl-NL">Klanten creëren bij Mollie</label>
            <label lang="it-IT">Crea clienti presso Mollie</label>
            <label lang="pt-PT">Criar clientes na Mollie</label>
            <label lang="es-ES">Crear clientes en Mollie</label>
            <label lang="sv-SE">Skapa kunder hos Mollie</label><label lang="nb-NO">Opprett kunder hos Mollie</label><label lang="pl-PL">Twórz klientów w Mollie</label><label lang="cs-CZ">Vytvořit zákazníky v Mollie</label><label lang="sl-SL">Ustvari stranke v Mollie</label><label lang="hu-HU">Ügyfelek létrehozása Mollie-nál</label><label lang="fi-FI">Luo asiakkaita Molliessa</label><label lang="da-DK">Opret kunder hos Mollie</label><label lang="sk-SK">Vytvorte zákazníkov v Mollie</label>
            <defaultValue>false</defaultValue>
            <helpText>Automatically have customers being created inside your Mollie Dashboard to see all payments of a specific customer.</helpText>
            <helpText lang="de-DE">Erstellt automatisch Kunden im Mollie Dashboard. Dadurch hat man einen zusätzlichen Überblick über alle Zahlungen dieses Kunden innerhalb von Mollie.</helpText>
            <helpText lang="nl-NL">Automatisch klanten laten aanmaken in het Mollie Dashboard om alle betalingen van een specifieke klant te zien.</helpText>
            <helpText lang="it-IT">Crea automaticamente i clienti all'interno della tua Mollie Dashboard per vedere tutti i pagamenti di un cliente specifico.</helpText>
            <helpText lang="pt-PT">Crie automaticamente clientes no seu painel de controlo da Mollie para ver todos os pagamentos de um cliente específico.</helpText>
            <helpText lang="es-ES">Crear clientes automáticamente desde el Mollie Dashboard para ver todos los pagos de un cliente determinado.</helpText>
            <helpText lang="sv-SE">Automatiskt skapa kunder i din Mollie Dashboard för att se alla betalningar av en specifik kund.ld upbest</helpText><helpText lang="nb-NO">Opprett kunder automatisk i ditt Mollie Dashboard for å se alle betalinger fra en spesifikk kunde.</helpText><helpText lang="pl-PL">Ustaw automatyczne tworzenie klientów w Panelu kontrolnym Mollie, aby mieć dostęp do wszystkich płatności konkretnego klienta.</helpText><helpText lang="cs-CZ">Automaticky vytvářejte zákazníky ve svém Mollie Dashboard, abyste viděli všechny platby konkrétního zákazníka.</helpText><helpText lang="sl-SL">Samodejno ustvarite stranke v Mollie Dashboard, da vidite vsa plačila določene stranke.</helpText><helpText lang="hu-HU">Automatikusan hozzon létre ügyfeleket a Mollie irányítópultjáról, hogy megtekinthesse az adott ügyfél összes fizetését.</helpText><helpText lang="fi-FI">Luo automaattisesti asiakkaita Mollie-hallintapaneeliin, jotta näet kaikki tietyn asiakkaan maksut.</helpText><helpText lang="da-DK">Automatisk oprettelse af kunder i din Mollie Dashboard for at se alle betalinger fra en specifik kunde.</helpText><helpText lang="sk-SK">Automaticky vytvárajte zákazníkov vo svojom Mollie Dashboarde, aby ste videli všetky platby konkrétneho zákazníka.</helpText>
        </input-field>
        <input-field type="bool">
            <name>useMolliePaymentMethodLimits</name>
            <defaultValue>false</defaultValue>
            <label>Use Mollie's availability rules for payment methods</label>
            <label lang="de-DE">Mollies Verfügbarkeitsregeln für Zahlungsarten verwenden</label>
            <label lang="nl-NL">Gebruik de beschikbaarheidsregels van Mollie voor betaalmethoden</label>
            <label lang="it-IT">Usa le regole di disponibilità di Mollie per i metodi di pagamento</label>
            <label lang="pt-PT">Utilize as regras de disponibilidade da Mollie para métodos de pagamento</label>
            <label lang="es-ES">Usar reglas de disponibilidad de Mollie para métodos de pago</label>
            <label lang="sv-SE">Använd Mollies tillgänglighetsregler för betalningsmetoder</label><label lang="nb-NO">Bruk Mollies tilgjengelighetsregler for betalingsmetoder</label><label lang="pl-PL">Użyj zasad dostępności Mollie dla metod płatności</label><label lang="cs-CZ">Použít pravidla přístupnosti Mollie pro platební metody</label><label lang="sl-SL">Uporabite pravila razpoložljivosti Mollie za načine plačila</label><label lang="hu-HU">Használja a Mollie elérhetőségi szabályait a fizetési módokhoz</label><label lang="fi-FI">Käytä maksutavoissa Mollien saatavuussääntöjä</label><label lang="da-DK">Brug Mollies tilgængelighedsregler for betalingsmetoder</label><label lang="sk-SK">Použite pravidlá dostupnosti Mollie pre spôsoby platby</label>
            <helpText>Automatically hides payment methods in the checkout based on the availability rules for payment methods. Only active payment methods from your mollie dashboard will be shown. If the payment method has a cart limit, currency restriction or billing address restriction, it will be hidden during checkout.</helpText>
            <helpText lang="de-DE">Blendet automatisch Zahlungsart im Checkout basierend auf Verfügbarkeitsregeln von Mollie. Es werden nur die aktiven Zahlungsarten aus dem Mollie Dashboard angezeigt. Wenn die Zahlungsart eine Einschränkung auf den Warenkorbwert, Währung oder Rechnungsadresse hat, wird diese auch ausgeblendet.</helpText>
            <helpText lang="nl-NL">Automatische betalingsmethode wordt verborgen tijdens het afrekenen op basis van beschikbaarheidsregels van Mollie. Alleen actieve betalingsmethoden uit het Mollie-dashboard worden weergegeven. Als de betalingsmethode beperkingen heeft op de winkelwagenwaarde, valuta of factuuradres, wordt deze ook verborgen.</helpText>
            <helpText lang="it-IT">Nasconde automaticamente i metodi di pagamento nel checkout in base alle regole di disponibilità per i metodi di pagamento. Verranno mostrati solo i metodi di pagamento attivi dalla tua Mollie Dashboard. Se il metodo di pagamento ha un limite di carrello, una restrizione di valuta o una restrizione all'indirizzo di fatturazione, verrà nascosto durante il checkout.</helpText>
            <helpText lang="pt-PT">Oculta automaticamente os métodos de pagamento na finalização da compra com base nas regras de disponibilidade dos métodos de pagamento. Apenas serão mostrados os métodos de pagamento ativos do seu painel de controlo da Mollie. Se o método de pagamento tiver um limite de carrinho, restrição de moeda ou restrição de endereço de faturação, será ocultado durante a finalização da compra.</helpText>
            <helpText lang="es-ES">Oculta automáticamente los métodos de pago en el proceso de compra según las reglas de disponibilidad para métodos de pago. Solo se mostrarán los métodos de pago activos en tu Mollie Dashboard. Si el método de pago tiene un límite de carrito, restricción de moneda o restricción de dirección de facturación, se ocultará durante el proceso de compra.</helpText>
            <helpText lang="sv-SE">Döljer automatiskt betalningsmetoder i kassan baserat på tillgänglighetsreglerna för betalningsmetoder. Endast aktiva betalningsmetoder från din Mollie Dashboard kommer att visas. Om betalningsmetoden har en varukorgsgräns, valutabegränsning eller begränsning av faktureringsadress, kommer den att döljas under kassan.</helpText><helpText lang="nb-NO">Skjuler automatisk betalingsmetoder i kassen basert på tilgjengelighetsregler for betalingsmetoder. Kun aktive betalingsmetoder fra ditt Mollie Dashboard vil bli vist. Hvis betalingsmetoden har en handlekurvgrense, valutabegrensning eller faktureringsadressebegrensning, vil den bli skjult under kassen.</helpText><helpText lang="pl-PL">Ta opcja automatycznie ukrywa metody płatności w koszyku na podstawie zasad dostępności metod płatności. Tylko aktywne metody płatności z Twojego panelu Mollie będą wyświetlane. Jeśli metoda płatności ma limit koszyka, ograniczenia waluty lub adresu rozliczeniowego, zostanie ukryta podczas realizacji zamówienia.</helpText><helpText lang="cs-CZ">Automaticky skrývá platební metody v košíku na základě pravidel dostupnosti platebních metod. Zobrazí se pouze aktivní platební metody z vašeho Mollie Dashboard. Pokud má platební metoda omezení na hodnotu košíku, měnu nebo fakturační adresu, bude ve fázi pokladny skryta.</helpText><helpText lang="sl-SL">Samodejno skrije načine plačila na blagajni na podlagi pravil o razpoložljivosti načinov plačila. Prikazani bodo samo aktivni načini plačila iz vaše nadzorne plošče Mollie. Če ima način plačila omejitev košarice, omejitev valute ali omejitev naslova za obračun, bo med blagajno skrit.</helpText><helpText lang="hu-HU">A fizetési módok automatikus elrejtése a fizetési folyamatban a fizetési módok rendelkezésre állási szabályai alapján. Csak az aktív fizetési módok jelennek meg a Mollie Dashboardon. Ha a fizetési mód kosárkorláttal, devizakorlátozással vagy számlázási címre vonatkozó korlátozással rendelkezik, az el lesz rejtve a fizetési folyamat során.</helpText><helpText lang="fi-FI">Piilottaa maksutavat automaattisesti kassalla maksutapojen saatavuussääntöjen perusteella. Vain Mollie-hallintapaneelisi aktiiviset maksutavat näytetään. Jos maksutavalla on ostoskorirajoitus, valuuttarajoitus tai laskutusosoiterajoitus, se piilotetaan kassalla.</helpText><helpText lang="da-DK">Skjuler automatisk betalingsmetoder i kassen baseret på tilgængelighedsreglerne for betalingsmetoder. Kun aktive betalingsmetoder fra din Mollie Dashboard vil blive vist. Hvis betalingsmetoden har en handlekurvgrænse, valutabegrænsning eller begrænsning af faktureringsadresse, vil den blive skjult under kassen.</helpText><helpText lang="sk-SK">Platobné metódy sa v pokladni automaticky skryjú na základe pravidiel dostupnosti. Zobrazia sa iba aktívne platobné metódy z vášho Mollie Dashboardu. Ak má niektorá metóda obmedzenie podľa hodnoty košíka, meny alebo fakturačnej adresy, počas platby nebude zobrazená.</helpText>
        </input-field>
        <input-field type="text">
            <name>formatOrderNumber</name>
            <label>Custom format for Mollie order numbers (Dashboard, PayPal, ...)</label>
            <label lang="de-DE">Format für Mollie Bestellnummern (Dashboard, PayPal, ...)</label>
            <label lang="nl-NL">Aangepast formaat voor Mollie bestelnummers (Dashboard, PayPal, ...)</label>
            <label lang="it-IT">Formato personalizzato per i numeri d'ordine di Mollie (Dashboard, PayPal, ...)</label><label lang="pt-PT">Formato personalizado para os números de encomenda Mollie (Dashboard, PayPal, ...)</label><label lang="es-ES">Formato personalizado para números de pedido de Mollie (Dashboard, PayPal, ...)</label><label lang="sv-SE">Anpassat format för Mollie beställningsnummer (Dashboard, PayPal, ...)</label><label lang="nb-NO">Egendefinert format for Mollie ordrenumre (Dashboard, PayPal, ...)</label><label lang="pl-PL">Niestandardowy format numerów zamówień Mollie (Panel, PayPal, ...)</label><label lang="cs-CZ">Vlastní formát pro čísla objednávek Mollie (Přehled, PayPal, ...)</label><label lang="sl-SL">Prilagojena oblika za številke naročil Mollie (Dashboard, PayPal, ...)</label><label lang="hu-HU">Egyedi formátum a Mollie megrendelési számokhoz (Irányítópult, PayPal, ...)</label><label lang="fi-FI">Räätälöity muoto Mollie-tilausnumeroille (Dashboard, PayPal, ...)</label><label lang="da-DK">Brugerdefineret format for Mollie ordrenumre (Dashboard, PayPal, ...)</label><label lang="sk-SK">Vlastný formát čísiel objednávok pre Mollie (Dashboard, PayPal, ...)</label>
            <helpText>If set, this format will be used before the order number in the Mollie dashboard. This will also be passed on to PayPal as invoice number.</helpText>
            <helpText lang="de-DE">Wenn gesetzt, wird dieses Format vor der Bestellnummer im Mollie-Dashboard verwendet. Dieser Wert wird auch an PayPal als Rechnungsnummber übergeben</helpText>
            <helpText lang="nl-NL">Indien ingesteld, wordt dit formaat vóór het bestelnummer in het Mollie-dashboard gebruikt. Dit wordt ook als factuurnummer doorgegeven aan PayPal.</helpText>
            <helpText lang="it-IT">Se impostato, questo formato verrà utilizzato prima del numero d'ordine nella Mollie Dashboard. Verrà inoltre passato a PayPal come numero di fattura.</helpText><helpText lang="pt-PT">Se definido, este formato será utilizado antes do número de encomenda no painel de controlo da Mollie. Este formato também será transmitido ao PayPal como número de fatura.</helpText><helpText lang="es-ES">Si se establece, este formato se usará antes del número de pedido en el Mollie Dashboard. Pasará también a PayPal como número de factura.</helpText><helpText lang="sv-SE">Om inställt, kommer detta format att användas före ordernumret i Mollies dashboard. Detta kommer också att skickas till PayPal som fakturanummer.</helpText><helpText lang="nb-NO">Hvis angitt, vil dette formatet bli brukt før ordrenummeret i Mollie Dashbord. Dette vil også bli videreført til PayPal som fakturanummer.</helpText><helpText lang="pl-PL">Jeśli ta opcja jest ustawiona, ten format będzie używany przed numerem zamówienia w panelu Mollie. Zostanie on również przekazany do PayPal jako numer faktury.</helpText><helpText lang="cs-CZ">Pokud je toto nastaveno, tento formát bude použit před číslem objednávky v Mollie Dashboard. Bude také předán PayPalu jako číslo faktury.</helpText><helpText lang="sl-SL">Če je to nastavljeno, bo ta oblika uporabljena pred številko naročila v Mollie Dashboard. To se bo preneslo tudi na PayPal kot številka računa.</helpText><helpText lang="hu-HU">Ha be van állítva, ez a formátum a rendelésszám előtt kerül felhasználásra a Mollie Dashboardon. A PayPal-nak is átkerül a számlaszámként.</helpText><helpText lang="fi-FI">Jos tämä on asetettu, tätä muotoa käytetään ennen tilausnumeroa Mollie-hallintapaneelissa. Tämä välitetään myös PayPalille laskun numerona.</helpText><helpText lang="da-DK">Hvis indstillet, vil dette format blive brugt før ordrenummeret i Mollie dashboardet. Dette vil også blive sendt til PayPal som fakturanummer.</helpText><helpText lang="sk-SK">Ak je nastavený, tento formát sa použije pred číslom objednávky v Mollie Dashboarde. Rovnako sa odošle aj do služby PayPal ako číslo faktúry.</helpText>
        </input-field>
        <component name="mollie-pluginconfig-section-payments-format">
            <name>molliePluginConfigSectionPaymentsFormat</name>
        </component>
        <component name="mollie-pluginconfig-section-payments">
            <name>molliePluginConfigSectionPayments</name>
        </component>
    </card>
    <card>
        <title>Credit card</title>
        <title lang="de-DE">Kreditkarte</title>
        <title lang="nl-NL">Credit card</title>
        <title lang="it-IT">Carta di Credito</title>
        <title lang="pt-PT">Cartão de Crédito</title>
        <title lang="es-ES">Tarjeta de crédito</title>
        <title lang="sv-SE">Kreditkort</title>
        <title lang="nb-NO">Kredittkort</title>
        <title lang="pl-PL">Karta kredytowa</title><title lang="cs-CZ">Kreditní karta</title><title lang="sl-SL">Kreditna kartica</title><title lang="hu-HU">Hitelkártya</title><title lang="fi-FI">Luottokortti</title><title lang="da-DK">Kreditkort</title><title lang="sk-SK">Kreditná karta</title>
        <input-field type="bool">
            <name>enableCreditCardComponents</name>
            <label>Enable Credit Card Components</label>
            <label lang="de-DE">Kreditkarten Komponenten aktivieren</label>
            <label lang="nl-NL">Credit Card componenten activeren</label>
            <label lang="it-IT">Abilita Componenti Carta di Credito</label><label lang="pt-PT">Ativar Componentes de Cartão de Crédito</label><label lang="es-ES">Habilitar módulo de tarjeta de crédito</label><label lang="sv-SE">Aktivera kreditkortskomponenter</label><label lang="nb-NO">Aktiver Kredittkortkomponenter</label><label lang="pl-PL">Włącz Karty Kredytowe</label><label lang="cs-CZ">Povolit komponenty kreditních karet</label><label lang="sl-SL">Omogoči komponente kreditnih kartic</label><label lang="hu-HU">Kártya összetevők engedélyezése</label><label lang="fi-FI">Ota luottokorttikomponentit käyttöön</label><label lang="da-DK">Aktiver kreditkortkomponenter</label><label lang="sk-SK">Povoliť komponenty kreditných kariet</label>
            <defaultValue>true</defaultValue>
            <helpText>Show credit card input fields directly within your Shopware shop. If disabled, Mollie will show
                the forms on the Mollie payment page.
            </helpText>
            <helpText lang="de-DE">Zeigt Kreditkartenfelder direkt im Shopware shop an. Wenn nicht aktiviert, dann zeigt
                Mollie diese Felder direkt auf der externen Mollie Zahlungsseite.
            </helpText>
            <helpText lang="nl-NL">Toon credit card invoervelden direct in jouw Shopware shop. Indien uitgeschakeld, zal
                Mollie de formulieren tonen op de Mollie betaalpagina.
            </helpText>
            <helpText lang="it-IT">Mostra i campi di inserimento della carta di credito direttamente nel tuo negozio
                Shopware. Se disabilitato, Mollie mostrerà i moduli nella pagina di pagamento di Mollie.
            </helpText><helpText lang="pt-PT">Mostrar os campos de introdução de cartões de crédito diretamente na sua loja Shopware. Se estiver desativado, o Mollie mostrará os formulários na página de pagamento da Mollie.</helpText><helpText lang="es-ES">Mostrar los campos de tarjeta de crédito directamente en tu tienda de Shopware. Si se desactiva, Mollie mostrará el formulario en la página de pagos de Mollie.</helpText><helpText lang="sv-SE">Visa kreditkortsinmatningsfält direkt inom din Shopware-butik. Om inaktiverad kommer Mollie att visa formulären på Mollies betalningssida.</helpText><helpText lang="nb-NO">Vis kredittkortinformasjon direkte i din Shopware butikk. Hvis deaktivert, vil Mollie vise skjemaene på Mollie betalingsside.</helpText><helpText lang="pl-PL">Pokaż pola wprowadzania danych karty kredytowej bezpośrednio w Twoim sklepie Shopware. Jeśli ta opcja jest wyłączona, Mollie wyświetli formularze na stronie płatności Mollie.</helpText><helpText lang="cs-CZ">Zobrazit pole pro zadání kreditní karty přímo ve vašem Shopware obchodě. Pokud je tato možnost zakázána, Mollie zobrazí formuláře na platební stránce Mollie.</helpText><helpText lang="sl-SL">Prikaži polja za kreditne kartic neposredno v vaši trgovini Shopware. Če je onemogočeno, bo Mollie prikazal obrazce na plačilni strani Mollie.</helpText><helpText lang="hu-HU">Jelenítse meg a hitelkártya-beviteli mezőket közvetlenül a Shopware üzletében. Ha le van tiltva, Mollie megjeleníti az űrlapokat Mollie fizetési oldalán.</helpText><helpText lang="fi-FI">Näytä luottokortin syöttökentät suoraan Shopware-kaupassasi. Jos poistettu käytöstä, Mollie näyttää lomakkeet Mollien maksusivulla.</helpText><helpText lang="da-DK">Vis kreditkortindtastningsfelter direkte i din Shopware butik. Hvis deaktiveret, vil Mollie vise formularerne på Mollies betalingsside.</helpText><helpText lang="sk-SK">Zobraziť polia na zadanie údajov o kreditnej karte priamo vo vašom obchode Shopware. Ak je táto možnosť vypnutá, formuláre zobrazí Mollie na svojej platobnej stránke.</helpText>
        </input-field>
        <input-field type="bool">
            <name>oneClickPaymentsEnabled</name>
            <label>Enable One-Click Payments</label>
            <label lang="de-DE">One-Click-Zahlungen aktivieren</label>
            <label lang="nl-NL">One-Click betalingen activeren</label>
            <label lang="it-IT">Abilita i pagamenti con un solo clic</label><label lang="pt-PT">Ativar Pagamentos em um Clique</label><label lang="es-ES">Habilitar pagos con un clic</label><label lang="sv-SE">Aktivera Enklicksbetalningar</label><label lang="nb-NO">Aktiver betalinger med ett klikk</label><label lang="pl-PL">Włącz płatności jednym kliknięciem</label><label lang="cs-CZ">Povolit platby jedním kliknutím</label><label lang="sl-SL">Omogoči plačila z enim klikom</label><label lang="hu-HU">Egyszerűsített kifizetések engedélyezése</label><label lang="fi-FI">Ota käyttöön yhden klikkauksen maksut</label><label lang="da-DK">Aktiver betalninger med et klik</label><label lang="sk-SK">Povoliť platby jedným kliknutím</label>
            <defaultValue>false</defaultValue>
            <helpText>Customers can choose to save their credit card data for repeating orders. Sensitive data will only
                be stored on the Mollie servers and not in Shopware.
            </helpText>
            <helpText lang="de-DE">Kunden haben die Möglichkeit, ihre Kreditkartendaten für erneute Bestellungen zu
                speichern. Sensible Daten werden nur auf den Mollie-Servern und nicht in Shopware gespeichert.
            </helpText>
            <helpText lang="nl-NL">Klanten kunnen ervoor kiezen hun creditcardgegevens op te slaan voor toekomstige
                bestellingen. Gevoelige gegevens worden alleen opgeslagen op de servers van Mollie en niet in Shopware.
            </helpText>
            <helpText lang="it-IT">I clienti possono scegliere di salvare i dati della propria carta di credito per ordini
                ripetuti. I dati sensibili saranno memorizzati solo sui server di Mollie e non in Shopware.
            </helpText><helpText lang="pt-PT">Os clientes podem optar por guardar os dados do seu cartão de crédito para encomendas repetidas. Os dados sensíveis serão armazenados apenas nos servidores da Mollie e não no Shopware.</helpText><helpText lang="es-ES">Los clientes pueden guardar los datos de su tarjeta para pedidos repetidos. La información sensible solo se almacenará en los servidores de Mollie y no en Shopware.</helpText><helpText lang="sv-SE">Kunder kan välja att spara sina kreditkortsuppgifter för återkommande beställningar. Känsliga uppgifter kommer endast att lagras på Mollies servrar och inte i Shopware.</helpText><helpText lang="nb-NO">Kunder kan velge å lagre kredittkortdataene sine for gjentakende bestillinger. Sensitive data vil kun bli lagret på Mollie-serverne og ikke i Shopware.</helpText><helpText lang="pl-PL">Klienci mogą zdecydować się na zapisanie danych karty kredytowej do przyszłych zamówień. Dane karty kredytowej będą przechowywane jedynie na serwerach Mollie, a nie w Shopware.</helpText><helpText lang="cs-CZ">Zákazníci si mohou zvolit, zda si uloží data své kreditní karty pro opakované objednávky. Citlivá data budou uchovávána pouze na serverech Mollie a ne v Shopware.</helpText><helpText lang="sl-SL">Stranke lahko izberejo, da shranijo podatke o kreditnih karticah za ponavljajoča plačila. Občutljivi podatki bodo shranjeni samo na strežnikih Mollie in ne v Shopware.</helpText><helpText lang="hu-HU">Az ügyfelek elmenthetik kártyaadataikat az ismételt megrendelésekhez. A bizalmas információkat csak a Mollie szerverein tároljuk, a Shopware-en nem.</helpText><helpText lang="fi-FI">Asiakkaat voivat valita, haluavatko he tallentaa luottokorttitietonsa uusia tilauksia varten. Arkaluontoisia tietoja säilytetään vain Mollie-palvelimilla, ei Shopwareissa.</helpText><helpText lang="da-DK">Kunder kan vælge at gemme deres kreditkortdata til gentagne ordrer. Følsomme data vil kun blive gemt på Mollies servere og ikke i Shopware.</helpText><helpText lang="sk-SK">Zákazníci si môžu zvoliť uloženie údajov o kreditnej karte pre opakujúce sa objednávky. Citlivé údaje sa budú uchovávať iba na serveroch Mollie a nie v Shopware.</helpText>
        </input-field>
        <input-field type="bool">
            <name>oneClickPaymentsCompactView</name>
            <label>Enable One-Click Payments compact view</label>
            <label lang="de-DE">One-Click-Zahlungen Kompaktansicht aktivieren</label>
            <label lang="nl-NL">Compacte weergave van One-Click Payments</label>
            <label lang="it-IT">Abilita la visualizzazione compatta dei pagamenti con un solo clic</label><label lang="pt-PT">Ativar a vista compacta dos pagamentos com um clique</label><label lang="es-ES">Habilitar vista comprimida de pagos con un clic</label><label lang="sv-SE">Aktivera kompaktvy för Enklicksbetalningar</label><label lang="nb-NO">Aktiver kompakt visning for betalinger med ett klikk</label><label lang="pl-PL">Włącz kompaktowy widok dla płatności jednym kliknięciem</label><label lang="cs-CZ">Povolit kompaktní zobrazení plateb jedním kliknutím</label><label lang="sl-SL">Omogoči kompakten pregled plačil z enim klikom</label><label lang="hu-HU">Engedélyezze az egykattintásos fizetések tömörített nézetét</label><label lang="fi-FI">Ota käyttöön yhden klikkauksen maksujen kompakti näkymä</label><label lang="da-DK">Aktiver kompakt visning for betalinger med et klik</label><label lang="sk-SK">Povoliť kompaktný náhľad platieb jedným kliknutím</label>
            <defaultValue>false</defaultValue>
            <helpText>If enabled, the stored credit cards will not be displayed as visual cards on the checkout page.
            </helpText>
            <helpText lang="de-DE">Wenn aktiviert, werden die gespeicherten Kreditkarten nicht als visuelle Karten auf
                der Checkout-Seite angezeigt.
            </helpText>
            <helpText lang="nl-NL">Indien ingeschakeld, worden de opgeslagen creditcards niet weergegeven als visuele
                kaarten op de afrekenpagina.
            </helpText>
            <helpText lang="it-IT">Se abilitato, le carte di credito memorizzate non saranno mostrate come carte visive
                nella pagina di checkout.
            </helpText><helpText lang="pt-PT">Se ativado, os cartões de crédito guardados não serão apresentados como cartões visuais na página de finalização da compra.</helpText><helpText lang="es-ES">Si se habilita, las tarjetas de crédito almacenadas no se mostrarán de forma gráfica en la página de pago.</helpText><helpText lang="sv-SE">Om aktiverad kommer de lagrade kreditkorten inte att visas som visuella kort på kassasidan.</helpText><helpText lang="nb-NO">Hvis aktivert, vil de lagrede kredittkortene ikke bli vist som visuelle kort på kassesiden.</helpText><helpText lang="pl-PL">Jeśli ta opcja jest włączona, zapisane karty kredytowe nie będą wyświetlane jako wizualne karty na stronie finalizacji zamówienia.</helpText><helpText lang="cs-CZ">Pokud je tato možnost povolena, uložené kreditní karty nebudou zobrazeny jako vizuální karty na stránce pokladny.</helpText><helpText lang="sl-SL">Če je omogočeno, shranjene kreditne kartice ne bodo prikazane kot vizualne kartice na strani blagajne.</helpText><helpText lang="hu-HU">Ha engedélyezve van, a tárolt hitelkártyák nem jelennek meg grafikusan a fizetési oldalon.</helpText><helpText lang="fi-FI">Jos otettu käyttöön, tallennettuja luottokortteja ei näytetä visuaalisina korteina maksusivulla.</helpText><helpText lang="da-DK">Hvis aktiveret, vises de gemte kreditkort ikke som visuelle kort på kassesiden.</helpText><helpText lang="sk-SK">Ak je táto možnosť povolená, uložené kreditné karty sa nebudú na stránke pokladne zobrazovať ako vizuálne karty.</helpText>
        </input-field>
    </card>
    <!--card>
        <title>PayPal Express</title>
        <title lang="de-DE">PayPal Express</title>
        <title lang="nl-NL">PayPal Express</title>
        <title lang="it-IT">PayPal Express</title>
        <input-field type="single-select">
            <name>paypalExpressButtonStyle</name>
            <label>PayPal Express Button Style</label>
            <defaultValue>1</defaultValue>
            <options>
                <option>
                    <id>1</id>
                    <name>Gold</name>
                    <name lang="de-DE">Gold</name>
                    <name lang="nl-NL">Goud</name>
                    <name lang="it-IT">Oro</name>
                </option>
                <option>
                    <id>2</id>
                    <name>Blue</name>
                    <name lang="de-DE">Blau</name>
                    <name lang="nl-NL">Blauw</name>
                    <name lang="it-IT">Blu</name>
                </option>
                <option>
                    <id>3</id>
                    <name>Silver</name>
                    <name lang="de-DE">Silber</name>
                    <name lang="nl-NL">Zilver</name>
                    <name lang="it-IT">Argento</name>
                </option>
                <option>
                    <id>4</id>
                    <name>White</name>
                    <name lang="de-DE">Weiß</name>
                    <name lang="nl-NL">Wit</name>
                    <name lang="it-IT">Bianco</name>
                </option>
                <option>
                    <id>5</id>
                    <name>Black</name>
                    <name lang="de-DE">Schwarz</name>
                    <name lang="nl-NL">Zwart</name>
                    <name lang="it-IT">Nero</name>
                </option>
            </options>
        </input-field>
        <input-field type="single-select">
            <name>paypalExpressButtonShape</name>
            <label>PayPal Express Button Shape</label>
            <defaultValue>1</defaultValue>
            <options>
                <option>
                    <id>1</id>
                    <name>Rect</name>
                    <name lang="de-DE">Rect</name>
                    <name lang="nl-NL">Rect</name>
                    <name lang="it-IT">Rect</name>
                </option>
                <option>
                    <id>2</id>
                    <name>Pill</name>
                    <name lang="de-DE">Pill</name>
                    <name lang="nl-NL">Pill</name>
                    <name lang="it-IT">Pill</name>
                </option>
            </options>
        </input-field>
        <input-field type="multi-select">
            <name>paypalExpressRestrictions</name>
            <label>PayPal Express Display Restrictions</label>
            <label lang="de-DE">PayPal Express Anzeige Einschränkungen</label>
            <label lang="nl-NL">PayPal Express weergavebeperkingen</label>
            <label lang="it-IT">Restrizioni di visualizzazione di PayPal Express</label>
            <helpText>Restrict PayPal Express from being displayed on these pages.</helpText>
            <helpText lang="de-DE">Verhindere die Anzeige von PayPal Express auf den hier gewählten Seiten</helpText>
            <helpText lang="nl-NL">Voorkom dat PayPal Express wordt weergegeven op deze pagina's.</helpText>
            <helpText lang="it-IT">Limitare la visualizzazione di PayPal Express in queste pagine.</helpText>
            <options>
                <option>
                    <id>plp</id>
                    <name>Category pages</name>
                    <name lang="de-DE">Kategorieseiten</name>
                    <name lang="nl-NL">Categorie pagina's</name>
                    <name lang="it-IT">Pagine della categorie</name>
                </option>
                <option>
                    <id>pdp</id>
                    <name>Product pages</name>
                    <name lang="de-DE">Produktseiten</name>
                    <name lang="nl-NL">Product pagina's</name>
                    <name lang="it-IT">Pagine dei prodotti</name>
                </option>
                <option>
                    <id>offcanvas</id>
                    <name>Offcanvas cart</name>
                    <name lang="de-DE">Offcanvas Warenkorb</name>
                    <name lang="nl-NL">Offcanvas winkelmand</name>
                    <name lang="it-IT">Carrello offcanvas</name>
                </option>
                <option>
                    <id>cart</id>
                    <name>Cart page</name>
                    <name lang="de-DE">Warenkorbseite</name>
                    <name lang="nl-NL">Winkelmand</name>
                    <name lang="it-IT">Pagina del carrello</name>
                </option>
                <option>
                    <id>register</id>
                    <name>Registration page</name>
                    <name lang="de-DE">Registrierungsseite</name>
                    <name lang="nl-NL">Registratiepagina</name>
                    <name lang="it-IT">Pagina di registrazione</name>
                </option>
            </options>
        </input-field>
    </card -->
    <card>
        <title>Apple Pay</title>
        <title lang="de-DE">Apple Pay</title>
        <title lang="nl-NL">Apple Pay</title>
        <title lang="it-IT">Apple Pay</title><title lang="pt-PT">Apple Pay</title><title lang="es-ES">Apple Pay</title><title lang="sv-SE">Apple Pay</title><title lang="nb-NO">Apple Pay</title><title lang="pl-PL">Apple Pay</title><title lang="cs-CZ">Apple Pay</title><title lang="sl-SL">Apple Pay</title><title lang="hu-HU">Apple Pay</title><title lang="fi-FI">Apple Pay</title><title lang="da-DK">Apple Pay</title><title lang="sk-SK">Apple Pay</title>
        <input-field type="bool">
            <name>enableApplePayDirect</name>
            <label>Enable Apple Pay Direct</label>
            <label lang="de-DE">Apple Pay Direct aktivieren</label>
            <label lang="nl-NL">Apple Pay Direct activeren</label>
            <label lang="it-IT">Abilita Apple Pay Direct</label><label lang="pt-PT">Ativar o Apple Pay Direct</label><label lang="es-ES">Habilitar Apple Pay Directo</label><label lang="sv-SE">Aktivera Apple Pay Direkt</label><label lang="nb-NO">Aktiver Apple Pay Direct</label><label lang="pl-PL">Włącz Apple Pay Direct</label><label lang="cs-CZ">Povolit Apple Pay Direct</label><label lang="sl-SL">Omogoči Apple Pay Direct</label><label lang="hu-HU">Apple Pay közvetlen engedélyezése</label><label lang="fi-FI">Ota käyttöön Apple Pay Direct</label><label lang="da-DK">Aktiver Apple Pay Direct</label><label lang="sk-SK">Povoliť Apple Pay Direct</label>
            <defaultValue>false</defaultValue>
            <helpText>Show Apple Pay buttons and payment options directly on a product detail page or listing. This feature requires the payment method Apple Pay to be assigned to your Sales Channel.</helpText>
            <helpText lang="de-DE">Zeigt Apple Pay Buttons direkt auf der Produktseite oder Kategorie Seite an. Dieses Feature setzt voraus, dass die Zahlungsart 'Apple Pay' dem Verkaufskanal zugewiesen ist.</helpText>
            <helpText lang="nl-NL">Toon Apple Pay-buttons en betaalopties direct op een productdetailpagina of product listing pagina. Deze functie vereist dat de betaalmethode Apple Pay is toegewezen aan jouw verkoopkanaal.</helpText>
            <helpText lang="it-IT">Mostra i pulsanti e le opzioni di pagamento Apple Pay direttamente su una pagina di dettaglio del prodotto o nell'elenco dei prodotti. Questa funzione richiede che il metodo di pagamento Apple Pay sia assegnato al tuo Canale di Vendita.</helpText><helpText lang="pt-PT">Mostrar os botões Apple Pay e as opções de pagamento diretamente na página de detalhes ou na listagem de um produto. Esta funcionalidade requer que o método de pagamento Apple Pay seja atribuído ao seu Canal de vendas.</helpText><helpText lang="es-ES">Mostrar botones y opciones de pago de Apple Pay directamente en la descripción del artículo o el catálogo. Esta función requiere que el método de pago Apple Pay esté conectado en tu Canal de ventas.</helpText><helpText lang="sv-SE">Visa Apple Pay-knappar och betalningsalternativ direkt på en produktdetaljsida eller lista. Denna funktion kräver att betalningsmetoden Apple Pay tilldelas din försäljningskanal.</helpText><helpText lang="nb-NO">Vis Apple Pay-knapper og betalingsalternativer direkte på en produktdetaljside eller produktliste. Denne funksjonen krever at betalingsmetoden Apple Pay er tildelt i salgskanalen din.</helpText><helpText lang="pl-PL">Wyświetl przyciski Apple Pay oraz opcje płatności bezpośrednio na stronie szczegółów produktu lub w widoku listy. Ta funkcja wymaga przypisania metody płatności Apple Pay do Twojego Kanału Sprzedaży.</helpText><helpText lang="cs-CZ">Zobrazit tlačítka Apple Pay a možnosti platby přímo na stránce detailu produktu nebo v seznamu produktů. Tato funkce vyžaduje, aby byla platební metoda Apple Pay přiřazena k vašemu prodejnímu kanálu.</helpText><helpText lang="sl-SL">Prikažite gumbe in možnosti plačila Apple Pay neposredno na strani o podrobnostih izdelka ali v seznamu. Ta funkcija zahteva, da je način plačila Apple Pay dodeljen vašemu prodajnemu kanalu.</helpText><helpText lang="hu-HU">Mutassa meg az Apple Pay gombokat és fizetési lehetőségeket közvetlenül a termékleírásban vagy a katalógusban. A funkció használatához az Apple Pay fizetési módnak csatlakoznia kell az értékesítési csatornához.</helpText><helpText lang="fi-FI">Näytä Apple Pay -painikkeet ja maksutapavaihtoehdot suoraan tuotetietosivulla tai luettelossa. Tämä ominaisuus vaatii sen, että maksutapa Apple Pay on liitetty myyntikanavaasi.</helpText><helpText lang="da-DK">Vis Apple Pay knapper og betalingsmetoder direkte på en produktside eller i en liste. Denne funktion kræver, at betalingsmetoden Apple Pay er tildelt din salgskanal.</helpText><helpText lang="sk-SK">Zobraziť tlačidlá Apple Pay a platobné možnosti priamo na stránke s detailom produktu alebo v zozname produktov. Táto funkcia vyžaduje, aby bola platobná metóda Apple Pay priradená k vášmu predajnému kanálu.</helpText>
        </input-field>
        <input-field type="multi-select">
            <name>applePayDirectRestrictions</name>
            <label>Apple Pay Display Restrictions</label>
            <label lang="de-DE">Apple Pay Anzeige Einschränkungen</label>
            <label lang="nl-NL">Apple Pay weergavebeperkingen</label>
            <label lang="it-IT">Restrizioni di Visualizzazione di Apple Pay</label><label lang="pt-PT">Restrições de Exibição do Apple Pay</label><label lang="es-ES">Restricciones de visualización de Apple Pay</label><label lang="sv-SE">Apple Pay visningsbegränsningar</label><label lang="nb-NO">Apple Pay visningsbegrensninger</label><label lang="pl-PL">Ograniczenia wyświetlania Apple Pay</label><label lang="cs-CZ">Omezení zobrazení Apple Pay</label><label lang="sl-SL">Omejitve prikazovanja Apple Pay</label><label lang="hu-HU">Apple Pay kijelzési korlátozások</label><label lang="fi-FI">Apple Pay -näyttörajoitukset</label><label lang="da-DK">Apple Pay visningsbegrænsninger</label><label lang="sk-SK">Obmedzenia zobrazenia Apple Pay</label>
            <helpText>Restrict Apple Pay Direct from being displayed on these pages.</helpText>
            <helpText lang="de-DE">Verhindere die Anzeige von Apple Pay Direct auf den hier gewählten Seiten</helpText>
            <helpText lang="nl-NL">Voorkom dat Apple Pay Direct wordt weergegeven op deze pagina's.</helpText>
            <helpText lang="it-IT">Impedisci la visualizzazione di Apple Pay Direct su queste pagine.</helpText><helpText lang="pt-PT">Impedir que o Apple Pay Diret seja apresentado nestas páginas.</helpText><helpText lang="es-ES">Restringir la opción de Apple Pay Direct en estas páginas.</helpText><helpText lang="sv-SE">Begränsa Apple Pay Direkt från att visas på dessa sidor.</helpText><helpText lang="nb-NO">Begrens Apple Pay Direct fra å bli vist på disse sidene.</helpText><helpText lang="pl-PL">Ogranicz wyświetlanie Apple Pay Direct na tych stronach.</helpText><helpText lang="cs-CZ">Omezit zobrazení Apple Pay Direct na těchto stránkách.</helpText><helpText lang="sl-SL">Omejite, da se Apple Pay Direct ne prikaže na teh straneh.</helpText><helpText lang="hu-HU">Korlátozza az Apple Pay közvetlen megjelenítését ezeken az oldalakon.</helpText><helpText lang="fi-FI">Rajoita Apple Pay Directin näyttämistä näillä sivuilla.</helpText><helpText lang="da-DK">Begræns visningen af Apple Pay Direct på disse sider.</helpText><helpText lang="sk-SK">Obmedziť zobrazenie Apple Pay Direct na týchto stránkach.</helpText>
            <options>
                <option>
                    <id>plp</id>
                    <name>Category pages</name>
                    <name lang="de-DE">Kategorieseiten</name>
                    <name lang="nl-NL">Categorie pagina's</name>
                    <name lang="it-IT">Pagine della categorie</name><name lang="pt-PT">Páginas de categoria</name><name lang="es-ES">Páginas de categoría</name><name lang="sv-SE">Kategorisidor</name><name lang="nb-NO">Kategorisider</name><name lang="pl-PL">Strony kategorii</name><name lang="cs-CZ">Stránky kategorií</name><name lang="sl-SL">Strani kategorij</name><name lang="hu-HU">Kategória oldalak</name><name lang="fi-FI">Kategoriasivut</name><name lang="da-DK">Kategorisider</name><name lang="sk-SK">Stránky kategórií</name>
                </option>
                <option>
                    <id>pdp</id>
                    <name>Product pages</name>
                    <name lang="de-DE">Produktseiten</name>
                    <name lang="nl-NL">Product pagina's</name>
                    <name lang="it-IT">Pagine dei prodotti</name><name lang="pt-PT">Páginas de produto</name><name lang="es-ES">Páginas de producto</name><name lang="sv-SE">Produkt sidor</name><name lang="nb-NO">Produktsider</name><name lang="pl-PL">Strony produktów</name><name lang="cs-CZ">Stránky produktu</name><name lang="sl-SL">Strani izdelkov</name><name lang="hu-HU">Termék oldalak</name><name lang="fi-FI">Tuotesivut</name><name lang="da-DK">Produktsider</name><name lang="sk-SK">Stránky produktov</name>
                </option>
                <option>
                    <id>offcanvas</id>
                    <name>Offcanvas cart</name>
                    <name lang="de-DE">Offcanvas Warenkorb</name>
                    <name lang="nl-NL">Offcanvas winkelmand</name>
                    <name lang="it-IT">Carrello offcanvas</name><name lang="pt-PT">Carrinho suspenso</name><name lang="es-ES">Páginas desplegable</name><name lang="sv-SE">Offcanvas-korg</name><name lang="nb-NO">Offcanvas handlekurv</name><name lang="pl-PL">Koszyk wysuwany z boku</name><name lang="cs-CZ">Boční vyskakovací košík</name><name lang="sl-SL">Odstranitev košarice</name><name lang="hu-HU">Oldalsávos kosár</name><name lang="fi-FI">Offcanvas-ostoskori</name><name lang="da-DK">Offcanvas kurv</name><name lang="sk-SK">Vysúvací košík</name>
                </option>
                <option>
                    <id>cart</id>
                    <name>Cart page</name>
                    <name lang="de-DE">Warenkorbseite</name>
                    <name lang="nl-NL">Winkelmand</name>
                    <name lang="it-IT">Pagina del carrello</name><name lang="pt-PT">Página do carrinho</name><name lang="es-ES">Página del carrito</name><name lang="sv-SE">Varukorgs sida</name><name lang="nb-NO">Handlekurvside</name><name lang="pl-PL">Strona koszyka</name><name lang="cs-CZ">Stránka košíku</name><name lang="sl-SL">Stran košarice</name><name lang="hu-HU">Kosár oldal</name><name lang="fi-FI">Ostoskori-sivu</name><name lang="da-DK">Kurvside</name><name lang="sk-SK">Stránka košíka</name>
                </option>
            </options>
        </input-field>
        <input-field type="text">
            <name>applePayDirectDomainAllowList</name>
            <label>Allowed Domains for Apple Pay Direct</label>
            <label lang="de-DE">Zulässige Domains für die Apple Pay Direct</label>
            <label lang="nl-NL">Toegestane domeinen voor Apple Pay Direct</label>
            <label lang="it-IT">Domini consentiti per Apple Pay Direct</label><label lang="pt-PT">Domínios Permitidos para o Apple Pay Direct</label><label lang="es-ES">Dominios permitidos Apple Pay Direct</label><label lang="sv-SE">Tillåtna domäner för Apple Pay Direkt</label><label lang="nb-NO">Tillatte domener for Apple Pay Direct</label><label lang="pl-PL">Dozwolone domeny dla Apple Pay Direct</label><label lang="cs-CZ">Povolené domény pro Apple Pay Direct</label><label lang="sl-SL">Dovoljene domene za Apple Pay Direct</label><label lang="hu-HU">Engedélyezett domainek az Apple Pay közvetlenhez</label><label lang="fi-FI">Sallitut verkkotunnukset Apple Pay Directille</label><label lang="da-DK">Tilladte domæner for Apple Pay Direct</label><label lang="sk-SK">Povolené domény pre Apple Pay Direct</label>
            <helpText>
                Enter the domains that are allowed for Apple Pay Direct, separated by commas.
                This setting is optional and only required if you are using a headless setup
                and want to provide an alternative domain for your Apple Pay Direct integration.
            </helpText>
            <helpText lang="de-DE">
                Geben Sie die Domains ein, die für die Apple Pay Direct zugelassen sind, getrennt durch Kommas.
                Diese Einstellung ist optional und nur erforderlich, wenn Sie ein Headless-Setup verwenden
                und eine alternative Domain für Ihre Apple Pay Direct Integration bereitstellen möchten.
            </helpText>
            <helpText lang="nl-NL">
                Voer de domeinen in die zijn toegestaan voor Apple Pay Direct, gescheiden door komma's.
                Deze instelling is optioneel en alleen nodig als u een headless setup gebruikt
                en een alternatieve domein voor uw Apple Pay Direct integratie wilt opgeven.
            </helpText>
            <helpText lang="it-IT">
                Inserisci i domini consentiti per Apple Pay Direct, separati da virgole.
                Questa impostazione è facoltativa ed è necessaria solo
                se stai utilizzando una configurazione headless
            </helpText><helpText lang="pt-PT">Insira os domínios que são permitidos para o Apple Pay Direct, separados por vírgulas. Esta configuração é opcional e só é necessária se estiver a utilizar uma configuração sem headless </helpText><helpText lang="es-ES">Añade dominios permitidos para Apple Pay Direct, separados por comas. Esta configuración es opcional y solo se requiere si estás usando la configuración headless </helpText><helpText lang="sv-SE">Ange de domäner som är tillåtna för Apple Pay Direkt, separerade med kommatecken. Denna inställning är valfri och krävs endast om du använder en headless-uppställning </helpText><helpText lang="nb-NO">Skriv inn domenene som er tillatt for Apple Pay Direct, atskilt med komma. Denne innstillingen er valgfri og kreves kun hvis du bruker et headless-oppsett </helpText><helpText lang="pl-PL">Wprowadź domeny, które są dozwolone dla Apple Pay Direct, oddzielone przecinkami. To ustawienie jest opcjonalne i wymagane tylko wtedy, gdy używasz konfiguracji headless </helpText><helpText lang="cs-CZ">Zadejte domény, které jsou povolené pro Apple Pay Direct, oddělené čárkami. Tato nastavení jsou volitelná a vyžadována pouze v případě, že používáte headless setup </helpText><helpText lang="sl-SL">Vnesite domene, ki so dovoljene za Apple Pay Direct, ločene z vejicami. Ta nastavitev je neobvezna in potrebna le, če uporabljate headless sistem </helpText><helpText lang="hu-HU">Adja hozzá az Apple Pay Direct számára engedélyezett domaineket, vesszővel elválasztva. Ez a konfiguráció nem kötelező, és csak akkor szükséges, ha fej nélküli konfigurációt használ </helpText><helpText lang="fi-FI">Anna Apple Pay Directin sallitut verkkotunnukset pilkuilla erotettuina. Tämä asetus on valinnainen ja vaaditaan vain, jos käytät headless-asetusta </helpText><helpText lang="da-DK">Indtast de domæner, der er tilladt for Apple Pay Direct, adskilt af kommaer. Denne indstilling er valgfri og kræves kun, hvis du bruger en headless-opsætning </helpText><helpText lang="sk-SK">Zadajte domény, ktoré sú povolené pre Apple Pay Direct, oddelené čiarkami. Toto nastavenie je voliteľné a vyžaduje sa iba ak používate bezhlavé nastavenie.</helpText>
        </input-field>
    </card>


    <card>
        <title>Order Management</title>
        <title lang="de-DE">Auftragsverwaltung</title>
        <title lang="nl-NL">Order beheer</title>
        <title lang="it-IT">Gestione degli Ordini</title><title lang="pt-PT">Gestão de encomendas</title><title lang="es-ES">Gestión de pedidos</title><title lang="sv-SE">Beställningshantering</title><title lang="nb-NO">Ordrebehandling</title><title lang="pl-PL">Zarządzanie zamówieniami</title><title lang="cs-CZ">Správa objednávek</title><title lang="sl-SL">Upravljanje naročil</title><title lang="hu-HU">Megrendelés kezelése</title><title lang="fi-FI">Tilauksen hallinta</title><title lang="da-DK">Ordrehåndtering</title><title lang="sk-SK">Správa objednávok</title>
        <input-field type="int">
            <name>paymentMethodBankTransferDueDateDays</name>
            <label>Bank Transfer Due Date (Days)</label>
            <label lang="de-DE">Banküberweisung Fälligkeitsdauer (in Tagen seit Bestelleingang)</label>
            <label lang="nl-NL">Bankoverschrijving vervaldatum (in dagen vanaf ontvangen bestelling)</label>
            <label lang="it-IT">Data di scadenza del bonifico bancario (giorni)</label><label lang="pt-PT">Data de Vencimento da Transferência Bancária (Dias)</label><label lang="es-ES">Fecha de vencimiento de transferencia bancaria (días)</label><label lang="sv-SE">Banköverförings förfallodatum (dagar)</label><label lang="nb-NO">Forfallsdato for bankoverføring (dager)</label><label lang="pl-PL">Termin płatności przelewem (dni)</label><label lang="cs-CZ">Datum splatnosti pro bankovní převod (dny)</label><label lang="sl-SL">Rok plačila za bančno nakazilo (dni)</label><label lang="hu-HU">Banki átutalás esedékességi napja (napok)</label><label lang="fi-FI">Tilisiirron eräpäivä (päivät)</label><label lang="da-DK">Forfaldsdato for bankoverførsel (dage)</label><label lang="sk-SK">Dátum splatnosti bankového prevodu (dni)</label>
            <helpText>Assign a custom "due date" for the Bank Transfer payment method. This is the time the customer can pay until the payment expires.</helpText>
            <helpText lang="de-DE">Konfiguration eines eigenen Verfallsdatums für die Zahlungsart 'Bank Transfer'. Dies ist der Zeitraum einer möglichen Zahlung bis die Zahlungsmöglichkeit verfällt.</helpText>
            <helpText lang="nl-NL">Wijs een aangepaste "vervaldatum" toe voor de betaalmethode Bankoverschrijving. Dit is de periode dat de klant kan betalen totdat de betaling vervalt.</helpText>
            <helpText lang="it-IT">Assegna una "data di scadenza" personalizzata per il metodo di pagamento tramite bonifico bancario. Questo è il tempo entro il quale il cliente può effettuare il pagamento prima che scada.</helpText><helpText lang="pt-PT">Atribua uma "data de vencimento" personalizada para o método de pagamento por transferência bancária. Este é o período em que o cliente pode pagar até o pagamento expirar.</helpText><helpText lang="es-ES">Asigna una "fecha de vencimiento" personalizada para el pago mediante transferencia bancaria. Será el plazo de pago del cliente hasta su vencimiento.</helpText><helpText lang="sv-SE">Tilldela ett anpassat "förfallodatum" för betalningsmetoden banköverföring. Detta är den tid kunden kan betala innan betalningen löper ut.</helpText><helpText lang="nb-NO">Tildel en egendefinert "forfallsdato" for betalingsmetoden bankoverføring. Dette er tidsfristen kunden har for å betale før betalingen utløper.</helpText><helpText lang="pl-PL">Przypisz niestandardowy "termin płatności" dla metody płatności Przelew bankowy. Jest to czas, w którym klient może dokonać płatności, zanim termin wygaśnie.</helpText><helpText lang="cs-CZ">Přiřaďte vlastní 'datum splatnosti' pro platební metodu Bankovní převod. Toto je doba, dokdy může zákazník zaplatit, než platba vyprší.</helpText><helpText lang="sl-SL">Dodelite prilagojen "rok" za način plačila z bančnim nakazilom. To je čas, do katerega lahko stranka plača, preden plačilo poteče.</helpText><helpText lang="hu-HU">Állítson be egyéni "esedékességi dátumot" a banki átutalás fizetési módhoz. Ez az idő, ameddig az ügyfél tud fizetni, amíg a tranzakció lejár.</helpText><helpText lang="fi-FI">Määritä mukautettu eräpäivä tilisiirto maksutavalle. Tämä on aika, jonka kuluessa asiakas voi maksaa, kunnes maksu erääntyy.</helpText><helpText lang="da-DK">Tildel en brugerdefineret "forfaldsdato" for betalingsmetoden bankoverførsel. Dette er den tid, kunden kan betale, indtil betalingen udløber.</helpText><helpText lang="sk-SK">Priraďte vlastný 'dátum splatnosti' pre platobnú metódu bankový prevod. Ide o lehotu, do ktorej môže zákazník vykonať platbu, kým nevyprší jej platnosť.</helpText>
        </input-field>
        <component name="mollie-pluginconfig-section-order-lifetime-warning">
            <name>molliePluginConfigSectionOrderLifeTimeWarning</name>
        </component>
        <input-field type="int">
            <name>orderLifetimeDays</name>
            <label>Order Lifetime Days</label>
            <label lang="de-DE">Bestellungs Lebensdauer bei Mollie (in Tagen seit Bestelleingang)</label>
            <label lang="nl-NL">Levensduur bestelling bij Mollie (in dagen vanaf ontvangen bestelling)</label>
            <label lang="it-IT">Durata dell'Ordine (Giorni)</label><label lang="pt-PT">Dias de vida da encomenda</label><label lang="es-ES">Días de vida del pedido</label><label lang="sv-SE">Beställningars livstid (dagar)</label><label lang="nb-NO">Ordrelevetid dager</label><label lang="pl-PL">Czas aktywności zamówienia (dni)</label><label lang="cs-CZ">Dny platnosti objednávky</label><label lang="sl-SL">Število dni trajanja naročila</label><label lang="hu-HU">Order Lifetime Days</label><label lang="fi-FI">Tilauksen elinikäpäivät</label><label lang="da-DK">Ordrelevetid dage</label><label lang="sk-SK">Doba platnosti objednávky (v dňoch)</label>
            <helpText>Configure the lifetime of an order until it expires when not paid. This applies to all payment methods.</helpText>
            <helpText lang="de-DE">Konfiguration der Lebensdauer bis eine Bestellung verfällt, sofern sie nicht bezahlt wurde. Diese Konfiguration wirkt sich auf alle Zahlungsarten aus.</helpText>
            <helpText lang="nl-NL">Configureer de levensduur van een bestelling totdat deze vervalt als er niet betaald is. Dit geldt voor alle betaalmethoden.</helpText>
            <helpText lang="it-IT">Configura la durata di un ordine fino alla sua scadenza se non pagato. Questo si applica a tutti i metodi di pagamento.</helpText><helpText lang="pt-PT">Configure o tempo de vida de uma encomenda até que esta expire se não for paga. Isto aplica-se a todos os métodos de pagamento.</helpText><helpText lang="es-ES">Configura la duración de vida de un pedido hasta que venza su pago. Aplica a todos los métodos de pago.</helpText><helpText lang="sv-SE">Konfigurera livslängden för en order tills den löper ut om den inte betalas. Detta gäller alla betalningsmetoder.</helpText><helpText lang="nb-NO">Konfigurer varigheten til en ordre til den utløper når den ikke er betalt. Dette gjelder for alle betalingsmetoder.</helpText><helpText lang="pl-PL">Skonfiguruj czas aktywności zamówienia do momentu jego wygaśnięcia, jeśli nie zostanie opłacone. Dotyczy to wszystkich metod płatności.</helpText><helpText lang="cs-CZ">Nastavte dobu platnosti objednávky, dokud nevyprší, pokud není uhrazena. Toto nastavení platí pro všechny platební metody.</helpText><helpText lang="sl-SL">Nastavite življenjsko dobo naročila, dokler ne poteče, ko ni plačano. To velja za vse načine plačila.</helpText><helpText lang="hu-HU">Állítsa be egy rendelés élettartamát, ameddig az lejár, ha nem fizetnek érte. Ez minden fizetési módra vonatkozik.</helpText><helpText lang="fi-FI">Määritä tilauksen kesto, kunnes se vanhenee, kun sitä ei ole maksettu. Tämä koskee kaikkia maksutapoja.</helpText><helpText lang="da-DK">Konfigurer levetiden for en ordre, indtil den udløber, hvis den ikke betales. Dette gælder for alle betalingsmetoder.</helpText><helpText lang="sk-SK">Nakonfigurujte dobu platnosti objednávky, po ktorú zostane aktívna, ak nebude zaplatená. Toto nastavenie platí pre všetky platobné metódy.</helpText>
        </input-field>
        <input-field type="bool">
            <name>automaticShipping</name>
            <defaultValue>true</defaultValue>
            <label>Automatic Shipping</label>
            <label lang="de-DE">Automatischer Versand</label>
            <label lang="nl-NL">Automatische Verzending</label>
            <label lang="it-IT">Spedizione automatica</label><label lang="pt-PT">Envio Automático</label><label lang="es-ES">Envío automático</label><label lang="sv-SE">Automatisk frakt</label><label lang="nb-NO">Automatisk frakt</label><label lang="pl-PL">Automatyczna wysyłka</label><label lang="cs-CZ">Automatické odeslání</label><label lang="sl-SL">Samodejno pošiljanje</label><label lang="hu-HU">Automatikus szállítás</label><label lang="fi-FI">Automaattinen toimitus</label><label lang="da-DK">Automatisk forsendelse</label><label lang="sk-SK">Automatické odoslanie</label>
            <helpText>If enabled, the plugin will automatically trigger a shipment at Mollie when the delivery status transitions to 'shipped'.</helpText>
            <helpText lang="de-DE">Sofern aktiv, schickt das Plugin automatisch eine Versand Mitteilung an Mollie, sobald der Lieferstatus auf 'verschickt' übergeleitet wird.</helpText>
            <helpText lang="nl-NL">Indien ingeschakeld, zal de plugin automatisch een verzending activeren bij Mollie wanneer de leveringstatus overgaat naar ‘verzonden’.</helpText>
            <helpText lang="it-IT">Se abilitato, il plugin avvierà automaticamente una spedizione su Mollie quando lo stato di consegna passa a 'spedito'.</helpText><helpText lang="pt-PT">Se ativado, o plugin acionará automaticamente um envio na Mollie quando o estado de entrega passar para 'enviado'.</helpText><helpText lang="es-ES">Si se habilita, el plugin activará automáticamente un envío en Mollie cuando el estado de entrega cambie a 'enviado'.</helpText><helpText lang="sv-SE">Om aktiverad, kommer pluginet automatiskt att utlösa en frakt hos Mollie när leveransstatusen övergår till 'skickad'.</helpText><helpText lang="nb-NO">Hvis aktivert, vil pluginen automatiskt utløse en forsendelse hos Mollie når leveringsstatusen endres til 'fraktet'.</helpText><helpText lang="pl-PL">Jeśli ta opcja jest włączona, wtyczka automatycznie wywoła wysyłkę w Mollie, gdy status dostawy zmieni się na 'wysłane'.</helpText><helpText lang="cs-CZ">Pokud je tato možnost povolena, plugin automaticky spustí odeslání u Mollie, když se stav dodávky změní na 'odesláno'.</helpText><helpText lang="sl-SL">Če je omogočeno, bo vtičnik samodejno sprožil pošiljanje pri Mollie, ko se status dostave spremeni v 'odposlano'.</helpText><helpText lang="hu-HU">Ha engedélyezve van, a bővítmény automatikusan aktivál egy szállítást Mollie-nál, amikor a szállítási állapot 'kiszállítva' állapotra vált.</helpText><helpText lang="fi-FI">Jos laajennus on käytössä, se käynnistää automaattisesti lähetyksen Molliessa, kun toimitustila muuttuu lähetetyksi.</helpText><helpText lang="da-DK">Hvis aktiveret, vil pluginet automatisk udløse en forsendelse hos Mollie, når leveringsstatussen skifter til 'afsendt'.</helpText><helpText lang="sk-SK">Ak je táto možnosť povolená, doplnok automaticky spustí odoslanie v Mollie, keď sa stav doručenia zmení na 'odoslané'.</helpText>
        </input-field>
        <input-field type="bool">
            <name>automaticCancellation</name>
            <defaultValue>true</defaultValue>
            <label>Automatic Cancellation</label>
            <label lang="de-DE">Automatische Stornierung</label>
            <label lang="nl-NL">Automatische annulering</label>
            <label lang="it-IT">Annullamento automatico</label><label lang="pt-PT">Cancelamento Automático</label><label lang="es-ES">Cancelación automática</label><label lang="sv-SE">Automatisk avbokning</label><label lang="nb-NO">Automatisk kansellering</label><label lang="pl-PL">Automatyczne anulowanie</label><label lang="cs-CZ">Automatické zrušení</label><label lang="sl-SL">Samodejni preklic</label><label lang="hu-HU">Automatikus törlés</label><label lang="fi-FI">Automaattinen peruutus</label><label lang="da-DK">Automatisk annullering</label><label lang="sk-SK">Automatické zrušenie</label>
            <helpText>If enabled, the plugin will automatically cancel Mollie orders when being cancelled in Shopware. Only orders that are created, authorized or partially shipped will be cancelled. If partially shipped, only items that where not shipped will be cancelled.</helpText>
            <helpText lang="de-DE">Wenn aktiviert, storniert das Plugin Mollie-Bestellungen automatisch, wenn sie in Shopware storniert werden. Nur Bestellungen, die erstellt, autorisiert oder teilweise versandt wurden, werden storniert. Bei teilweisem Versand werden nur Artikel storniert, die nicht versendet wurden.</helpText>
            <helpText lang="nl-NL">Indien ingeschakeld, zal de plug-in automatisch Mollie-bestellingen annuleren wanneer ze worden geannuleerd in Shopware. Alleen bestellingen die zijn aangemaakt, geautoriseerd of gedeeltelijk zijn verzonden, worden geannuleerd. Indien gedeeltelijk verzonden, worden alleen artikelen geannuleerd die niet zijn verzonden.</helpText>
            <helpText lang="it-IT">Se abilitato, il plugin annullerà automaticamente gli ordini Mollie quando vengono annullati in Shopware. Verranno annullati solo gli ordini creati, autorizzati o parzialmente spediti. Se parzialmente spediti, verranno annullati solo gli articoli non spediti.</helpText><helpText lang="pt-PT">Se ativado, o plugin cancelará automaticamente as encomendas da Mollie quando estas forem canceladas no Shopware. Apenas encomendas criadas, autorizadas ou parcialmente enviadas serão canceladas. Se parcialmente enviadas, apenas os itens que não foram enviados serão cancelados.</helpText><helpText lang="es-ES">Si se habilita, el plugin cancelará los pedidos de Mollie automáticamente cuando se cancelen en Shopware. Solo se cancelarán los pedidos que se hayan creado, autorizado o parcialmente enviados. Si se envía parcialmente, solo se cancelarán los artículos que no se hayan enviado.</helpText><helpText lang="sv-SE">Om aktiverad kommer pluginet automatiskt att avbryta Mollie-beställningar när de avbryts i Shopware. Endast beställningar som är skapade, auktoriserade eller delvis skickade kommer att avbokas. Om delvis skickad, kommer endast artiklar som inte skickats avbokas.</helpText><helpText lang="nb-NO">Hvis aktivert, vil pluginen automatisk kansellere Mollie ordrer når de blir kansellert i Shopware. Kun bestillinger som er opprettet, autorisert eller delvis fraktet vil bli kansellert. Hvis delvis fraktet, vil kun varer som ikke ble sendt bli kansellert.</helpText><helpText lang="pl-PL">Jeśli ta opcja jest włączona, wtyczka automatycznie anuluje zamówienia Mollie, gdy zostaną anulowane w Shopware. Tylko zamówienia o statusie utworzone, autoryzowane lub częściowo wysłane zostaną anulowane. Jeśli zamówienie zostało częściowo wysłane, anulowane zostaną tylko pozycje, które nie zostały wysłane.</helpText><helpText lang="cs-CZ">Pokud je tato možnost povolena, plugin automaticky zruší objednávky Mollie, když budou zrušeny v Shopware. Zrušeny budou pouze objednávky, které byly vytvořeny, autorizovány nebo částečně odeslány. Při částečném odeslání budou zrušeny pouze položky, které nebyly odeslány.</helpText><helpText lang="sl-SL">Če je omogočeno, bo vtičnik samodejno preklical naročila Mollie, ko bodo preklicana v Shopware. Preklicana bodo samo naročila, ki so bila ustvarjena, avtorizirana ali delno odposlana. Če so bila delno odposlana, se bodo preklicali samo tisti predmeti, ki niso bili odposlani.</helpText><helpText lang="hu-HU">Ha engedélyezve, a bővítmény automatikusan törli a Mollie megrendeléseket, amikor azokat a Shopware-ban törlik. Csak a létrehozott, engedélyezett vagy részben kiszállított megrendelések kerülnek törlésre. Ha részben ki vannak szállítva, csak a nem kiszállított tételek kerülnek törlésre.</helpText><helpText lang="fi-FI">Jos käytössä, laajennus peruuttaa automaattisesti Mollie-tilaukset, kun ne peruutetaan Shopwaressa. Vain luodut, valtuutetut tai osittain toimitetut tilaukset peruutetaan. Jos tilaus toimitetaan osittain, vain tuotteet, joita ei ole lähetetty, peruutetaan.</helpText><helpText lang="da-DK">Hvis aktiveret, vil plugin'et automatisk annullere Mollie bestillinger, når de annulleres i Shopware. Kun bestillinger, der er oprettet, godkendt eller delvist afsendt, vil blive annulleret. Hvis delvist afsendt, vil kun de varer, der ikke er sendt, blive annulleret.</helpText><helpText lang="sk-SK">Ak je táto možnosť povolená, doplnok automaticky zruší objednávky v Mollie, keď budú zrušené v Shopware. Zrušené budú iba objednávky, ktoré sú vytvorené, autorizované alebo čiastočne odoslané. V prípade čiastočného odoslania budú zrušené iba tie položky, ktoré neboli odoslané.</helpText>
        </input-field>
        <input-field type="bool">
            <name>automaticOrderExpire</name>
            <defaultValue>false</defaultValue>
            <label>Automatic Expiration</label>
            <label lang="de-DE">Automatische Ablauf</label>
            <label lang="nl-NL">Automatische vervaldatum</label>
            <label lang="it-IT">Scadenza automatica</label><label lang="pt-PT">Expiração Automática</label><label lang="es-ES">Vencimiento automático</label><label lang="sv-SE">Automatisk utgång</label><label lang="nb-NO">Automatisk utløp</label><label lang="pl-PL">Automatyczne wygaśnięcie</label><label lang="cs-CZ">Automatické vypršení platnosti</label><label lang="sl-SL">Samodejni potek</label><label lang="hu-HU">Automatikus lejárat</label><label lang="fi-FI">Automaattinen vanheneminen</label><label lang="da-DK">Automatisk udløb</label><label lang="sk-SK">Automatické vypršanie</label>
            <helpText>If enabled, the plugin will automatically expire orders with the payment status "In Progress".</helpText>
            <helpText lang="de-DE">Wenn aktiviert, lässt das Plugin Bestellungen mit dem Status „In Bearbeitung“ und dem Zahlungsstatus „Offen“ oder „Autorisiert“ automatisch ablaufen.</helpText>
            <helpText lang="nl-NL">Als deze optie is ingeschakeld, verlopen bestellingen met de status 'In uitvoering' en de betalingsstatus 'Open' of 'Geautoriseerd' automatisch.</helpText>
            <helpText lang="it-IT">Se abilitato, il plugin scadrà automaticamente gli ordini con lo stato di pagamento "In corso".</helpText><helpText lang="pt-PT">Se ativado, o plugin expirará automaticamente as encomendas com o estado de pagamento "Em curso".</helpText><helpText lang="es-ES">Si se habilita, el plugin marcará automáticamente como vencidos los pedidos con el estado de pago "En curso".</helpText><helpText lang="sv-SE">Om aktiverad kommer pluginet automatiskt att utlösa utgång av beställningar med betalningsstatus "Pågår".</helpText><helpText lang="nb-NO">Hvis aktivert, vil pluginen automatisk la ordrer med betalingsstatusen "Under behandling" løpe ut.</helpText><helpText lang="pl-PL">Jeśli ta opcja jest włączona, wtyczka automatycznie zakończy termin aktywności zamówień ze statusem płatności „W trakcie realizacji”.</helpText><helpText lang="cs-CZ">Pokud je tato možnost povolena, plugin automaticky zneplatní objednávky se stavem platby 'Probíhá'.</helpText><helpText lang="sl-SL">Če je omogočeno, bo vtičnik samodejno potekel naročila s statusom plačila "V obdelavi".</helpText><helpText lang="hu-HU">Ha engedélyezve van, a bővítmény automatikusan lejárja a "Folyamatban" állapotú megrendeléseket.</helpText><helpText lang="fi-FI">Jos käytössä, laajennus vanhentaa automaattisesti tilaukset, joiden maksutila on "käsittelyssä".</helpText><helpText lang="da-DK">Hvis aktiveret, vil pluginet automatisk udløbe ordrer med betalingsstatus "I gang".</helpText><helpText lang="sk-SK">Ak je táto možnosť povolená, doplnok automaticky nastaví objednávky so stavom platby "Prebieha" ako expirované.</helpText>
        </input-field>
    </card>
    <card>
        <title>Refund Manager</title>
        <title lang="de-DE">Refund Manager</title>
        <title lang="nl-NL">Refund Manager</title>
        <title lang="it-IT">Refund Manager</title>
        <title lang="pt-PT">Refund Manager</title>
        <title lang="es-ES">Refund Manager</title>
        <title lang="sv-SE">Refund Manager</title>
        <title lang="nb-NO">Refund Manager</title>
        <title lang="pl-PL">Refund Manager</title><title lang="cs-CZ">Správce vrácení peněz</title><title lang="sl-SL">Upravljalnik vračil</title><title lang="hu-HU">Visszatérítés kezelő</title><title lang="fi-FI">Hyvityshallinta</title><title lang="da-DK">Refusionsadministrator</title><title lang="sk-SK">Správca vrátení peňazí</title>

        <input-field type="bool">
            <name>refundManagerEnabled</name>
            <defaultValue>true</defaultValue>
            <label>Enable Refund Manager</label>
            <label lang="de-DE">Refund Manager aktivieren</label>
            <label lang="nl-NL">Refund Manager inschakelen</label>
            <label lang="it-IT">Abilita Refund Manager</label>
            <label lang="pt-PT">Ativar o Refund Manager</label>
            <label lang="es-ES">Habilitar el administrador de reembolsos</label>
            <label lang="sv-SE">Aktivera återbetalningshanteraren</label>
            <label lang="nb-NO">Aktiver Refund Manager</label>
            <label lang="pl-PL">Włącz Menedżera zwrotów</label><label lang="cs-CZ">Povolit správce vrácení peněz</label><label lang="sl-SL">Omogoči upravljalnik vračil</label><label lang="hu-HU">Visszatérítés kezelő engedélyezése</label><label lang="fi-FI">Ota käyttöön hyvityshallinta</label><label lang="da-DK">Aktiver Refusion Manager</label><label lang="sk-SK">Povoliť správcu vrátení peňazí</label>
            <helpText>Enable or disable the Refund Manager in the Administration</helpText>
            <helpText lang="de-DE">Aktivieren oder deaktivieren Sie den Refund Manager in der Administration</helpText>
            <helpText lang="nl-NL">Schakel de Refund Manager in of uit in de administratie</helpText>
            <helpText lang="it-IT">Attivare o disattivare il Gestore dei rimborsi nell'Amministrazione.</helpText>
            <helpText lang="pt-PT">Ativar ou desativar o Refund Manager na Administração</helpText>
            <helpText lang="es-ES">Habilitar o deshabilitar el Administrador de reembolsos en la Administración</helpText>
            <helpText lang="sv-SE">Aktivera eller inaktivera återbetalningshanteraren i administrationen</helpText>
            <helpText lang="nb-NO">Aktiver eller deaktiver refusjonsbehandleren i administrasjonen</helpText>
            <helpText lang="pl-PL">Włączanie i wyłączanie Menedżera zwrotów w Administracji</helpText><helpText lang="cs-CZ">Povolte nebo zakažte správce vrácení peněz v Administraci</helpText><helpText lang="sl-SL">Omogoči ali onemogoči upravljalnik vračil v upravljanju</helpText><helpText lang="hu-HU">A Visszatérítéskezelőt engedélyezheti vagy letilthatja az Adminisztrációban</helpText><helpText lang="fi-FI">Ota hyvityshallinta käyttöön tai poista käytöstä hallinnoinnissa</helpText><helpText lang="da-DK">Aktiver eller deaktiver Refusion Manager i administrationen</helpText><helpText lang="sk-SK">Povoliť alebo zakázať Správcu vrátení peňazí v administrácii</helpText>
        </input-field>
        <input-field type="bool">
            <name>refundManagerAutoStockReset</name>
            <defaultValue>true</defaultValue>
            <label>Automatically include Stock-Reset</label>
            <label lang="de-DE">Automatisch Lagerbestand zurücksetzen vorbefüllen</label>
            <label lang="nl-NL">Automatisch voorraad-reset instellen</label>
            <label lang="it-IT">Includi automaticamente Reimpostazione Stock</label><label lang="pt-PT">Incluir automaticamente a Reposição de Stock</label><label lang="es-ES">Ajustar stock automáticamente</label><label lang="sv-SE">Automatiskt inkludera lageråterställning</label><label lang="nb-NO">Automatisk inkluder tilbakestilling av lagret</label><label lang="pl-PL">Automatycznie uwzględnij reset stanu magazynowego</label><label lang="cs-CZ">Automaticky zahrnout obnovení zásob</label><label lang="sl-SL">Samodejno vključite ponastavitev zalog</label><label lang="hu-HU">Automatikusan tartalmazza a készlet-visszaállítást</label><label lang="fi-FI">Sisällytä automaattisesti varaston nollaus</label><label lang="da-DK">Inkluderer automatisk lagernulstilling</label><label lang="sk-SK">Automaticky zahrnúť obovenie zásob</label>
            <helpText>Automatically set the entered refund quantity also as the quantity to be used to increase the stock again.</helpText>
            <helpText lang="de-DE">Sofern aktiv, wird die eingegebene Rückerstattungsmenge automatisch als Menge für den Lagerbestand verwendet und dieses Feld vorbefüllt.</helpText>
            <helpText lang="nl-NL">Stel de ingevoerde restitutiehoeveelheid automatisch ook in als de hoeveelheid die moet worden gebruikt om de voorraad weer te vergroten</helpText>
            <helpText lang="it-IT">Imposta automaticamente la quantità di rimborso inserita anche come quantità da utilizzare per aumentare nuovamente lo stock.</helpText>
            <helpText lang="pt-PT">Definir automaticamente a quantidade de reembolso introduzida bem como a quantidade a utilizar para aumentar novamente o stock.</helpText><helpText lang="es-ES">Establece automáticamente que la cantidad de devoluciones es la cantidad a utilizar para reponer el stock.</helpText><helpText lang="sv-SE">Automatiskt ställ in den angivna återbetalningskvantiteten som även kvantiteten som ska användas för att öka lagret igen.</helpText><helpText lang="nb-NO">Automatisk angi den angitte refusjonsmengden også som kvantitet for å øke lageret igjen.</helpText><helpText lang="pl-PL">Automatycznie ustaw wprowadzoną ilość zwrotu również jako ilość dodawaną do stanu magazynowego.</helpText><helpText lang="cs-CZ">Automaticky nastavte zadané množství vrácení jako množství, které se použije k opětovnému navýšení zásob.</helpText><helpText lang="sl-SL">Samodejno nastavite vnešeno količino vračila tudi kot količino, ki se uporabi za ponovno povečanje zaloge.</helpText><helpText lang="hu-HU">Automatikusan állítsa be az beírt visszatérítési mennyiséget is a készlet növelésére szolgáló mennyiségként.</helpText><helpText lang="fi-FI">Aseta syötetty palautusmäärä automaattisesti myös määräksi, jota käytetään varaston lisäämiseen.</helpText><helpText lang="da-DK">Automatisk indstill den indtastede refusionsmængde også som den mængde, der skal bruges til at øge lageret igen.</helpText><helpText lang="sk-SK">Automaticky nastaviť zadané množstvo na vrátenie aj ako množstvo, ktoré sa má opäť pridať do skladu.</helpText>
        </input-field>
        <input-field type="bool">
            <name>refundManagerVerifyRefund</name>
            <defaultValue>true</defaultValue>
            <label>Verify Refunds</label>
            <label lang="de-DE">Rückerstattungen überprüfen</label>
            <label lang="nl-NL">Terugbetalingen controleren</label>
            <label lang="it-IT">Verifica rimborsi</label><label lang="pt-PT">Verificar Reembolsos</label><label lang="es-ES">Verificar reembolsos</label><label lang="sv-SE">Verifiera återbetalningar</label><label lang="nb-NO">Verifiser refusjoner</label><label lang="pl-PL">Weryfikuj zwroty</label><label lang="cs-CZ">Ověřit vrácení peněz</label><label lang="sl-SL">Potrdite vračila</label><label lang="hu-HU">Visszatérítések ellenőrzése</label><label lang="fi-FI">Vahvista hyvitykset</label><label lang="da-DK">Verificer tilbagebetalinger</label><label lang="sk-SK">Overiť vrátenia peňazí</label>
            <helpText>If enabled, a verification checkbox needs to be checked to proceed with the refund. We recommend this to avoid accidental refunds and stock changes.</helpText>
            <helpText lang="de-DE">Wenn aktiv, muss ein Überprüfungskästchen aktiviert werden, um mit der Rückerstattung fortzufahren. Wir empfehlen dies, um versehentliche Rückerstattungen und Bestandsänderungen zu vermeiden.</helpText>
            <helpText lang="nl-NL">Indien actief, moet een selectievakje worden geactiveerd om verder te gaan met de terugbetaling. Wij raden dit aan om onbedoelde terugbetalingen en voorraadwijzigingen te voorkomen.</helpText>
            <helpText lang="it-IT">Se abilitato, è necessario selezionare una casella di verifica per procedere con il rimborso. Raccomandiamo questa opzione per evitare rimborsi accidentali e modifiche dello stock.</helpText>
            <helpText lang="pt-PT">Se ativado, é necessário marcar uma caixa de verificação para proceder ao reembolso. Recomendamos esta opção para evitar reembolsos acidentais e alterações de stock.</helpText><helpText lang="es-ES">Si se habilita, será necesario marcar una casilla de verificación para proceder con el reembolso. Opción recomendada para evitar reembolsos y cambios de stock accidentales.</helpText><helpText lang="sv-SE">Om aktiverad, behöver en verifieringscheckbox kontrolleras för att fortsätta med återbetalningen. Vi rekommenderar detta för att undvika oavsiktliga återbetalningar och lagerändringar.</helpText><helpText lang="nb-NO">Hvis aktivert, må en verifiseringsboks bli krysset av for å fortsette med refusjonen. Vi anbefaler dette for å unngå utilsiktede refusjoner og lagerendringer.</helpText><helpText lang="pl-PL">Jeśli ta opcja jest włączona, konieczne będzie zaznaczenie pola weryfikacji, aby kontynuować zwrot. Zalecamy tę opcję, aby uniknąć przypadkowych zwrotów i zmian w stanie magazynowym.</helpText><helpText lang="cs-CZ">Pokud je tato možnost povolena, je nutné zaškrtnout ověřovací políčko, aby bylo možné pokračovat ve vrácení. Doporučujeme to, aby se předešlo náhodným vrácením a změnám zásob.</helpText><helpText lang="sl-SL">Če je omogočeno, je treba potrditveno polje označiti, da nadaljujete z vračilom. Priporočamo vam, da to storite, da se izognete naključnim vračilom in spremembam zalog.</helpText><helpText lang="hu-HU">Ha engedélyezve van, egy jelölőnégyzetet be kell jelölni a visszatérítés folytatásához. Ajánlott lehetőség a véletlen visszatérítések és készletváltozások elkerülésére.</helpText><helpText lang="fi-FI">Jos käytössä, vahvistusvalintaruutu on valittava hyvityksen jatkamiseksi. Suosittelemme tätä välttääksesi vahingossa tapahtuvia palautuksia ja varastomuutoksia.</helpText><helpText lang="da-DK">Hvis aktiveret, skal en verifikationsboks krydses af for at fortsætte med refunderingen. Vi anbefaler dette for at undgå utilsigtede refunderinger og lagerændringer.</helpText><helpText lang="sk-SK">Ak je táto možnosť povolená, na pokračovanie vo vrátení platby je potrebné zaškrtnúť overovací checkbox. Odporúčame to na zabránenie náhodným vráteniam a zmenám skladu.</helpText>
        </input-field>
        <input-field type="bool">
            <name>refundManagerShowInstructions</name>
            <defaultValue>true</defaultValue>
            <label>Show Instructions</label>
            <label lang="de-DE">Anleitungen anzeigen</label>
            <label lang="nl-NL">Handleiding tonen</label>
            <label lang="it-IT">Mostra istruzioni</label><label lang="pt-PT">Mostrar Instruções</label><label lang="es-ES">Mostrar instrucciones</label><label lang="sv-SE">Visa instruktioner</label><label lang="nb-NO">Vis instruksjoner</label><label lang="pl-PL">Pokaż instrukcje</label><label lang="cs-CZ">Zobrazit pokyny</label><label lang="sl-SL">Prikaži navodila</label><label lang="hu-HU">Ut instrukciók megjelenítése</label><label lang="fi-FI">Näytä ohjeet</label><label lang="da-DK">Vis instruktioner</label><label lang="sk-SK">Zobraziť pokyny</label>
            <helpText>Shows or hides the instructions area. You can simply turn this off in case it's disturbing once you're familiar with the Refund Manager.</helpText>
            <helpText lang="de-DE">Diese Funktion kann benutzt werden, um die Anleitungen auszublenden, sofern man einmal mit dem Refund Manager vetraut ist.</helpText>
            <helpText lang="nl-NL">Toont of verbergt de handleiding. Als het storend is, kan je het direkt deactiveren als je eenmaal vertrouwd bent met de Refund Manager.</helpText>
            <helpText lang="it-IT">Mostra o nasconde l'area delle istruzioni. Puoi semplicemente disattivarla nel caso in cui diventi fastidiosa una volta che hai preso familiarità con il Gestore Rimborsi.</helpText><helpText lang="pt-PT">Mostra ou oculta a área de instruções. Pode simplesmente desativar esta opção, caso seja perturbadora, quando estiver familiarizado com o Gestor de Reembolsos.</helpText><helpText lang="es-ES">Muestra u oculta las instrucciones. Puedes desactivar la opción una vez que estés familiarizado con el Administrador de reembolsos.</helpText><helpText lang="sv-SE">Visar eller döljer instruktionen för området. Du kan helt enkelt stänga av detta om det är störande när du blivit bekant med Återbetalningshanteraren.</helpText><helpText lang="nb-NO">Viser eller skjuler instruksjonsområdet. Du kan enkelt slå av dette hvis det forstyrrer når du er kjent med Refusjonsbehandleren.</helpText><helpText lang="pl-PL">Pokazuje lub ukrywa obszar instrukcji. Możesz wyłączyć tę opcję, jeśli przeszkadza Ci, gdy już zaznajomiłeś się z Menedżerem Zwrotów.</helpText><helpText lang="cs-CZ">Zobrazuje nebo skrývá pokyny. Můžete ji jednoduše vypnout, pokud vám začne překážet, jakmile se seznámíte se Správcem vrácení peněz.</helpText><helpText lang="sl-SL">Pokaže ali skrije področje z navodili. To lahko preprosto izklopite, če vas moti, ko poznate uporabo upravljalca vračil.</helpText><helpText lang="hu-HU">Megjeleníti vagy elrejti az útmutató területet. Egyszerűen kikapcsolhatja, ha zavaró, miután megismerte a Visszatérítés Kezelőt.</helpText><helpText lang="fi-FI">Näyttää tai piilottaa ohjealueen. Voit yksinkertaisesti poistaa tämän käytöstä, jos se on häiritsee, kun olet tutustunut hyvityshallintaan.</helpText><helpText lang="da-DK">Viser eller skjuler instruktionsområdet. Du kan nemt deaktivere dette, hvis det forstyrrer, når du er blevet bekendt med Refusion Manager.</helpText><helpText lang="sk-SK">Zobrazuje alebo skrýva oblasť s inštrukciami. Keď sa so Správcom vrátení peňazí už zoznámite, môžete ju jednoducho vypnúť, ak vám bude vadiť.</helpText>
        </input-field>
        <input-field type="bool">
            <name>refundManagerCreateCreditNotes</name>
            <defaultValue>false</defaultValue>
            <label>Create Credit Notes</label>
            <label lang="de-DE">Gutschriften erstellen</label>
            <label lang="nl-NL">Creditnota's maken</label>
            <label lang="it-IT">Crea note di credito</label>
            <label lang="pt-PT">Criar Nota de Crédito</label>
            <label lang="es-ES">Crear notas de crédito</label>
            <label lang="sv-SE">Skapa kreditnotor</label>
            <label lang="nb-NO">Opprett kreditnotaer</label>
            <label lang="pl-PL">Utwórz noty kredytowe</label>
            <label lang="cs-CZ">Vytvořte kreditní poznámky</label>
            <label lang="sl-SL">Ustvarite dobropise</label>
            <label lang="hu-HU">Készítsen jóváírási jegyeket</label>
            <label lang="fi-FI">Luo luottolaskuja</label>
            <label lang="da-DK">Opret kreditnotaer</label>
            <label lang="sk-SK">Vytvoriť dobropisy</label>
            <helpText>Automatically create a credit note in Shopware when a refund is processed.</helpText>
            <helpText lang="de-DE">Erstellt automatisch eine Gutschrift in Shopware, wenn eine Rückerstattung verarbeitet wird.</helpText>
            <helpText lang="nl-NL">Maak automatisch een creditnota in Shopware wanneer een terugbetaling wordt verwerkt.</helpText>
            <helpText lang="it-IT">Crea automaticamente una nota di credito in Shopware quando viene elaborato un rimborso.</helpText>
            <helpText lang="pt-PT">Criar automaticamente uma nota de crédito no Shopware ao processar um reembolso</helpText>
            <helpText lang="es-ES">Cree automáticamente una nota de crédito en Shopware cuando se procese un reembolso</helpText>
            <helpText lang="sv-SE">Skapa automatiskt en kreditnota i Shopware när en återbetalning behandlas</helpText>
            <helpText lang="nb-NO">Opprett automatisk en kreditnota i Shopware når en refusjon behandles.</helpText>
            <helpText lang="pl-PL">Automatyczne tworzenie noty kredytowej w Shopware w przypadku przetworzenia zwrotu.</helpText>
            <helpText lang="cs-CZ">Automaticky vytvořit dobropis v Shopware při zpracování refundace.</helpText>
            <helpText lang="sl-SL">Samodejno ustvarite dobropis v Shopware, ko je vračilo obdelano.</helpText>
            <helpText lang="hu-HU">A visszatérítés feldolgozásakor automatikusan jóváírást hoz létre a Shopware-ben.</helpText>
            <helpText lang="fi-FI">Luo automaattisesti hyvityslasku Shopwaressa, kun hyvitys käsitellään.</helpText>
            <helpText lang="da-DK">Opret automatisk en kreditnota i Shopware, når en refusion behandles.</helpText>
            <helpText lang="sk-SK">Automaticky vytvorte dobropis v Shopware pri spracovaní refundácie.</helpText>
        </input-field>
        <input-field type="text">
            <name>refundManagerCreateCreditNotesPrefix</name>
            <defaultValue>Refund: </defaultValue>
            <label>Credit Note Prefix</label>
            <label lang="de-DE">Gutschrift Präfix</label>
            <label lang="nl-NL">Creditnota voorvoegsel</label>
            <label lang="it-IT">Prefisso della nota di credito</label><label lang="pt-PT">Prefixo da Nota de Crédito</label><label lang="es-ES">Prefijo nota de abono</label><label lang="sv-SE">Prefix för kreditnota</label><label lang="nb-NO">Kreditnota-prefiks</label><label lang="pl-PL">Prefiks noty kredytowej</label><label lang="cs-CZ">Předpona dobropisu</label><label lang="sl-SL">Predpona dobropisa</label><label lang="hu-HU">Hiteljegy előtag</label><label lang="fi-FI">Hyvityslaskun etuliite</label><label lang="da-DK">Kreditnote præfix</label><label lang="sk-SK">Predpona dobropisu</label>
            <helpText>Prefix for the credit note number. Credit note consist of prefix, original line item name and suffix</helpText>
            <helpText lang="de-DE">Präfix für die Gutschriftsnummer. Die Gutschrift besteht aus Präfix, ursprünglichem Positionsnamen und Suffix</helpText>
            <helpText lang="nl-NL">Voorvoegsel voor het creditnotanummer. De creditnota bestaat uit een voorvoegsel, de oorspronkelijke naam van het line item en een achtervoegsel.</helpText>
            <helpText lang="it-IT">Prefisso per il numero della nota di credito. La nota di credito è composta da prefisso, nome dell'articolo originale e suffisso</helpText>
            <helpText lang="pt-PT">Prefixo para o número da nota de crédito. A nota de crédito é constituída pelo prefixo, nome original do artigo, e sufixo</helpText>
            <helpText lang="es-ES">Prefijo de la nota de abono. La nota de abono consta de un prefijo, el nombre original del artículo y un sufijo</helpText>
            <helpText lang="sv-SE">Prefix for the credit note number. Credit note consist of prefix, original line item name and suffix</helpText><helpText lang="nb-NO">Prefiks for kreditnotanummeret. Kreditnotaen består av prefiks, original linjepostnavn og suffiks</helpText><helpText lang="pl-PL">Prefiks numeru noty kredytowej. Nota kredytowa składa się z prefiksu, nazwy oryginalnej pozycji i sufiksu</helpText><helpText lang="cs-CZ">Předpona pro číslo dobropisu. Dobropis se skládá z předpony, původního názvu položky a přípony</helpText><helpText lang="sl-SL">Predpona za številko dobropisa. Dobropis je sestavljen iz predpone, izvirnega imena postavke in pripone</helpText><helpText lang="hu-HU">Prefix for the credit note number. Credit note consist of prefix, original line item name and suffix</helpText><helpText lang="fi-FI">Hyvityslaskun etuliite. Hyvityslasku koostuu etuliitteestä, alkuperäisestä rivikohdan nimestä ja jälkiliitteestä</helpText><helpText lang="da-DK">Præfix for kreditnotenummeret. Kreditnoten består af præfix, original linjepostnavn og suffiks</helpText><helpText lang="sk-SK">Predpona pre číslo dobropisu. Dobropis sa skladá z predpony, pôvodného názvu položky a prípony</helpText>
        </input-field>
        <input-field type="text">
            <name>refundManagerCreateCreditNotesSuffix</name>
            <defaultValue/>
            <label>Credit Note Suffix</label>
            <label lang="de-DE">Gutschrift Suffix</label>
            <label lang="nl-NL">Creditnota achtervoegsel</label>
            <label lang="it-IT">Suffisso della nota di credito</label><label lang="pt-PT">Sufixo da Nota de Crédito</label><label lang="es-ES">Sufijo de la nota de abono</label><label lang="sv-SE">Suffix för kreditnota</label><label lang="nb-NO">Kreditnota-suffiks</label><label lang="pl-PL">Sufiks noty kredytowej</label><label lang="cs-CZ">Přípona dobropisu</label><label lang="sl-SL">Pripona dobropisa</label><label lang="hu-HU">Hiteljegy utótag</label><label lang="fi-FI">Hyvityslaskun jälkiliitte</label><label lang="da-DK">Kreditnote suffiks</label><label lang="sk-SK">Prípona dobropisu</label>
            <helpText>Suffix for the credit note number. Credit note consist of prefix, original line item name and suffix</helpText>
            <helpText lang="de-DE">Suffix für die Gutschriftsnummer. Die Gutschrift besteht aus Präfix, ursprünglichem Positionsnamen und Suffix</helpText>
            <helpText lang="nl-NL">Achtervoegsel voor het creditnotanummer. De creditnota bestaat uit een voorvoegsel, de oorspronkelijke naam van het line item en een achtervoegsel.</helpText>
            <helpText lang="it-IT">Suffisso per il numero della nota di credito. La nota di credito è composta da prefisso, nome dell'articolo originale e suffisso</helpText>
            <helpText lang="pt-PT">Sufixo para o número da nota de crédito. A nota de crédito é constituída pelo prefixo, nome original do artigo, e sufixo</helpText>
            <helpText lang="es-ES">Sufijo de la nota de abono. La nota de abono consta de un prefijo, el nombre original del artículo y un sufijo</helpText>
            <helpText lang="sv-SE">Suffix for the credit note number. Credit note consist of prefix, original line item name and suffix</helpText><helpText lang="nb-NO">Suffiks for kreditnotanummeret. En kreditnota består av prefiks, opprinnelig linjepostnavn og suffiks</helpText><helpText lang="pl-PL">Sufiks numeru noty kredytowej. Nota kredytowa składa się z prefiksu, nazwy oryginalnej pozycji i sufiksu</helpText><helpText lang="cs-CZ">Přípona pro číslo dobropisu. Dobropis se skládá z předpony, původního názvu položky a přípony</helpText><helpText lang="sl-SL">Predpona za številko dobropisa. Dobropis je sestavljen iz predpone, izvirnega imena postavke in pripone</helpText><helpText lang="hu-HU">Suffix for the credit note number. Credit note consist of prefix, original line item name and suffix</helpText><helpText lang="fi-FI">Hyvityslaskun jälkiliitte. Hyvityslasku koostuu etuliitteestä, alkuperäisestä rivikohdan nimestä ja jälkiliitteestä.</helpText><helpText lang="da-DK">Suffiks for kreditnotenummer. Kreditnoten består af præfiks, oprindeligt linjepostnavn og suffiks</helpText><helpText lang="sk-SK">Prípona pre číslo dobropisu. Dobropis sa skladá z predpony, pôvodného názvu položky a prípony</helpText>
        </input-field>
    </card>
    <card>
        <title>Order State Automation</title>
        <title lang="de-DE">Automatisch Order Status setzen</title>
        <title lang="nl-NL">Automatisch bestelstatus instellen</title>
        <title lang="it-IT">Automazione dello Stato dell'Ordine</title><title lang="pt-PT">Automatização do estado da encomenda</title><title lang="es-ES">Automatización de los estados del pedido</title><title lang="sv-SE">Orderstatusautomation</title><title lang="nb-NO">Automatisering av ordrestatus</title><title lang="pl-PL">Automatyzacja stanu zamówienia</title><title lang="cs-CZ">Automatizace stavu objednávky</title><title lang="sl-SL">Avtomatizacija stanja naročila</title><title lang="hu-HU">Megrendelés állapot automatizáció</title><title lang="fi-FI">Tilauksen tilaus automaatio</title><title lang="da-DK">Automatisering af ordrestatus</title><title lang="sk-SK">Automatizácia stavu objednávok</title>

        <input-field type="single-select">
            <name>orderStateWithAPaidTransaction</name>
            <label>Order state with a paid transaction</label>
            <label lang="de-DE">Bestellstatus bei einer bezahlten Transaktion</label>
            <label lang="nl-NL">Bestelstatus bij een betaalde transactie</label>
            <label lang="it-IT">Stato dell'ordine per una transazione pagata</label><label lang="pt-PT">Estado da encomenda com uma transação paga</label><label lang="es-ES">Estado del pedido con transacción pagada</label><label lang="sv-SE">Orderstatus med en betald transaktion</label><label lang="nb-NO">Ordrestatus med en betalt transaksjon</label><label lang="pl-PL">Status zamówienia ze zrealizowaną transakcją</label><label lang="cs-CZ">Stav objednávky s uhrazenou transakcí</label><label lang="sl-SL">Stanje naročila s plačano transakcijo</label><label lang="hu-HU">Megrendelés állapot fizetett tranzakcióval</label><label lang="fi-FI">Tilaus, jossa on maksettu maksutapahtuma</label><label lang="da-DK">Ordrestatus med en betalt transaktion</label><label lang="sk-SK">Stav objednávky so zaplatenou transakciou</label>
            <options>
                <option>
                    <id>skip</id>
                    <name>Skip this status</name>
                    <name lang="de-DE">nichts machen</name>
                    <name lang="nl-NL">Sla deze status over</name>
                    <name lang="it-IT">Salta questo stato</name><name lang="pt-PT">Ignorar este estado</name><name lang="es-ES">Omitir este estado</name><name lang="sv-SE">Hoppa över denna status</name><name lang="nb-NO">Hopp over denne statusen</name><name lang="pl-PL">Pomiń ten status</name><name lang="cs-CZ">Přeskočit tento status</name><name lang="sl-SL">Preskoči to stanje</name><name lang="hu-HU">Ugorja át ezt az állapotot</name><name lang="fi-FI">Ohita tämä tila</name><name lang="da-DK">Spring denne status over</name><name lang="sk-SK">Preskočiť tento stav</name>
                </option>
                <option>
                    <id>open</id>
                    <name>Open</name>
                    <name lang="de-DE">Offen</name>
                    <name lang="nl-NL">Open</name>
                    <name lang="it-IT">Aperto</name><name lang="pt-PT">Aberto</name><name lang="es-ES">Abierto</name><name lang="sv-SE">Öppen</name><name lang="nb-NO">Åpen</name><name lang="pl-PL">Otwarte</name><name lang="cs-CZ">Otevřené</name><name lang="sl-SL">Odprto</name><name lang="hu-HU">Nyitott</name><name lang="fi-FI">Avoin</name><name lang="da-DK">Åben</name><name lang="sk-SK">Otvorené</name>
                </option>
                <option>
                    <id>in_progress</id>
                    <name>In progress</name>
                    <name lang="de-DE">In Bearbeitung</name>
                    <name lang="nl-NL">In uitvoering</name>
                    <name lang="it-IT">In corso</name><name lang="pt-PT">Em curso</name><name lang="es-ES">En curso</name><name lang="sv-SE">Pågår</name><name lang="nb-NO">Under behandling</name><name lang="pl-PL">W trakcie realizacji</name><name lang="cs-CZ">Probíhá</name><name lang="sl-SL">V teku</name><name lang="hu-HU">Folyamatban</name><name lang="fi-FI">Käynnissä</name><name lang="da-DK">I gang</name><name lang="sk-SK">Prebieha</name>
                </option>
                <option>
                    <id>completed</id>
                    <name>Completed</name>
                    <name lang="de-DE">Komplett</name>
                    <name lang="nl-NL">Voltooid</name>
                    <name lang="it-IT">Completato</name><name lang="pt-PT">Concluído</name><name lang="es-ES">Completado</name><name lang="sv-SE">Slutförd</name><name lang="nb-NO">Fullført</name><name lang="pl-PL">Zakończone</name><name lang="cs-CZ">Dokončeno</name><name lang="sl-SL">Končano</name><name lang="hu-HU">Befejezett</name><name lang="fi-FI">Suoritettu</name><name lang="da-DK">Færdiggjort</name><name lang="sk-SK">Dokončené</name>
                </option>
                <option>
                    <id>cancelled</id>
                    <name>Cancelled</name>
                    <name lang="de-DE">Abgebrochen</name>
                    <name lang="nl-NL">Geannuleerd</name>
                    <name lang="it-IT">Annullato</name><name lang="pt-PT">Cancelado</name><name lang="es-ES">Cancelado</name><name lang="sv-SE">Avbruten</name><name lang="nb-NO">Kansellert</name><name lang="pl-PL">Anulowane</name><name lang="cs-CZ">Zrušeno</name><name lang="sl-SL">Preklicano</name><name lang="hu-HU">Törölt</name><name lang="fi-FI">Peruutettu</name><name lang="da-DK">Annulleret</name><name lang="sk-SK">Zrušené</name>
                </option>
            </options>
        </input-field>
        <input-field type="single-select">
            <name>orderStateWithAFailedTransaction</name>
            <label>Order state with a failed transaction</label>
            <label lang="de-DE">Bestellstatus bei einer fehlgeschlagenen Transaktion</label>
            <label lang="nl-NL">Bestelstatus bij een mislukte transactie</label>
            <label lang="it-IT">Stato dell'ordine per una transazione non riuscita</label><label lang="pt-PT">Estado da encomenda com uma transação falhada</label><label lang="es-ES">Estado del pedido con transacción fallida</label><label lang="sv-SE">Orderstatus med en misslyckad transaktion</label><label lang="nb-NO">Ordrestatus med en mislykket transaksjon</label><label lang="pl-PL">Status zamówienia z nieudaną transakcją</label><label lang="cs-CZ">Stav objednávky s neúspěšnou transakcí</label><label lang="sl-SL">Stanje naročila z neuspešno transakcijo</label><label lang="hu-HU">Megrendelés állapot sikertelen tranzakcióval</label><label lang="fi-FI">Tilaus, jossa on epäonnistunut maksutapahtuma</label><label lang="da-DK">Ordrestatus med en mislykket transaktion</label><label lang="sk-SK">Stav objednávky so neúspešnou transakciou</label>
            <options>
                <option>
                    <id>skip</id>
                    <name>Skip this status</name>
                    <name lang="de-DE">nichts machen</name>
                    <name lang="nl-NL">Sla deze status over</name>
                    <name lang="it-IT">Salta questo stato</name><name lang="pt-PT">Ignorar este estado</name><name lang="es-ES">Omitir este estado</name><name lang="sv-SE">Hoppa över denna status</name><name lang="nb-NO">Hopp over denne statusen</name><name lang="pl-PL">Pomiń ten status</name><name lang="cs-CZ">Přeskočit tento stav</name><name lang="sl-SL">Preskoči to stanje</name><name lang="hu-HU">Ugorja át ezt az állapotot</name><name lang="fi-FI">Ohita tämä tila</name><name lang="da-DK">Spring denne status over</name><name lang="sk-SK">Preskočiť tento stav</name>
                </option>
                <option>
                    <id>open</id>
                    <name>Open</name>
                    <name lang="de-DE">Offen</name>
                    <name lang="nl-NL">Open</name>
                    <name lang="it-IT">Aperto</name><name lang="pt-PT">Aberto</name><name lang="es-ES">Abierto</name><name lang="sv-SE">Öppen</name><name lang="nb-NO">Åpen</name><name lang="pl-PL">Otwarte</name><name lang="cs-CZ">Otevřené</name><name lang="sl-SL">Odprto</name><name lang="hu-HU">Nyitott</name><name lang="fi-FI">Avoin</name><name lang="da-DK">Åben</name><name lang="sk-SK">Otvorené</name>
                </option>
                <option>
                    <id>in_progress</id>
                    <name>In progress</name>
                    <name lang="de-DE">In Bearbeitung</name>
                    <name lang="nl-NL">In uitvoering</name>
                    <name lang="it-IT">In corso</name><name lang="pt-PT">Em curso</name><name lang="es-ES">En curso</name><name lang="sv-SE">Pågår</name><name lang="nb-NO">Under behandling</name><name lang="pl-PL">W trakcie realizacji</name><name lang="cs-CZ">Probíhá</name><name lang="sl-SL">V teku</name><name lang="hu-HU">Folyamatban</name><name lang="fi-FI">Käynnissä</name><name lang="da-DK">I gang</name><name lang="sk-SK">V priebehu</name>
                </option>
                <option>
                    <id>completed</id>
                    <name>Completed</name>
                    <name lang="de-DE">Komplett</name>
                    <name lang="nl-NL">Voltooid</name>
                    <name lang="it-IT">Completato</name><name lang="pt-PT">Concluído</name><name lang="es-ES">Completado</name><name lang="sv-SE">Slutförd</name><name lang="nb-NO">Fullført</name><name lang="pl-PL">Zakończone</name><name lang="cs-CZ">Dokončeno</name><name lang="sl-SL">Končano</name><name lang="hu-HU">Befejezett</name><name lang="fi-FI">Suoritettu</name><name lang="da-DK">Færdiggjort</name><name lang="sk-SK">Dokončené</name>
                </option>
                <option>
                    <id>cancelled</id>
                    <name>Cancelled</name>
                    <name lang="de-DE">Abgebrochen</name>
                    <name lang="nl-NL">Geannuleerd</name>
                    <name lang="it-IT">Annullato</name><name lang="pt-PT">Cancelado</name><name lang="es-ES">Cancelado</name><name lang="sv-SE">Avbruten</name><name lang="nb-NO">Kansellert</name><name lang="pl-PL">Anulowane</name><name lang="cs-CZ">Zrušeno</name><name lang="sl-SL">Preklicano</name><name lang="hu-HU">Törölt</name><name lang="fi-FI">Peruutettu</name><name lang="da-DK">Annulleret</name><name lang="sk-SK">Zrušené</name>
                </option>
            </options>
        </input-field>
        <input-field type="single-select">
            <name>orderStateWithACancelledTransaction</name>
            <label>Order state with a cancelled transaction</label>
            <label lang="de-DE">Bestellstatus bei einer abgebrochenen Transaktion</label>
            <label lang="nl-NL">Bestelstatus bij een geannuleerde transactie</label>
            <label lang="it-IT">Stato dell'ordine per una transazione annullata</label><label lang="pt-PT">Estado da encomenda com uma transação cancelada</label><label lang="es-ES">Estado del pedido con transacción cancelada</label><label lang="sv-SE">Orderstatus med en avbruten transaktion</label><label lang="nb-NO">Ordrestatus med en kansellert transaksjon</label><label lang="pl-PL">Status zamówienia z anulowaną transakcją</label><label lang="cs-CZ">Stav objednávky se zrušenou transakcí</label><label lang="sl-SL">Stanje naročila s preklicano transakcijo</label><label lang="hu-HU">Megrendelés állapot törölt tranzakcióval</label><label lang="fi-FI">Tilaus, jossa on peruutettu maksutapahtuma</label><label lang="da-DK">Ordrestatus med en annulleret transaktion</label><label lang="sk-SK">Stav objednávky so zrušenou transakciou</label>
            <options>
                <option>
                    <id>skip</id>
                    <name>Skip this status</name>
                    <name lang="de-DE">nichts machen</name>
                    <name lang="nl-NL">Sla deze status over</name>
                    <name lang="it-IT">Salta questo stato</name><name lang="pt-PT">Ignorar este estado</name><name lang="es-ES">Omitir este estado</name><name lang="sv-SE">Hoppa över denna status</name><name lang="nb-NO">Hopp over denne statusen</name><name lang="pl-PL">Pomiń ten status</name><name lang="cs-CZ">Přeskočit tento stav</name><name lang="sl-SL">Preskoči to stanje</name><name lang="hu-HU">Ugorja át ezt az állapotot</name><name lang="fi-FI">Ohita tämä tila</name><name lang="da-DK">Spring denne status over</name><name lang="sk-SK">Preskočiť túto značku</name>
                </option>
                <option>
                    <id>open</id>
                    <name>Open</name>
                    <name lang="de-DE">Offen</name>
                    <name lang="nl-NL">Open</name>
                    <name lang="it-IT">Aperto</name><name lang="pt-PT">Aberto</name><name lang="es-ES">Abierto</name><name lang="sv-SE">Öppen</name><name lang="nb-NO">Åpen</name><name lang="pl-PL">Otwarte</name><name lang="cs-CZ">Otevřené</name><name lang="sl-SL">Odprto</name><name lang="hu-HU">Nyitott</name><name lang="fi-FI">Avoin</name><name lang="da-DK">Åben</name><name lang="sk-SK">Otvorené</name>
                </option>
                <option>
                    <id>in_progress</id>
                    <name>In progress</name>
                    <name lang="de-DE">In Bearbeitung</name>
                    <name lang="nl-NL">In uitvoering</name>
                    <name lang="it-IT">In corso</name><name lang="pt-PT">Em curso</name><name lang="es-ES">En curso</name><name lang="sv-SE">Pågår</name><name lang="nb-NO">Under behandling</name><name lang="pl-PL">W trakcie realizacji</name><name lang="cs-CZ">Probíhá</name><name lang="sl-SL">V teku</name><name lang="hu-HU">Folyamatban</name><name lang="fi-FI">Käynnissä</name><name lang="da-DK">I gang</name><name lang="sk-SK">V priebehu</name>
                </option>
                <option>
                    <id>completed</id>
                    <name>Completed</name>
                    <name lang="de-DE">Komplett</name>
                    <name lang="nl-NL">Voltooid</name>
                    <name lang="it-IT">Completato</name><name lang="pt-PT">Concluído</name><name lang="es-ES">Completado</name><name lang="sv-SE">Slutförd</name><name lang="nb-NO">Fullført</name><name lang="pl-PL">Zakończone</name><name lang="cs-CZ">Dokončeno</name><name lang="sl-SL">Končano</name><name lang="hu-HU">Befejezett</name><name lang="fi-FI">Suoritettu</name><name lang="da-DK">Færdiggjort</name><name lang="sk-SK">Dokončené</name>
                </option>
                <option>
                    <id>cancelled</id>
                    <name>Cancelled</name>
                    <name lang="de-DE">Abgebrochen</name>
                    <name lang="nl-NL">Geannuleerd</name>
                    <name lang="it-IT">Annullato</name><name lang="pt-PT">Cancelado</name><name lang="es-ES">Cancelado</name><name lang="sv-SE">Avbruten</name><name lang="nb-NO">Kansellert</name><name lang="pl-PL">Anulowane</name><name lang="cs-CZ">Zrušeno</name><name lang="sl-SL">Preklicano</name><name lang="hu-HU">Törölt</name><name lang="fi-FI">Peruutettu</name><name lang="da-DK">Annulleret</name><name lang="sk-SK">Zrušené</name>
                </option>
            </options>
        </input-field>
        <input-field type="single-select">
            <name>orderStateWithAAuthorizedTransaction</name>
            <label>Order state with a authorized transaction</label>
            <label lang="de-DE">Bestellstatus bei einer authorisierten Transaktion</label>
            <label lang="nl-NL">Bestelstatus bij een geautoriseerde transactie</label>
            <label lang="it-IT">Stato dell'ordine per una transazione autorizzata</label><label lang="pt-PT">Estado da encomenda com uma transação autorizada</label><label lang="es-ES">Estado del pedido con transacción autorizada</label><label lang="sv-SE">Orderstatus med en auktoriserad transaktion</label><label lang="nb-NO">Ordrestatus med en autorisert transaksjon</label><label lang="pl-PL">Status zamówienia z autoryzowaną transakcją</label><label lang="cs-CZ">Stav objednávky s autorizovanou transakcí</label><label lang="sl-SL">Stanje naročila z avtorizirano transakcijo</label><label lang="hu-HU">Megrendelés állapot engedélyezett tranzakcióval</label><label lang="fi-FI">Tilaus, jossa on valtuutettu maksutapahtuma</label><label lang="da-DK">Ordrestatus med en autoriseret transaktion</label><label lang="sk-SK">Stav objednávky s autorizovanou transakciou</label>
            <options>
                <option>
                    <id>skip</id>
                    <name>Skip this status</name>
                    <name lang="de-DE">nichts machen</name>
                    <name lang="nl-NL">Sla deze status over</name>
                    <name lang="it-IT">Salta questo stato</name><name lang="pt-PT">Ignorar este estado</name><name lang="es-ES">Omitir este estado</name><name lang="sv-SE">Hoppa över denna status</name><name lang="nb-NO">Hopp over denne statusen</name><name lang="pl-PL">Pomiń ten status</name><name lang="cs-CZ">Přeskočit tento status</name><name lang="sl-SL">Preskoči to stanje</name><name lang="hu-HU">Ugorja át ezt az állapotot</name><name lang="fi-FI">Ohita tämä tila</name><name lang="da-DK">Spring status over</name><name lang="sk-SK">Preskočiť túto značku</name>
                </option>
                <option>
                    <id>open</id>
                    <name>Open</name>
                    <name lang="de-DE">Offen</name>
                    <name lang="nl-NL">Open</name>
                    <name lang="it-IT">Aperto</name><name lang="pt-PT">Aberto</name><name lang="es-ES">Abierto</name><name lang="sv-SE">Öppen</name><name lang="nb-NO">Åpen</name><name lang="pl-PL">Otwarte</name><name lang="cs-CZ">Otevřené</name><name lang="sl-SL">Odprto</name><name lang="hu-HU">Nyitott</name><name lang="fi-FI">Avoin</name><name lang="da-DK">Åben</name><name lang="sk-SK">Otvorené</name>
                </option>
                <option>
                    <id>in_progress</id>
                    <name>In progress</name>
                    <name lang="de-DE">In Bearbeitung</name>
                    <name lang="nl-NL">In uitvoering</name>
                    <name lang="it-IT">In corso</name><name lang="pt-PT">Em curso</name><name lang="es-ES">En curso</name><name lang="sv-SE">Pågår</name><name lang="nb-NO">Under behandling</name><name lang="pl-PL">W trakcie realizacji</name><name lang="cs-CZ">Probíhá</name><name lang="sl-SL">V teku</name><name lang="hu-HU">Folyamatban</name><name lang="fi-FI">Käynnissä</name><name lang="da-DK">I gang</name><name lang="sk-SK">V priebehu</name>
                </option>
                <option>
                    <id>completed</id>
                    <name>Completed</name>
                    <name lang="de-DE">Komplett</name>
                    <name lang="nl-NL">Voltooid</name>
                    <name lang="it-IT">Completato</name><name lang="pt-PT">Concluído</name><name lang="es-ES">Completado</name><name lang="sv-SE">Slutförd</name><name lang="nb-NO">Fullført</name><name lang="pl-PL">Zakończone</name><name lang="cs-CZ">Dokončeno</name><name lang="sl-SL">Končano</name><name lang="hu-HU">Befejezett</name><name lang="fi-FI">Suoritettu</name><name lang="da-DK">Færdiggjort</name><name lang="sk-SK">Dokončené</name>
                </option>
                <option>
                    <id>cancelled</id>
                    <name>Cancelled</name>
                    <name lang="de-DE">Abgebrochen</name>
                    <name lang="nl-NL">Geannuleerd</name>
                    <name lang="it-IT">Annullato</name><name lang="pt-PT">Cancelado</name><name lang="es-ES">Cancelado</name><name lang="sv-SE">Avbruten</name><name lang="nb-NO">Kansellert</name><name lang="pl-PL">Anulowane</name><name lang="cs-CZ">Zrušeno</name><name lang="sl-SL">Preklicano</name><name lang="hu-HU">Törölt</name><name lang="fi-FI">Peruutettu</name><name lang="da-DK">Annulleret</name><name lang="sk-SK">Zrušené</name>
                </option>
            </options>
        </input-field>
        <input-field type="single-select">
            <name>orderStateWithAChargebackTransaction</name>
            <label>Order state with a charged back transaction</label>
            <label lang="de-DE">Bestellstatus bei einer zurückgebuchten Transaktion</label>
            <label lang="nl-NL">Bestelstatus bij een teruggevorderde transactie</label>
            <label lang="it-IT">Stato dell'ordine per una transazione rimborsata</label><label lang="pt-PT">Estado da encomenda com uma transação estornada</label><label lang="es-ES">Estado del pedido con cargo devuelto</label><label lang="sv-SE">Orderstatus med en återbetald transaktion</label><label lang="nb-NO">Ordrestatus med en chargeback transaksjon</label><label lang="pl-PL">Status zamówienia z obciążeniem zwrotnym</label><label lang="cs-CZ">Stav objednávky s transakcí zaúčtovanou zpětně</label><label lang="sl-SL">Stanje naročila z vračilom transakcije</label><label lang="hu-HU">Megrendelés állapot visszatérített tranzakcióval</label><label lang="fi-FI">Tilaus, jossa on takaisinveloitettu maksutapahtuma</label><label lang="da-DK">Ordrestatus med en tilbagebetalingstransaktion</label><label lang="sk-SK">Stav objednávky pri spätnom zaúčtovaní transakcie</label>
            <options>
                <option>
                    <id>skip</id>
                    <name>Skip this status</name>
                    <name lang="de-DE">nichts machen</name>
                    <name lang="nl-NL">Sla deze status over</name>
                    <name lang="it-IT">Salta questo stato</name><name lang="pt-PT">Ignorar este estado</name><name lang="es-ES">Omitir este estado</name><name lang="sv-SE">Hoppa över denna status</name><name lang="nb-NO">Hopp over denne statusen</name><name lang="pl-PL">Pomiń ten status</name><name lang="cs-CZ">Přeskočit tento status</name><name lang="sl-SL">Preskoči to stanje</name><name lang="hu-HU">Ugorja át ezt az állapotot</name><name lang="fi-FI">Ohita tämä tila</name><name lang="da-DK">Spring denne status over</name><name lang="sk-SK">Preskočiť tento stav</name>
                </option>
                <option>
                    <id>open</id>
                    <name>Open</name>
                    <name lang="de-DE">Offen</name>
                    <name lang="nl-NL">Open</name>
                    <name lang="it-IT">Aperto</name><name lang="pt-PT">Aberto</name><name lang="es-ES">Abierto</name><name lang="sv-SE">Öppen</name><name lang="nb-NO">Åpen</name><name lang="pl-PL">Otwarte</name><name lang="cs-CZ">Otevřeno</name><name lang="sl-SL">Odprto</name><name lang="hu-HU">Nyitott</name><name lang="fi-FI">Avoin</name><name lang="da-DK">Åben</name><name lang="sk-SK">Otvorené</name>
                </option>
                <option>
                    <id>in_progress</id>
                    <name>In progress</name>
                    <name lang="de-DE">In Bearbeitung</name>
                    <name lang="nl-NL">In uitvoering</name>
                    <name lang="it-IT">In corso</name><name lang="pt-PT">Em curso</name><name lang="es-ES">En curso</name><name lang="sv-SE">Pågår</name><name lang="nb-NO">Under behandling</name><name lang="pl-PL">W trakcie realizacji</name><name lang="cs-CZ">Probíhá</name><name lang="sl-SL">V teku</name><name lang="hu-HU">Folyamatban</name><name lang="fi-FI">Käynnissä</name><name lang="da-DK">I gang</name><name lang="sk-SK">V priebehu</name>
                </option>
                <option>
                    <id>completed</id>
                    <name>Completed</name>
                    <name lang="de-DE">Komplett</name>
                    <name lang="nl-NL">Voltooid</name>
                    <name lang="it-IT">Completato</name><name lang="pt-PT">Concluído</name><name lang="es-ES">Completado</name><name lang="sv-SE">Slutförd</name><name lang="nb-NO">Fullført</name><name lang="pl-PL">Zakończone</name><name lang="cs-CZ">Dokončeno</name><name lang="sl-SL">Končano</name><name lang="hu-HU">Befejezett</name><name lang="fi-FI">Suoritettu</name><name lang="da-DK">Færdiggjort</name><name lang="sk-SK">Dokončené</name>
                </option>
                <option>
                    <id>cancelled</id>
                    <name>Cancelled</name>
                    <name lang="de-DE">Abgebrochen</name>
                    <name lang="nl-NL">Geannuleerd</name>
                    <name lang="it-IT">Annullato</name><name lang="pt-PT">Cancelado</name><name lang="es-ES">Cancelado</name><name lang="sv-SE">Avbruten</name><name lang="nb-NO">Kansellert</name><name lang="pl-PL">Anulowane</name><name lang="cs-CZ">Zrušeno</name><name lang="sl-SL">Preklicano</name><name lang="hu-HU">Törölt</name><name lang="fi-FI">Peruutettu</name><name lang="da-DK">Annulleret</name><name lang="sk-SK">Zrušené</name>
                </option>
            </options>
        </input-field>
        <input-field type="single-select">
            <name>orderStateWithRefundTransaction</name>
            <label>Order state with a refund transaction</label>
            <label lang="de-DE">Bestellstatus bei einer zurückerstatteten Transaktion</label>
            <label lang="nl-NL">Bestelstatus bij een terugbetaalde transactie</label>
            <label lang="it-IT">Stato dell'ordine per una transazione di rimborso</label><label lang="pt-PT">Estado da encomenda com uma transação de reembolso</label><label lang="es-ES">Estado del pedido con reembolso</label><label lang="sv-SE">Orderstatus med en återbetalningstransaktion</label><label lang="nb-NO">Ordrestatus med en refusjonstransaksjon</label><label lang="pl-PL">Status zamówienia ze zwrotem</label><label lang="cs-CZ">Stav objednávky s vrácenou transakcí</label><label lang="sl-SL">Stanje naročila z vračilom transakcije</label><label lang="hu-HU">Megrendelés állapot visszatérített tranzakcióval</label><label lang="fi-FI">Tilaus, jossa on hyvitetty maksutapahtuma</label><label lang="da-DK">Ordrestatus med en refunderingstransaktion</label><label lang="sk-SK">Stav objednávky pri refundácii transakcie</label>
            <options>
                <option>
                    <id>skip</id>
                    <name>Skip this status</name>
                    <name lang="de-DE">nichts machen</name>
                    <name lang="nl-NL">Sla deze status over</name>
                    <name lang="it-IT">Salta questo stato</name><name lang="pt-PT">Ignorar este estado</name><name lang="es-ES">Omitir estado</name><name lang="sv-SE">Hoppa över denna status</name><name lang="nb-NO">Hopp over denne statusen</name><name lang="pl-PL">Pomiń ten status</name><name lang="cs-CZ">Přeskočit tento status</name><name lang="sl-SL">Preskoči to stanje</name><name lang="hu-HU">Ugorja át ezt az állapotot</name><name lang="fi-FI">Ohita tämä tila</name><name lang="da-DK">Spring denne status over</name><name lang="sk-SK">Preskočiť tento stav</name>
                </option>
                <option>
                    <id>open</id>
                    <name>Open</name>
                    <name lang="de-DE">Offen</name>
                    <name lang="nl-NL">Open</name>
                    <name lang="it-IT">Aperto</name><name lang="pt-PT">Aberto</name><name lang="es-ES">Abierto</name><name lang="sv-SE">Öppen</name><name lang="nb-NO">Åpen</name><name lang="pl-PL">Otwarte</name><name lang="cs-CZ">Otevřeno</name><name lang="sl-SL">Odprto</name><name lang="hu-HU">Nyitott</name><name lang="fi-FI">Avoin</name><name lang="da-DK">Åben</name><name lang="sk-SK">Otvorené</name>
                </option>
                <option>
                    <id>in_progress</id>
                    <name>In progress</name>
                    <name lang="de-DE">In Bearbeitung</name>
                    <name lang="nl-NL">In uitvoering</name>
                    <name lang="it-IT">In corso</name><name lang="pt-PT">Em curso</name><name lang="es-ES">En curso</name><name lang="sv-SE">Pågår</name><name lang="nb-NO">Under behandling</name><name lang="pl-PL">W trakcie realizacji</name><name lang="cs-CZ">Probíhá</name><name lang="sl-SL">V teku</name><name lang="hu-HU">Folyamatban</name><name lang="fi-FI">Käynnissä</name><name lang="da-DK">I gang</name><name lang="sk-SK">V priebehu</name>
                </option>
                <option>
                    <id>completed</id>
                    <name>Completed</name>
                    <name lang="de-DE">Komplett</name>
                    <name lang="nl-NL">Voltooid</name>
                    <name lang="it-IT">Completato</name><name lang="pt-PT">Concluído</name><name lang="es-ES">Completado</name><name lang="sv-SE">Slutförd</name><name lang="nb-NO">Fullført</name><name lang="pl-PL">Zakończone</name><name lang="cs-CZ">Dokončeno</name><name lang="sl-SL">Končano</name><name lang="hu-HU">Befejezett</name><name lang="fi-FI">Suoritettu</name><name lang="da-DK">Færdiggjort</name><name lang="sk-SK">Dokončené</name>
                </option>
                <option>
                    <id>cancelled</id>
                    <name>Cancelled</name>
                    <name lang="de-DE">Abgebrochen</name>
                    <name lang="nl-NL">Geannuleerd</name>
                    <name lang="it-IT">Annullato</name><name lang="pt-PT">Cancelado</name><name lang="es-ES">Cancelado</name><name lang="sv-SE">Avbruten</name><name lang="nb-NO">Kansellert</name><name lang="pl-PL">Anulowane</name><name lang="cs-CZ">Zrušeno</name><name lang="sl-SL">Preklicano</name><name lang="hu-HU">Törölt</name><name lang="fi-FI">Peruutettu</name><name lang="da-DK">Annulleret</name><name lang="sk-SK">Zrušené</name>
                </option>
            </options>
        </input-field>
        <input-field type="single-select">
            <name>orderStateWithPartialRefundTransaction</name>
            <label>Order state with a partial refund transaction</label>
            <label lang="de-DE">Bestellstatus bei einer teilweise erstatteten Transaktion</label>
            <label lang="nl-NL">Bestelstatus bij een gedeeltelijk terugbetaalde transactie</label>
            <label lang="it-IT">Stato dell'ordine per una transazione di rimborso parziale</label><label lang="pt-PT">Estado da encomenda com uma transação de reembolso parcial</label><label lang="es-ES">Estado del pedido con reembolso parcial</label><label lang="sv-SE">Orderstatus med en delvis återbetald transaktion</label><label lang="nb-NO">Ordrestatus med en delvis refusjonstransaksjon</label><label lang="pl-PL">Status zamówienia z częściowym zwrotem</label><label lang="cs-CZ">Stav objednávky s částečným vrácením peněz</label><label lang="sl-SL">Stanje naročila z delnim vračilom</label><label lang="hu-HU">Megrendelés állapot részleges visszatérítés tranzakcióval</label><label lang="fi-FI">Tilaus, jossa on osittain hyvitetty maksutapahtuma</label><label lang="da-DK">Ordrestatus med en delvis refunderingstransaktion</label><label lang="sk-SK">Stav objednávky pri čiastočnom vrátení platby</label>
            <options>
                <option>
                    <id>skip</id>
                    <name>Skip this status</name>
                    <name lang="de-DE">nichts machen</name>
                    <name lang="nl-NL">Sla deze status over</name>
                    <name lang="it-IT">Salta questo stato</name><name lang="pt-PT">Ignorar este estado</name><name lang="es-ES">Omitir estado</name><name lang="sv-SE">Hoppa över denna status</name><name lang="nb-NO">Hopp over denne statusen</name><name lang="pl-PL">Pomiń ten status</name><name lang="cs-CZ">Přeskočit tento status</name><name lang="sl-SL">Preskoči to stanje</name><name lang="hu-HU">Ugorja át ezt az állapotot</name><name lang="fi-FI">Ohita tämä tila</name><name lang="da-DK">Spring denne status over</name><name lang="sk-SK">Preskočiť tento stav</name>
                </option>
                <option>
                    <id>open</id>
                    <name>Open</name>
                    <name lang="de-DE">Offen</name>
                    <name lang="nl-NL">Open</name>
                    <name lang="it-IT">Aperto</name><name lang="pt-PT">Aberto</name><name lang="es-ES">Abierto</name><name lang="sv-SE">Öppen</name><name lang="nb-NO">Åpen</name><name lang="pl-PL">Otwarte</name><name lang="cs-CZ">Otevřené</name><name lang="sl-SL">Odprto</name><name lang="hu-HU">Nyitott</name><name lang="fi-FI">Avoin</name><name lang="da-DK">Åben</name><name lang="sk-SK">Otvorené</name>
                </option>
                <option>
                    <id>in_progress</id>
                    <name>In progress</name>
                    <name lang="de-DE">In Bearbeitung</name>
                    <name lang="nl-NL">In uitvoering</name>
                    <name lang="it-IT">In corso</name><name lang="pt-PT">Em curso</name><name lang="es-ES">En curso</name><name lang="sv-SE">Pågår</name><name lang="nb-NO">Under behandling</name><name lang="pl-PL">W trakcie realizacji</name><name lang="cs-CZ">Probíhá</name><name lang="sl-SL">V teku</name><name lang="hu-HU">Folyamatban</name><name lang="fi-FI">Käynnissä</name><name lang="da-DK">I gang</name><name lang="sk-SK">V priebehu</name>
                </option>
                <option>
                    <id>completed</id>
                    <name>Completed</name>
                    <name lang="de-DE">Komplett</name>
                    <name lang="nl-NL">Voltooid</name>
                    <name lang="it-IT">Completato</name><name lang="pt-PT">Concluído</name><name lang="es-ES">Completado</name><name lang="sv-SE">Slutförd</name><name lang="nb-NO">Fullført</name><name lang="pl-PL">Zakończone</name><name lang="cs-CZ">Dokončeno</name><name lang="sl-SL">Končano</name><name lang="hu-HU">Befejezett</name><name lang="fi-FI">Suoritettu</name><name lang="da-DK">Færdiggjort</name><name lang="sk-SK">Dokončené</name>
                </option>
                <option>
                    <id>cancelled</id>
                    <name>Cancelled</name>
                    <name lang="de-DE">Abgebrochen</name>
                    <name lang="nl-NL">Geannuleerd</name>
                    <name lang="it-IT">Annullato</name><name lang="pt-PT">Cancelado</name><name lang="es-ES">Cancelado</name><name lang="sv-SE">Avbruten</name><name lang="nb-NO">Kansellert</name><name lang="pl-PL">Anulowane</name><name lang="cs-CZ">Zrušeno</name><name lang="sl-SL">Preklicano</name><name lang="hu-HU">Törölt</name><name lang="fi-FI">Peruutettu</name><name lang="da-DK">Annulleret</name><name lang="sk-SK">Zrušené</name>
                </option>
            </options>
        </input-field>
        <component name="mollie-pluginconfig-element-orderstate-select">
            <name>orderStateFinalState</name>
            <entity>state_machine_state</entity>
            <label>Final order state</label>
            <label lang="de-DE">Finaler Bestellstatus</label>
            <label lang="nl-NL">Definitieve Bestelstatus</label>
            <label lang="it-IT">Stato finale dell'ordine</label><label lang="pt-PT">Estado final da encomenda</label><label lang="es-ES">Estado final del pedido</label><label lang="sv-SE">Slutlig beställningsstatus</label><label lang="nb-NO">Endelig ordrestatus</label><label lang="pl-PL">Końcowy stan zamówienia</label><label lang="cs-CZ">Konečný stav objednávky</label><label lang="sl-SL">Končno stanje naročila</label><label lang="hu-HU">Végső megrendelési állapot</label><label lang="fi-FI">Lopullinen tilauksen tila</label><label lang="da-DK">Endelig ordretilstand</label><label lang="sk-SK">Konečný stav objednávky</label>
            <helpText>If enabled, the plugin will not transition to a new order state, if the final state is already set in the order. Use this feature in combination with plugins and systems if their workflows do not match the one from Mollie.</helpText>
            <helpText lang="de-DE">Wenn aktiv, wechselt das Plugin nicht in einen neuen Bestellstatus, wenn der finale Status bereits in der Bestellung verwendet wird. Verwenden Sie diese Funktion in Kombination mit Plugins und -Systemen, wenn deren Workflows nicht mit denen von Mollie übereinstimmen.</helpText>
            <helpText lang="nl-NL">Indien ingeschakeld, gaat de plug-in niet over naar een nieuwe bestelstatus, als de definitieve status al in de bestelling is ingesteld. Gebruik deze functie in combinatie met plug-ins en -systemen als hun workflows niet overeenkomen met die van Mollie.</helpText>
            <helpText lang="it-IT">Se abilitato, il plugin non passerà a un nuovo stato dell'ordine se lo stato finale è già impostato nell'ordine. Usa questa funzione in combinazione con plugin e sistemi se i loro flussi di lavoro non corrispondono a quello di Mollie.</helpText><helpText lang="pt-PT">Se ativado, o plugin não fará a transição para um novo estado da encomenda, caso estado final já estiver definido na encomenda. Utilize esta funcionalidade em combinação com plugins e sistemas se os seus fluxos de trabalho não corresponderem ao da Mollie.</helpText><helpText lang="es-ES">Si se habilita, el plugin no cambiará el estado de pedido, si el estado final ya está establecido en el pedido. Usa esta función en combinación con plugins y sistemas si los flujos de trabajo no coinciden con el de Mollie.</helpText><helpText lang="sv-SE">Om aktiverad kommer pluginet inte att övergå till en ny beställningsstatus, om den slutliga statusen redan är inställd i beställningen. Använd denna funktion i kombination med plugin och system om deras arbetsflöden inte matchar Mollies.</helpText><helpText lang="nb-NO">Hvis aktivert, vil pluginen ikke gå over til en ny ordrestatus hvis den endelige statusen allerede er angitt i ordren. Bruk denne funksjonen i kombinasjon med plugins og systemer hvis arbeidsflytene deres ikke matcher den fra Mollie.</helpText><helpText lang="pl-PL">Jeśli ta opcja jest włączona, wtyczka nie przejdzie do nowego statusu zamówienia, jeśli w zamówieniu został już ustawiony status końcowy. Używaj tej funkcji w połączeniu z wtyczkami i systemami, jeśli ich procesy nie są zgodne procesami Mollie.</helpText><helpText lang="cs-CZ">Pokud je tato možnost povolena, plugin nepřejde do nového stavu objednávky, pokud je konečný stav již nastaven v objednávce. Použijte tuto funkci v kombinaci s pluginy a systémy, pokud jejich pracovní postupy neodpovídají těm, které používá Mollie.</helpText><helpText lang="sl-SL">Če je omogočeno, vtičnik ne bo prešel v novo stanje naročila, če je končno stanje že nastavljeno v naročilu. Uporabite to funkcijo v kombinaciji z vtičniki in sistemi, če njihovi delovni postopki ne ustrezajo tistemu iz Mollie.</helpText><helpText lang="hu-HU">Ha engedélyezve, a plugin nem vált új megrendelési állapotra, ha a végső állapot már be van állítva a megrendelésnél. Használja ezt a funkciót együtt pluginokkal és rendszerekkel, ha a munkafolyamataik nem egyeznek meg a Mollie munkafolyamatával.</helpText><helpText lang="fi-FI">Jos käytössä, laajennus ei siirry uuteen tilauksen tilaan, jos lopullinen tila on jo asetettu tilauksessa. Käytä tätä ominaisuutta yhdessä laajennusten ja järjestelmien kanssa, jos niiden työnkulku ei vastaa Mollien työnkulkua.</helpText><helpText lang="da-DK">Hvis aktiveret, vil plugin'et ikke overgå til en ny ordretilstand, hvis den endelige tilstand allerede er indstillet i ordren. Brug denne funktion i kombination med plugins og systemer, hvis deres arbejdsgange ikke matcher den, der er fra Mollie.</helpText><helpText lang="sk-SK">Ak je táto možnosť povolená, doplnok neprenesie objednávku do nového stavu, ak je v nej už nastavený konečný stav. Túto funkciu použite spolu s pluginmi a systémami, ktorých pracovné postupy sa nezhodujú s tými od Mollie.</helpText>
        </component>

    </card>

    <card>
        <title>Subscriptions</title>
        <title lang="de-DE">Abonnements</title>
        <title lang="nl-NL">Abonnementen</title>
        <title lang="it-IT">Abbonamenti</title><title lang="pt-PT">Subscrições</title><title lang="es-ES">Suscripciones</title><title lang="sv-SE">Prenumerationer</title><title lang="nb-NO">Abonnementer</title><title lang="pl-PL">Subskrypcje</title><title lang="cs-CZ">Předplatná</title><title lang="sl-SL">Naročnine</title><title lang="hu-HU">Előfizetések</title><title lang="fi-FI">Tilaukset</title><title lang="da-DK">Abonnementer</title><title lang="sk-SK">Predplatné</title>
        <input-field type="bool">
            <name>subscriptionsEnabled</name>
            <defaultValue>true</defaultValue>
            <label>Enable Mollie subscriptions</label>
            <label lang="de-DE">Mollie Abonnements aktivieren</label>
            <label lang="nl-NL">Mollie abonnementen activeren</label>
            <label lang="it-IT">Abilita abbonamenti Mollie</label><label lang="pt-PT">Ativar as subscrições da Mollie</label><label lang="es-ES">Habilitar suscripciones de Mollie</label><label lang="sv-SE">Aktivera Mollie prenumerationer</label><label lang="nb-NO">Aktiver Mollie abonnementer</label><label lang="pl-PL">Włącz subskrypcje Mollie</label><label lang="cs-CZ">Povolit předplatná Mollie</label><label lang="sl-SL">Omogoči Mollie naročnine</label><label lang="hu-HU">Mollie előfizetések engedélyezése</label><label lang="fi-FI">Ota käyttöön Mollie-tilaukset</label><label lang="da-DK">Aktiver Mollie abonnementer</label><label lang="sk-SK">Aktivovať predplatné Mollie</label>
            <helpText>Enables or disables the full subscription functionality. Please reload the administration after changing this setting.</helpText>
            <helpText lang="de-DE">Aktiviert oder deaktiviert die vollständige Abonnementfunktion. Bitte laden Sie die Administration neu, nachdem Sie diese Einstellung geändert haben.</helpText>
            <helpText lang="nl-NL">Schakelt de volledige abonnementsfunctionaliteit in of uit. Herlaad de administratie na het wijzigen van deze instelling.</helpText>
            <helpText lang="it-IT">Abilita o disabilita la funzionalità completa degli abbonamenti. Ricarica l'amministrazione dopo aver modificato questa impostazione.</helpText><helpText lang="pt-PT">Ativa ou desactiva a funcionalidade de subscrição completa. Por favor, recarregue a administração depois de alterar esta definição.</helpText><helpText lang="es-ES">Activa o desactiva la funcionalidad completa de la suscripción. Por favor, recarga la página después de cambiar esta configuración.</helpText><helpText lang="sv-SE">Aktiverar eller inaktiverar den fullständiga prenumerationsfunktionaliteten. Ladda om administrationen efter att ha ändrat denna inställning.</helpText><helpText lang="nb-NO">Aktiverer eller deaktiverer full abonnementsfunksjonalitet. Vennligst last inn administrasjonen på nytt etter å ha endret denne innstillingen.</helpText><helpText lang="pl-PL">Włącza lub wyłącza pełną funkcjonalność subskrypcji. Po zmianie tego ustawienia odśwież panel administracyjny.</helpText><helpText lang="cs-CZ">Povolí nebo zakáže plnou funkčnost předplatného. Po změně tohoto nastavení prosím znovu načtěte administraci.</helpText><helpText lang="sl-SL">Omogoča ali onemogoča celotno funkcionalnost naročnin. Po spremembi te nastavitve znova naložite upravljanje.</helpText><helpText lang="hu-HU">Engedélyezi vagy letiltja a teljes előfizetési funkciót. Kérjük, töltse újra az adminisztrációt a beállítás megváltoztatása után.</helpText><helpText lang="fi-FI">Otaa käyttöön tai poistaa käytöstä kaikki tilaustoiminnot. Uudelleen lataa hallinta tämän asetuksen muuttamisen jälkeen.</helpText><helpText lang="da-DK">Aktiverer eller deaktiverer den fulde abonnementsfunktionalitet. Venligst genindlæs administrationen efter ændring af denne indstilling.</helpText><helpText lang="sk-SK">Povoľuje alebo zakazuje plnú funkčnosť predplatného. Po zmene tohto nastavenia prosím znovu načítajte administráciu.</helpText>
        </input-field>
        <input-field type="bool">
            <name>subscriptionsShowIndicator</name>
            <defaultValue>true</defaultValue>
            <label>Show subscription indicator</label>
            <label lang="de-DE">Abonnementetikett auf Produktseite anzeigen</label>
            <label lang="nl-NL">Label Abonnementen weergeven op productpagina</label>
            <label lang="it-IT">Mostra indicatore di abbonamento</label><label lang="pt-PT">Mostrar indicador de subscrição</label><label lang="es-ES">Mostrar indicador de suscripción</label><label lang="sv-SE">Visa prenumerationsindikator</label><label lang="nb-NO">Vis abonnementindikator</label><label lang="pl-PL">Pokaż wskaźnik subskrypcji</label><label lang="cs-CZ">Zobrazit indikátor předplatného</label><label lang="sl-SL">Prikaži kazalnik naročnine</label><label lang="hu-HU">Előfizetés jelölő mutatása</label><label lang="fi-FI">Näytä tilausindikaattori</label><label lang="da-DK">Vis abonnementsindikator</label><label lang="sk-SK">Zobraziť indikátor predplatného</label>
            <helpText>Shows a subscription indicator on the product detail page of a subscription product.</helpText>
            <helpText lang="de-DE">Zeigt einen Abonnementhinweis auf der Produktdetailseite an.</helpText>
            <helpText lang="nl-NL">Toont een abonnement indicator op de productpagina van een abonnement product.</helpText>
            <helpText lang="it-IT">Mostra un indicatore di abbonamento nella pagina dei dettagli del prodotto di un prodotto in abbonamento.</helpText><helpText lang="pt-PT">Mostra um indicador de subscrição na página de detalhes de um produto de subscrição.</helpText><helpText lang="es-ES">Muestra un indicador visual de suscripción en la descripción del artículo de suscripción.</helpText><helpText lang="sv-SE">Visar en prenumerationsindikator på produktens detaljsida för en prenumerationsprodukt.</helpText><helpText lang="nb-NO">Viser en abonnementindikator på produktdetaljsiden for et abonnementprodukt.</helpText><helpText lang="pl-PL">Wyświetla wskaźnik subskrypcji na stronie szczegółów produktu subskrypcyjnego.</helpText><helpText lang="cs-CZ">Zobrazí indikátor předplatného na stránce detailu produktu s předplatným.</helpText><helpText lang="sl-SL">Prikaže kazalnik naročnine na strani podrobnosti izdelka naročnine.</helpText><helpText lang="hu-HU">Az előfizetési termék részletező oldalán jelzi az előfizetési lehetőséget.</helpText><helpText lang="fi-FI">Näyttää tilausindikaattorin tilaustuotteen tuotetietosivulla.</helpText><helpText lang="da-DK">Viser en abonnementsindikator på produktdetaljesiden for et abonnementsprodukt.</helpText><helpText lang="sk-SK">Zobrazuje indikátor predplatného na stránke s detailom produktu určeného na predplatné.</helpText>
        </input-field>
        <input-field type="bool">
            <name>subscriptionsAllowAddressEditing</name>
            <defaultValue>false</defaultValue>
            <label>Allow customers to edit billing and shipping addresses for running subscriptions</label>
            <label lang="de-DE">Kunden erlauben die Rechnungs- und Lieferadresse zu bearbeiten</label>
            <label lang="nl-NL">Klanten toelaten om factuur- en verzendadressen voor lopende abonnementen te bewerken</label>
            <label lang="it-IT">Consenti ai clienti di modificare gli indirizzi di fatturazione e spedizione per gli abbonamenti in corso</label><label lang="pt-PT">Permitir que os clientes editem endereços de faturação e de envio para subscrições em curso</label><label lang="es-ES">Permite a los clientes editar la dirección de facturación y envío para suscripciones en curso</label><label lang="sv-SE">Tillåt kunder att redigera fakturerings- och fraktadresser för pågående prenumerationer</label><label lang="nb-NO">Tillat kunder å redigere fakturerings- og fraktadresser for aktive abonnementer</label><label lang="pl-PL">Pozwól klientom na edytowanie adresów do fakturowania i wysyłki dla aktywnych subskrypcji</label><label lang="cs-CZ">Povolit zákazníkům upravit fakturační a doručovací adresy u aktivních předplatných</label><label lang="sl-SL">Dovoli strankam, da uredijo naslove za obračun in dostavo za aktivne naročnine</label><label lang="hu-HU">Engedje meg az ügyfeleknek, hogy szerkeszthessék a |számlázási és szállítási címeket aktív előfizetésekhez</label><label lang="fi-FI">Salli asiakkaiden muokata käynnissä olevien tilausten laskutus- ja toimitusosoitteita</label><label lang="da-DK">Tillad kunder at redigere fakturerings- og leveringsadresser for aktive abonnementer</label><label lang="sk-SK">Povoliť zákazníkom upravovať fakturačné a dodacie adresy pre aktívne predplatné</label>
            <helpText>If enabled, customers are allowed to edit their billing and shipping addresses in the shop. Please consider that no new shipping costs will be calculated for modified addresses. Countries are not allowed to be edited.</helpText>
            <helpText lang="de-DE">Wenn aktiv, dürfen Kunden ihre Rechnungs- und Lieferadressen im Shop bearbeiten. Bitte beachten Sie, dass für geänderte Adressen keine neuen Versandkosten berechnet werden. Länder dürfen nicht bearbeitet werden.</helpText>
            <helpText lang="nl-NL">Indien ingeschakeld, mogen klanten hun factuur- en verzendadres in de shop bewerken. Houd er rekening mee dat er geen nieuwe verzendkosten worden berekend voor gewijzigde adressen. Landen mogen niet worden bewerkt.</helpText>
            <helpText lang="it-IT">Se abilitato, i clienti possono modificare i propri indirizzi di fatturazione e spedizione nel negozio. Si prega di considerare che per gli indirizzi modificati non verranno calcolati nuovi costi di spedizione. Non è consentito modificare i paesi.</helpText><helpText lang="pt-PT">Se ativado, os clientes podem editar os seus endereços de faturação e de envio na loja. Tenha em conta que não serão calculados novos custos de envio para endereços alterados. Os países não podem ser editados.</helpText><helpText lang="es-ES">Si se habilita, permite que los clientes editen su dirección de facturación y envío en la tienda. Por favor, ten en cuenta que no se calcularán los nuevos gastos de envío para la dirección modificada. No es posible editar el país.</helpText><helpText lang="sv-SE">Om aktiverad, får kunder redigera sina fakturerings- och fraktadresser i butiken. Tänk på att inga nya fraktkostnader kommer att beräknas för ändrade adresser. Länder får inte redigeras.</helpText><helpText lang="nb-NO">Hvis aktivert, kan kundene redigere sine fakturerings- og fraktadresser i butikken. Vær oppmerksom på at ingen nye fraktkostnader vil bli beregnet for endre adresser. Land kan ikke redigeres.</helpText><helpText lang="pl-PL">Jeżeli ta opcja jest włączona, klienci mogą edytować swoje adresy fakturowania i wysyłki w sklepie. Proszę pamiętać, że nowe koszty wysyłki dla zmodyfikowanych adresów nie będą obliczane. Nie jest dozwolone edytowanie krajów.</helpText><helpText lang="cs-CZ">Pokud je tato možnost povolena, zákazníci mohou upravit své fakturační a doručovací adresy v obchodě. Vezměte prosím na vědomí, že pro upravené adresy nebudou přepočítány nové náklady na dopravu. Země nelze upravit.</helpText><helpText lang="sl-SL">Če je omogočeno, strankam ni dovoljeno, da urejajo naslove za obračun in dostavo v trgovini. Upoštevajte, da novi stroški dostave ne bodo izračunani za spremenjene naslove. Držav ni dovoljeno urejati.</helpText><helpText lang="hu-HU">Ha engedélyezve van, lehetővé teszi az ügyfelek számára, hogy módosítsák számlázási és szállítási címüket az üzletben. Felhívjuk figyelmét, hogy a megváltozott címre nem számolunk új szállítási költséget. Az ország szerkesztése nem lehetséges.</helpText><helpText lang="fi-FI">Jos käytössä, asiakkaat voivat muokata laskutus- ja toimitusosoitteitaan kaupassa. Huomaa, että muutetuille osoitteille ei lasketa uusia toimituskustannuksia. Maata ei voi muuttaa.</helpText><helpText lang="da-DK">Hvis aktiveret, kan kunder redigere deres fakturerings- og leveringsadresser i butikken. Bemærk venligst, at der ikke vil blive beregnet nye forsendelsesomkostninger for ændrede adresser. Lande må ikke redigeres.</helpText><helpText lang="sk-SK">Ak je táto možnosť povolená, zákazníci môžu v obchode upravovať svoju fakturačnú a doručovaciu adresu. Majte na pamäti, že pre zmenené adresy sa neprepočítajú nové náklady na dopravu. Úprava krajiny nie je povolená.</helpText>
        </input-field>
        <input-field type="bool">
            <name>subscriptionsAllowPauseResume</name>
            <defaultValue>false</defaultValue>
            <label>Allow customers to pause and resume running subscriptions</label>
            <label lang="de-DE">Kunden erlauben laufende Abonnements zu pausieren und fortzusetzen</label>
            <label lang="nl-NL">Laat klanten lopende abonnementen onderbreken en hervatten</label>
            <label lang="it-IT">Consenti ai clienti di mettere in pausa e riprendere gli abbonamenti in corso</label><label lang="pt-PT">Permitir que os clientes coloquem em pausa e retomem as subscrições em curso</label><label lang="es-ES">Permite que los clientes pausen y reanuden sus suscripciones en curso</label><label lang="sv-SE">Tillåt kunder att pausa och återuppta pågående prenumerationer</label><label lang="nb-NO">Tillat kunder å pause og gjenoppta aktive abonnementer</label><label lang="pl-PL">Pozwól klientom na wstrzymywanie i wznawianie aktywnych subskrypcji</label><label lang="cs-CZ">Povolit zákazníkům pozastavit a obnovit aktivní předplatná</label><label lang="sl-SL">Dovoli strankam, da prekličejo in ponovno aktivirajo aktivne naročnine</label><label lang="hu-HU">Engedje meg az ügyfeleknek, hogy szüneteltessék és folytathassák az aktív előfizetéseket</label><label lang="fi-FI">Salli asiakkaiden keskeyttää ja jatkaa käynnissä olevia tilauksia</label><label lang="da-DK">Tillad kunder at sætte aktive abonnementer på pause og genoptage dem</label><label lang="sk-SK">Povoliť zákazníkom pozastaviť a obnoviť aktívne predplatné</label>
            <helpText>If enabled, customers are allowed to pause and also resume their subscriptions in their account.</helpText>
            <helpText lang="de-DE">Wenn diese Option aktiviert ist, können Kunden ihre Abonnements in ihrem Konto pausieren und auch fortsetzen.</helpText>
            <helpText lang="nl-NL">Indien ingeschakeld, mogen klanten hun abonnementen onderbreken en hervatten in hun account.</helpText>
            <helpText lang="it-IT">Se abilitato, i clienti possono mettere in pausa e riprendere i loro abbonamenti nel loro account.</helpText><helpText lang="pt-PT">Se ativado, os clientes podem colocar em pausa e retomar as suas subscrições na sua conta.</helpText><helpText lang="es-ES">Si se habilita, permite que los clientes pausen y reanuden las suscripciones en su cuenta.</helpText><helpText lang="sv-SE">Om aktiverad, får kunder pausa och också återuppta sina prenumerationer i sitt konto.</helpText><helpText lang="nb-NO">Hvis aktivert, kan kundene pause og gjenoppta abonnementene sine i kontoen sin.</helpText><helpText lang="pl-PL">Jeśli ta opcja jest włączona, klienci mogą wstrzymać i wznawiać posiadane subskrypcje.</helpText><helpText lang="cs-CZ">Pokud je tato možnost povolena, zákazníci mohou pozastavit a také obnovit svá předplatná ve svém účtu.</helpText><helpText lang="sl-SL">Če je omogočeno, strankam ni dovoljeno, da prekličejo in ponovno aktivirajo svoje naročnine v njihovem računu.</helpText><helpText lang="hu-HU">Ha engedélyezve van, az ügyfelek szüneteltethetik és újra folytathatják az előfizetéseiket a fiókjukban.</helpText><helpText lang="fi-FI">Jos käytössä, asiakkaat voivat keskeyttää ja myös jatkaa tilauksiaan tilillään.</helpText><helpText lang="da-DK">Hvis aktiveret, kan kunderne sætte deres abonnementer på pause og også genoptage dem i deres konto.</helpText><helpText lang="sk-SK">Ak je povolené, zákazníci môžu pozastaviť a tiež obnoviť svoje predplatné vo svojom účte.</helpText>
        </input-field>
        <input-field type="bool">
            <name>subscriptionsAllowSkip</name>
            <defaultValue>false</defaultValue>
            <label>Allow customers to skip an upcoming subscription renewal</label>
            <label lang="de-DE">Kunden erlauben eine anstehende Abonnementverlängerung zu überspringen</label>
            <label lang="nl-NL">Sta klanten toe een lopende abonnementsverlenging over te slaan</label>
            <label lang="it-IT">Consenti ai clienti di saltare un prossimo rinnovo dell'abbonamento</label><label lang="pt-PT">Permitir que os clientes saltem uma próxima renovação de subscrição</label><label lang="es-ES">Permite que los clientes pospongan la próxima renovación de la suscripción</label><label lang="sv-SE">Tillåt kunder att hoppa över en kommande prenumerationsförnyelse</label><label lang="nb-NO">Tillat kunder å hoppe over en kommende fornyelse av abonnement</label><label lang="pl-PL">Pozwól klientom pominąć nadchodzące odnowienie subskrypcji</label><label lang="cs-CZ">Povolit zákazníkům přeskočit nadcházející obnovení předplatného</label><label lang="sl-SL">Dovoli strankam, da preskočijo prihajajoče obnovitve naročnine</label><label lang="hu-HU">Engedje meg az ügyfeleknek, hogy kihagyják a közelgő előfizetés megújítását</label><label lang="fi-FI">Salli asiakkaiden ohittaa tuleva tilauksen uusiminen</label><label lang="da-DK">Tillad kunder at springe en kommende fornyelse af abonnementet over</label><label lang="sk-SK">Povoliť zákazníkom preskočiť nadchádzajúce obnovenie predplatného</label>
            <helpText>If enabled, customers are allowed to skip an upcoming renewal of a running subscription. This also takes the last notice period into account.</helpText>
            <helpText lang="de-DE">Wenn diese Option aktiviert ist, können Kunden eine bevorstehende Verlängerung eines laufenden Abonnements überspringen. Dabei wird auch die letzte Kündigungsfrist berücksichtigt.</helpText>
            <helpText lang="nl-NL">Indien ingeschakeld, mogen klanten een aanstaande verlenging van een lopend abonnement overslaan. Hierbij wordt ook rekening gehouden met de laatste opzegtermijn.</helpText>
            <helpText lang="it-IT">Se abilitato, i clienti possono saltare un prossimo rinnovo di un abbonamento in corso. Viene preso in considerazione anche l'ultimo periodo di preavviso.</helpText><helpText lang="pt-PT">Se ativado, os clientes podem saltar uma próxima renovação de uma subscrição em curso. Isto também tem em conta o último período de pré-aviso.</helpText><helpText lang="es-ES">Si se habilita, permite que los clientes pospongan la próxima renovación de la suscripción en curso teniendo en cuenta el período de aviso.</helpText><helpText lang="sv-SE">Om aktiverad får kunder hoppa över en kommande förnyelse av en pågående prenumeration. Detta tar även hänsyn till den sista uppsägningstiden.</helpText><helpText lang="nb-NO">Hvis aktivert, kan kundene hoppe over en kommende fornyelse av et aktivt abonnement. Dette tar også hensyn til den siste påminnelseperioden.</helpText><helpText lang="pl-PL">Jeśli ta opcja jest włączona, klienci mogą pominąć nadchodzące odnowienie aktywnej subskrypcji, z uwzględnieniem ostatniego okres wypowiedzenia.</helpText><helpText lang="cs-CZ">Pokud je tato možnost povolena, zákazníci mohou přeskočit nadcházející obnovu aktivního předplatného. Tento proces také zohledňuje poslední výpovědní lhůtu.</helpText><helpText lang="sl-SL">Če je omogočeno, strankam ni dovoljeno, da preskočijo prihajajoče obnovitve aktivne naročnine. To upošteva tudi zadnji odpovedni rok.</helpText><helpText lang="hu-HU">Ha engedélyezve van, az ügyfelek kihagyhatják a közelgő megújítását egy aktív előfizetésnek. Ez figyelembe veszi az utolsó értesítési időszakot is.</helpText><helpText lang="fi-FI">Jos käytössä, asiakkaat voivat ohittaa käynnissä olevan tilauksen tulevan uusimisen. Tässä otetaan huomioon myös viimeinen irtisanomisaika.</helpText><helpText lang="da-DK">Hvis aktiveret, kan kunderne springe en kommende fornyelse af et aktivt abonnement over. Dette tager også den sidste varslingsperiode i betragtning.</helpText><helpText lang="sk-SK">Ak je povolené, zákazníci môžu preskočiť nadchádzajúce obnovenie aktívneho predplatného. To tiež zohľadňuje posledné obdobie oznámenia.</helpText>
        </input-field>
        <input-field type="bool">
            <name>subscriptionSkipRenewalsOnFailedPayments</name>
            <defaultValue>false</defaultValue>
            <label>Skip subscription renewal if payment fails</label>
            <label lang="de-DE">Abonnementverlängerung überspringen, wenn die Zahlung fehlschlägt</label>
            <label lang="nl-NL">Abonnementverlenging overslaan als de betaling mislukt</label>
            <label lang="it-IT">Salta il rinnovo dell'abbonamento se il pagamento non riesce</label><label lang="pt-PT">Ignorar a renovação da subscrição se o pagamento falhar</label><label lang="es-ES">Posponer renovación de suscripción si el pago es rechazado</label><label lang="sv-SE">Hoppa över prenumerationsförnyelse om betalningen misslyckas</label><label lang="nb-NO">Hopp over fornyelse av abonnement hvis betalingen mislykkes</label><label lang="pl-PL">Pomiń odnowienie subskrypcji, jeśli płatność nie powiedzie się</label><label lang="cs-CZ">Přeskočit obnovu předplatného, pokud platba selže</label><label lang="sl-SL">Preskoči obnovitev naročnine, če plačilo ne uspe</label><label lang="hu-HU">Előfizetés megújítása kihagyása, ha a fizetés nem sikerül</label><label lang="fi-FI">Ohita tilauksen uusiminen, jos maksu epäonnistuu</label><label lang="da-DK">Spring abonnement fornyelse over, hvis betalingen mislykkes</label><label lang="sk-SK">Preskočiť obnovenie predplatného, ak platba zlyhá</label>
            <helpText>If skipped, the plugin will not create new orders on subscription renewals, if the payment was not successful. If not skipped, then a new order is created and the customer can pay again within Shopware.</helpText>
            <helpText lang="de-DE">Wenn es übersprungen wird, erstellt das Plugin keine neuen Bestellungen bei Abonnementverlängerungen, wenn die Zahlung nicht erfolgreich war. Wenn nicht übersprungen, wird eine neue Bestellung erstellt und der Kunde kann innerhalb von Shopware erneut bezahlen.</helpText>
            <helpText lang="nl-NL">Indien overgeslagen, zal de plug-in geen nieuwe bestellingen maken bij abonnementsverlengingen, als de betaling niet succesvol was. Indien niet overgeslagen, dan wordt er een nieuwe bestelling aangemaakt en kan de klant opnieuw betalen binnen Shopware.</helpText>
            <helpText lang="it-IT">Se saltato, il plugin non creerà nuovi ordini al momento dei rinnovi degli abbonamenti se il pagamento non è stato completato con successo. Se non è saltato, verrà creato un nuovo ordine e il cliente potrà effettuare nuovamente il pagamento all'interno di Shopware.</helpText><helpText lang="pt-PT">Se ignorado, o plugin não criará novas encomendas nas renovações de subscrições, caso o pagamento tenha falhado. Se não for ignorado, será criada uma nova encomenda e o cliente poderá efetuar um novo pagamento no Shopware.</helpText><helpText lang="es-ES">Si se pospone y el pago ha sido rechazado, el plugin no creará pedidos nuevos de renovación de suscripción. Si no se pospone, se creará un nuevo pedido y el cliente podrá pagar de nuevo dentro de Shopware.</helpText><helpText lang="sv-SE">Om hoppa över, kommer pluginet inte att skapa nya beställningar på prenumerationsförnyelser, om betalningen inte var framgångsrik. Om inte hoppa över, skapas en ny beställning och kunden kan betala igen inom Shopware.</helpText><helpText lang="nb-NO">Hvis hoppet over, vil ikke pluginen opprette nye ordrer ved fornyelse av abonnementet hvis betalingen ikke var vellykket. Hvis ikke hoppet over, så blir en ny bestilling opprettet og kunden kan betale på nytt gjennom Shopware.</helpText><helpText lang="pl-PL">Jeśli pominięto, wtyczka nie utworzy nowych zamówień przy odnowieniu subskrypcji, jeśli płatność nie zostanie pomyślnie zrealizowana. Jeśli nie pominięto, zostanie utworzone nowe zamówienie, a klient będzie mógł ponownie dokonać płatności w systemie Shopware.</helpText><helpText lang="cs-CZ">Pokud je obnovení přeskočeno, plugin nevytvoří nové objednávky při obnovení předplatného, pokud platba nebyla úspěšná. Pokud obnovení není přeskočeno, vytvoří se nová objednávka a zákazník může znovu zaplatit v systému Shopware.</helpText><helpText lang="sl-SL">Če je preskočeno, vtičnik ne bo ustvaril novih naročil ob obnovitvah naročnin, če plačilo ni bilo uspešno. Če ni preskočeno, se ustvari novo naročilo in stranka lahko ponovno plača v Shopware.</helpText><helpText lang="hu-HU">Ha kihagyja, a bővítmény nem hoz létre új megrendeléseket az előfizetések megújításakor, ha a fizetés nem volt sikeres. Ha nem hagyja ki, akkor új megrendelés készül és az ügyfél újra tud fizetni a Shopware-ben.</helpText><helpText lang="fi-FI">Jos ohitetaan, laajennus ei luo uusia tilauksia tilauksen uusimisen yhteydessä, jos maksu ei onnistunut. Jos ei ohiteta, niin uusi tilaus luodaan ja asiakas voi maksaa uudelleen Shopwareissa.</helpText><helpText lang="da-DK">Hvis oversprunget, vil plugin'et ikke oprette nye ordrer ved abonnement fornyelser, hvis betalingen ikke var succesfuld. Hvis ikke oversprunget, så oprettes en ny ordre, og kunden kan betale igen inden for Shopware.</helpText><helpText lang="sk-SK">Ak je táto možnosť preskočená, doplnok nevytvorí nové objednávky pri obnovení predplatného, ak platba nebola úspešná. Ak nie je preskočená, vytvorí sa nová objednávka a zákazník ju v Shopware môže opakovane zaplatiť.</helpText>
        </input-field>
        <input-field type="int">
            <name>subscriptionsReminderDays</name>
            <defaultValue>2</defaultValue>
            <label>Reminder period before renewal (days)</label>
            <label lang="de-DE">Erinnerungszeitpunkt vor Erneuerung (Tage)</label>
            <label lang="nl-NL">Herinneringsperiode voor verlenging (dagen)</label>
            <label lang="it-IT">Periodo di promemoria prima del rinnovo (giorni)</label><label lang="pt-PT">Período de aviso antes da renovação (dias)</label><label lang="es-ES">Período de recordatorio antes de la renovación (días)</label><label lang="sv-SE">Påminnelseperiod före förnyelse (dagar)</label><label lang="nb-NO">Påminnelsesperiode før fornyelse (dager)</label><label lang="pl-PL">Okres przypomnienia przed odnowieniem (dni)</label><label lang="cs-CZ">Období připomenutí před obnovením (dny)</label><label lang="sl-SL">Odpovedni rok pred obnovitvijo (dni)</label><label lang="hu-HU">Emlékeztető időszak a megújítás előtt (napok)</label><label lang="fi-FI">Muistutusaika ennen uusimista (päivinä)</label><label lang="da-DK">Påmindelsesperiode før fornyelse (dage)</label><label lang="sk-SK">Obdobie pripomenutia pred obnovením (dni)</label>
            <helpText>Set the days in prior to the renewal for sending renewal reminder events in the system (Flow Builder, Business Events, ...).</helpText>
            <helpText lang="de-DE">Legen Sie die Tage vor der Verlängerung für das Senden von Verlängerungs-Erinnerungsereignissen im System fest (Flow Builder, Business Events, ...).</helpText>
            <helpText lang="nl-NL">Stel de dagen voorafgaand aan de verlenging in voor het verzenden van herinneringsgebeurtenissen in het systeem (Flow Builder, Business Events, ...)</helpText>
            <helpText lang="it-IT">Imposta il numero di giorni prima del rinnovo per l'invio degli eventi di promemoria del rinnovo nel sistema (Flow Builder, Business Events, ...).</helpText><helpText lang="pt-PT">Defina quantos dias antes da renovação pretende enviar eventos de lembrete de renovação no sistema (Flow Builder, Business Events, ...).</helpText><helpText lang="es-ES">Establece días previos a la renovación para enviar notificación de renovación en el sistema (Flow Builder, Business Events, ...).</helpText><helpText lang="sv-SE">Ange antalet dagar före förnyelsen för att skicka påminnelsehändelser om förnyelsen i systemet (Flödesbyggare, Affärshändelser, ...).</helpText><helpText lang="nb-NO">Angi antall dager før fornyelsen for å sende påminnelsesvarsler om fornyelse i systemet (Flow Builder, Business Events, ...).</helpText><helpText lang="pl-PL">Ustaw liczbę dni przed odnowieniem, w których będą wysyłane przypomnienia o odnowieniu w systemie (Flow Builder, Wydarzenia Biznesowe, ...).</helpText><helpText lang="cs-CZ">Nastavte počet dní před obnovou pro odesílání připomínkových událostí obnovy v systému (Flow Builder, Business Events, ...).</helpText><helpText lang="sl-SL">Nastavite dneve pred obnovitvijo za pošiljanje obvestil o obnovitvi v sistemu (Flow Builder, poslovni dogodki, ...).</helpText><helpText lang="hu-HU">Állítsa be a napokat a megújítás előtt, amikor emlékeztető eseményeket küld a rendszerben (Flow Builder, Üzleti Események, ...).</helpText><helpText lang="fi-FI">Aseta uusimista edeltävät päivät uusimismuistutustapahtumien lähettämiseksi järjestelmässä (Flow Builder, Business Events, ...).</helpText><helpText lang="da-DK">Indstil antal dage før fornyelse for at sende påmindelsesbegivenheder i systemet (Flow Builder, Business Events, ...).</helpText><helpText lang="sk-SK">Nastavte počet dní pred obnovením, kedy sa v systéme odošlú udalosti pripomenutia obnovenia (Flow Builder, Business Events, ...).</helpText>
        </input-field>
        <input-field type="int">
            <name>subscriptionsCancellationDays</name>
            <defaultValue>0</defaultValue>
            <label>Latest notice period before renewal (days)</label>
            <label lang="de-DE">Letzter Kündigungstermin vor Verlängerung (Tagen)</label>
            <label lang="nl-NL">Laatste opzegtermijn voor verlenging (dagen)</label>
            <label lang="it-IT">Ultimo periodo di preavviso prima del rinnovo (giorni)</label><label lang="pt-PT">Último período de pré-aviso antes da renovação (dias)</label><label lang="es-ES">Período de aviso antes de la renovación (días)</label><label lang="sv-SE">Senaste uppsägningstid före förnyelse (dagar)</label><label lang="nb-NO">Siste varslingsperiode før fornyelse (dager)</label><label lang="pl-PL">Ostatni okres wypowiedzenia przed odnowieniem (dni)</label><label lang="cs-CZ">Poslední výpovědní lhůta před obnovou (dny)</label><label lang="sl-SL">Zadnji odpovedni rok pred obnovitvijo (dni)</label><label lang="hu-HU">Legkésőbb értesítési időszak a megújítás előtt (napok)</label><label lang="fi-FI">Viimeinen irtisanomisaika ennen uusimista (päiviä)</label><label lang="da-DK">Seneste varslingsperiode før fornyelse (dage)</label><label lang="sk-SK">Posledné obdobie oznámenia pred obnovením (dni)</label>
            <helpText>Set a notice period for customers before renewing the subscription. If a subscription renews on Friday and you use "2", then it can be cancelled or paused with latest Wednesday. Use "0" to always allow cancellations.</helpText>
            <helpText lang="de-DE">Legen Sie eine Kündigungsfrist für Verlänägerungen von Abonnements fest. Wenn sich ein Abonnement am Freitag verlängert und Sie "2" verwenden, kann es bis spätestens Mittwoch gekündigt oder pausiert werden. Verwenden Sie "0", um Stornierungen immer zuzulassen.</helpText>
            <helpText lang="nl-NL">Stel een opzegtermijn in voor klanten voordat ze het abonnement verlengen. Als een abonnement op vrijdag wordt verlengd en je gebruikt "2", dan kan het uiterlijk woensdag worden opgezegd of onderbroken. Gebruik "0" om annuleringen altijd toe te staan</helpText>
            <helpText lang="it-IT">Imposta un periodo di preavviso per i clienti prima del rinnovo dell'abbonamento. Se l'abbonamento si rinnova il venerdì e imposti "2", allora può essere annullato o messo in pausa entro e non oltre mercoledì. Usa "0" per permettere sempre le cancellazioni.</helpText><helpText lang="pt-PT">Defina um período de pré-aviso para os clientes antes de renovar a subscrição. Se uma subscrição for renovada à sexta-feira e utilizar "2", pode ser cancelada ou colocada em pausa até quarta-feira. Utilize "0" para permitir sempre os cancelamentos.</helpText><helpText lang="es-ES">Establece un período de aviso para el cliente antes de renovar la suscripción. Si una suscripción se renueva el viernes y utilizas "2", entonces se puede cancelar o pausar hasta el miércoles (último día). Usa "0" para permitir la cancelación en cualquier momento.</helpText><helpText lang="sv-SE">Ange en uppsägningstid för kunder före förnyelsen av prenumerationen. Om en prenumeration förnyas på fredag och du använder "2", kan den avbrytas eller pausas senast onsdag. Använd "0" för att alltid tillåta uppsägningar.</helpText><helpText lang="nb-NO">Angi en varslingsperiode for kundene før abonnementet fornyes. Hvis et abonnement fornyes på fredag og du bruker "2", kan det kanselleres eller pauses senest onsdag. Bruk "0" for alltid å tillate kanselleringer.</helpText><helpText lang="pl-PL">Ustaw okres wypowiedzenia dla klientów przed odnowieniem subskrypcji. Jeśli subskrypcja odnawia się w piątek, a ustawisz "2", można ją anulować lub wstrzymać najpóźniej w środę. Użyj "0", aby zawsze zezwalać na anulowanie.</helpText><helpText lang="cs-CZ">Nastavte výpovědní lhůtu pro zákazníky před obnovením předplatného. Pokud se předplatné obnovuje v pátek a nastavíte '2', může být zrušeno nebo pozastaveno nejpozději ve středu. Použijte '0', aby bylo zrušení možné kdykoliv.</helpText><helpText lang="sl-SL">Nastavite odpovedni rok za stranke pred obnovitvijo naročnine. Če se naročnina obnovi v petek in uporabljate "2", jo lahko prekličete oziroma ustavite najkasneje do srede. Uporabite "0", da vedno omogočite preklic.</helpText><helpText lang="hu-HU">Állítson be egy értesítési időszakot az ügyfél számára az előfizetés megújítása előtt. Ha egy előfizetés pénteken újul meg, és a „2”-t használja, akkor az előfizetés lemondható vagy szünetelhető szerdáig (utolsó nap). A "0" használatával bármikor engedélyezheti a törlést.</helpText><helpText lang="fi-FI">Aseta asiakkaille irtisanomisaika ennen tilauksen uusimista. Jos tilaus uusitaan perjantaina ja käytät "2", se voidaan peruuttaa tai keskeyttää viimeistään keskiviikkona. Käytä "0" salliaksesi peruutukset aina.</helpText><helpText lang="da-DK">Indstil en varslingsperiode for kunderne før fornyelse af abonnementet. Hvis et abonnement fornyes på fredag og du bruger "2", så kan det annulleres eller sættes på pause senest onsdag. Brug "0" for altid at tillade annulleringer.</helpText><helpText lang="sk-SK">Nastavte výpovednú lehotu pre zákazníkov pred obnovením predplatného. Ak sa predplatné obnovuje v piatok a nastavíte „2“, je ho možné zrušiť alebo pozastaviť najneskôr v stredu. Použite „0“, aby bolo zrušenie vždy povolené.</helpText>
        </input-field>
    </card>

    <card>
        <title>Rounding</title>
        <title lang="de-DE">Rundungen</title>
        <title lang="nl-NL">Afrondingen</title>
        <title lang="it-IT">Arrotondamento</title><title lang="pt-PT">Arredondamento</title><title lang="es-ES">Redondeo</title><title lang="sv-SE">Avrundning</title><title lang="nb-NO">Avrunding</title><title lang="pl-PL">Zaokrąglanie</title><title lang="cs-CZ">Zaokrouhlování</title><title lang="sl-SL">Zaokroževanje</title><title lang="hu-HU">Kerekítés</title><title lang="fi-FI">Pyöristys</title><title lang="da-DK">Afrunding</title><title lang="sk-SK">Zaokrúhľovanie</title>
        <input-field type="bool">
            <name>fixRoundingDiffEnabled</name>
            <label>Create line item in Mollie Dashboard</label>
            <label lang="de-DE">Erstelle Position in Mollie Dashboard</label>
            <label lang="nl-NL">Item maken in Mollie Dashboard</label>
            <label lang="it-IT">Crea voce di dettaglio nella Mollie Dashboard</label><label lang="pt-PT">Criar item de linha no Painel de Controlo da Mollie</label><label lang="es-ES">Crear línea de artículo en el Mollie Dashboard</label><label lang="sv-SE">Skapa radobjekt i Mollie Dashboard</label><label lang="nb-NO">Opprett linjepost i Mollie Dashboard</label><label lang="pl-PL">Utwórz pozycję w Panelu Mollie</label><label lang="cs-CZ">Vytvořit položku v Mollie Dashboard</label><label lang="sl-SL">Ustvari postavko v Mollie Dashboard</label><label lang="hu-HU">Sor létrehozása a Mollie Irányítópultján</label><label lang="fi-FI">Luo rivikohta Mollie-hallintapaneelissa</label><label lang="da-DK">Opret linjepost i Mollie Dashboard</label><label lang="sk-SK">Vytvoriť položku v Mollie Dashboard</label>
            <defaultValue>false</defaultValue>
        </input-field>
        <input-field type="text">
            <name>fixRoundingDiffName</name>
            <label>Line item name (optional)</label>
            <label lang="de-DE">Name der Position (optional)</label>
            <label lang="nl-NL">Naam regelitem (optioneel)</label>
            <label lang="it-IT">Nome della voce di dettaglio (opzionale)</label><label lang="pt-PT">Nome do item de linha (opcional)</label><label lang="es-ES">Nombre de línea de artículo (opcional)</label><label lang="sv-SE">Radobjektsnamn (valfritt)</label><label lang="nb-NO">Navn på linjeelement (valgfritt)</label><label lang="pl-PL">Nazwa pozycji (opcjonalnie)</label><label lang="cs-CZ">Název položky (volitelné)</label><label lang="sl-SL">Ime postavke (neobvezno)</label><label lang="hu-HU">Sor neve (opcionális)</label><label lang="fi-FI">Rivikohdan nimi (valinnainen)</label><label lang="da-DK">Navn på linjepost (valgfrit)</label><label lang="sk-SK">Názov položky (voliteľné)</label>
            <helpText>Set a custom name for your separate line item. This helps if you need to identify it in another system.</helpText>
            <helpText lang="de-DE">Lege einen benutzerdefinierten Namen für die separate Position fest. Dies hilft, wenn diese in einem anderen System identifiert werden muss.</helpText>
            <helpText lang="nl-NL">Stel een aangepaste naam in voor uw afzonderlijke regelitem. Dit is handig als u het in een ander systeem moet identificeren.</helpText>
            <helpText lang="it-IT">Imposta un nome personalizzato per la tua voce di dettaglio separata. Questo è utile se devi identificarla in un altro sistema.</helpText><helpText lang="pt-PT">Defina um nome personalizado para o seu item de linha separado. Isto ajuda-o se precisar de o identificar noutro sistema.</helpText><helpText lang="es-ES">Establece un nombre personalizado para la línea complementaria de artículo. Servirá de ayuda si necesitas identificarla en otro sistema.</helpText><helpText lang="sv-SE">Ange ett anpassat namn för ditt separata radobjekt. Detta hjälper om du behöver identifiera det i ett annat system.</helpText><helpText lang="nb-NO">Angi et egendefinert navn for din separate linjepost. Dette hjelper deg hvis du trenger å identifisere det i et annet system.</helpText><helpText lang="pl-PL">Ustaw niestandardową nazwę dla oddzielnej pozycji zamówienia. Będzie to pomocne, jeśli będziesz musiał zidentyfikować ją w innym systemie.</helpText><helpText lang="cs-CZ">Nastavte vlastní název pro samostatnou položku. To pomůže, pokud ji potřebujete identifikovat v jiném systému.</helpText><helpText lang="sl-SL">Nastavite prilagojeno ime za svojo ločeno postavko. To vam pomaga, če jo potrebujete identificirati v drugem sistemu.</helpText><helpText lang="hu-HU">Állítson be egy egyéni nevet a különálló sorhoz. Ez segíthet, ha azonosítania kell egy másik rendszerben.</helpText><helpText lang="fi-FI">Aseta nimet erillisille rivikohdille. Tämä auttaa, tunnistamaan sen toisessa järjestelmässä.</helpText><helpText lang="da-DK">Indstil et tilpasset navn for din separate linjepost. Dette hjælper, hvis du skal identificere den i et andet system.</helpText><helpText lang="sk-SK">Nastavte vlastný názov pre samostatnú položku. Pomôže to pri jej identifikácii v inom systéme.</helpText>
        </input-field>
        <input-field type="text">
            <name>fixRoundingDiffSKU</name>
            <label>Line item SKU (optional)</label>
            <label lang="de-DE">SKU der Position (optional)</label>
            <label lang="nl-NL">SKU regelitem (optioneel)</label>
            <label lang="it-IT">SKU della voce di dettaglio (opzionale)</label><label lang="pt-PT">SKU do item de linha (opcional)</label><label lang="es-ES">Referencia de línea de artículo (opcional)</label><label lang="sv-SE">Radobjekt SKU (valfritt)</label><label lang="nb-NO">Linjepost SKU (valgfritt)</label><label lang="pl-PL">Numer SKU pozycji (opcjonalnie)</label><label lang="cs-CZ">SKU položky (volitelné)</label><label lang="sl-SL">SKU postavke (neobvezno)</label><label lang="hu-HU">Sor SKU (opcionális)</label><label lang="fi-FI">Rivikohta SKU (valinnainen)</label><label lang="da-DK">SKU for linjepost (valgfrit)</label><label lang="sk-SK">SKU položky (voliteľné)</label>
            <helpText>Set a custom SKU value for your separate line item. This helps if you need to identify it in another system.</helpText>
            <helpText lang="de-DE">Lege einen benutzerdefinierten SKU Wert für die separate Position fest. Dies hilft, wenn diese in einem anderen System identifiert werden muss.</helpText>
            <helpText lang="nl-NL">Stel een aangepaste SKU in voor uw afzonderlijke regelitem. Dit is handig als u het in een ander systeem moet identificeren.</helpText>
            <helpText lang="it-IT">Imposta un valore SKU personalizzato per la tua voce di dettaglio separata. Questo è utile se devi identificarla in un altro sistema.</helpText><helpText lang="pt-PT">Defina um valor SKU personalizado para o seu item de linha separado. Isto ajuda-o se precisar de o identificar noutro sistema.</helpText><helpText lang="es-ES">Establece un valor SKU personalizado para tu línea de artículo separada. Esto ayuda si necesitas identificarlo en otro sistema.</helpText><helpText lang="sv-SE">Ange ett anpassat SKU-värde för ditt separata radobjekt. Detta hjälper om du behöver identifiera det i ett annat system.</helpText><helpText lang="nb-NO">Angi en egendefinert SKU-verdi for din separate linjepost. Dette hjelper deg hvis du trenger å identifisere det i et annet system.</helpText><helpText lang="pl-PL">Ustaw niestandardową wartość numeru SKU dla oddzielnej pozycji zamówienia. Będzie to pomocne, jeśli będziesz musiał zidentyfikować ją w innym systemie.</helpText><helpText lang="cs-CZ">Nastavte vlastní hodnotu SKU pro samostatnou položku. To pomůže, pokud ji potřebujete identifikovat v jiném systému.</helpText><helpText lang="sl-SL">Nastavite prilagojeno vrednost SKU za svojo ločeno postavko. To pomaga, če jo potrebujete identificirati v drugem sistemu.</helpText><helpText lang="hu-HU">Állítson be egy egyéni SKU értéket a különálló sorhoz. Ez segíthet, ha azonosítania kell egy másik rendszerben.</helpText><helpText lang="fi-FI">Aseta muokattu SKU-arvo erilliselle rivikohdalle. Tämä auttaa sinua tunnistamaan sen toisessa järjestelmässä.</helpText><helpText lang="da-DK">Indstil en tilpasset SKU-værdi for din separate linjepost. Dette hjælper, hvis du skal identificere den i et andet system.</helpText><helpText lang="sk-SK">Nastavte vlastnú hodnotu SKU pre samostatnú položku. Pomôže to, ak ju potrebujete identifikovať v inom systéme.</helpText>
        </input-field>
        <component name="mollie-pluginconfig-section-rounding">
            <name>molliePluginConfigSectionRounding</name>
        </component>
    </card>

    <card>
        <title>Javascript</title>
        <title lang="de-DE">Storefront Javascript</title>
        <title lang="nl-NL">Storefront Javascript</title>
        <title lang="it-IT">Storefront Javascript</title><title lang="pt-PT">Javascript</title><title lang="es-ES">Javascript</title><title lang="sv-SE">Javascript</title><title lang="nb-NO">Javascript</title><title lang="pl-PL">Javascript</title><title lang="cs-CZ">Javascript</title><title lang="sl-SL">Javascript</title><title lang="hu-HU">Javascript</title><title lang="fi-FI">Javascript</title><title lang="da-DK">Javascript</title><title lang="sk-SK">Javascript</title>
        <input-field type="bool">
            <name>useShopwareJavascript</name>
            <label>Use Shopware default Javascript in Storefront (requires manual compilation)</label>
            <label lang="de-DE">Verwenden Sie Shopware-Standard-Javascript in Storefront (erfordert manuelle Kompilierung)</label>
            <label lang="nl-NL">Gebruik Shopware standaard Javascript in Storefront (vereist handmatig bouwen)</label>
            <label lang="it-IT">Usa il Javascript predefinito di Shopware nella vetrina (richiede la compilazione manuale)</label><label lang="pt-PT">Utilizar o Javascript predefinido do Shopware no interface da loja (requer compilação manual)</label><label lang="es-ES">Usar Javascript predeterminado de Shopware para la interfaz de la tienda (requiere compilación manual)</label><label lang="sv-SE">Använd Shopwares standard-Javascript i skyltfönstret (kräver manuell kompilering)</label><label lang="nb-NO">Bruk Shopware standard Javascript i butikkfronten (krever manuell kompilering)</label><label lang="pl-PL">Użyj domyślnego JavaScript Shopware w interfejsie użytkownika (wymaga ręcznej kompilacji)</label><label lang="cs-CZ">Použijte výchozí Javascript Shopware v obchodě (vyžaduje ruční kompilaci)</label><label lang="sl-SL">Uporabite privzeti Javascript Shopware v trgovini (zahteva ročno pripravo)</label><label lang="hu-HU">Használja a Shopware alapértelmezett Javascript-ját az Árufronton (kézi fordítást igényel)</label><label lang="fi-FI">Käytä Shopwaren oletus-Javascriptia kauppapaikalla (vaatii manuaalista koodausta)</label><label lang="da-DK">Brug Shopware standard Javascript i butiksvinduet (kræver manuel kompilering)</label><label lang="sk-SK">Použiť predvolený Javascript Shopware v obchode (vyžaduje ručnú kompiláciu)</label>
            <defaultValue>false</defaultValue>
            <helpText>You can also bring back Mollie inside the "all.js" of the theme directly. This requires that you rebuild the Storefront on your own.</helpText>
            <helpText lang="de-DE">Sie können Mollie auch direkt in die "all.js" des Themes zurückbringen. Dies erfordert, dass Sie die Storefront selbst neu erstellen.</helpText>
            <helpText lang="nl-NL">Je kunt Mollie ook rechtstreeks terugbrengen in de "all.js" van het thema. Dit vereist dat je de Storefront zelf herbouwt.</helpText>
            <helpText lang="it-IT">Puoi anche reintegrare Mollie direttamente all'interno del file "all.js" del tema. Questo richiede che tu ricompili la vetrina autonomamente.</helpText><helpText lang="pt-PT">Também é possível recuperar a Mollie diretamente no "all.js" do tema. Para isso, é necessário reconstruir o interface da loja por conta própria.</helpText><helpText lang="es-ES">También puedes incluir Mollie dentro de "all.js" del tema. Esto ermite reconstruir la interfaz de la tienda por tu cuenta.</helpText><helpText lang="sv-SE">Du kan också återföra Mollie direkt i "all.js" av temat. Detta kräver att du bygger om butiken på egen hand.</helpText><helpText lang="nb-NO">Du kan også gjenbruke Mollie inne i "all.js" til temaet direkte. Dette krever at du bygger om butikkfronten på egen hånd.</helpText><helpText lang="pl-PL">Możesz również przywrócić Mollie bezpośrednio w pliku motywu „all.js”. Wymaga to samodzielnej odbudowy interfejsu użytkownika.</helpText><helpText lang="cs-CZ">Mollie můžete také přidat přímo do souboru 'all.js' šablony. K tomu je nutné si vlastními silami znovu sestavit Storefront.</helpText><helpText lang="sl-SL">Mollie lahko prav tako vrnete v "all.js" teme neposredno. To zahteva, da sami ponovno vzpostavite trgovino.</helpText><helpText lang="hu-HU">A Mollie-t is visszahelyezheti a téma "all.js"-ban. Ehhez szükséges, hogy saját magának kell újraépítenie az Árufrontot.</helpText><helpText lang="fi-FI">Voit myös palauttaa Mollien suoraan teeman "all.js"-tiedostoon. Tämä edellyttää, että rakennat kaupan uudelleen itse.</helpText><helpText lang="da-DK">Du kan også bringe Mollie tilbage i "all.js" i temaet direkte. Dette kræver, at du genopbygger butiksvinduet selv.</helpText><helpText lang="sk-SK">Mollie môžete tiež pridať priamo do súboru `all.js` témy. Na to je potrebné vlastnoručne znovu zostaviť Storefront.</helpText>
        </input-field>
    </card>

</config>
